<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nesoid &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/nesoid/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Finest Android Video games: Jewellust, Nesoid and Farm Frenzy</title>
		<link>/finest-android-video-games-jewellust-nesoid-and-farm-frenzy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[farm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[frenzy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jewellust,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nesoid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/best-android-games-jewellust-nesoid-and-farm-frenzy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jewellust The Android Jewellust sport navigates you to the Historic Egypt the place you may swap and break open colourful gems, discover mosaic tiles and [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Jewellust</strong></p>
<p>The Android Jewellust sport navigates you to the Historic Egypt the place you may swap and break open colourful gems, discover mosaic tiles and transfer round pyramids. The consumer has to navigate 30 ranges in 7 pyramids and an underground Temple to achieve Pharaoh&#8217;s energy. You can also make use of Santa to ship items, go 7 villages and resolve jigsaw puzzles. The sport takes you to quite a few ranges, power-ups and scores. You&#8217;ll be able to play in survival mode for prime scores, after getting expert on this sport, in any other case the consumer has to modify into marketing campaign mode, which is supposed for the novice within the sport. The sport presents wealthy graphics to take pleasure in, charming sounds and completely different shapes to mess around. The sport could be very humorous, addictive and a superb time-killing train.</p>
<p><strong>Nesoid (NES Emulator)</strong></p>
<p>Nesoid is the well-known NES/FC emulator for Android apps and it presents you virtually limitless gaming potentialities. It gives the power to play NES video games in your favourite Android telephones. However earlier than you begin enjoying video games, it&#8217;s important to obtain and play NES ROMS, after which set up it in your system. You&#8217;ll be able to retailer the video games in your Android telephone SD reminiscence card. It comprises some nice previous NES titles. Nesoid presents numerous choices to play. You&#8217;ll be able to alter the show to full display screen or native decision. It&#8217;s also possible to play NES Zapper video games utilizing the contact display screen. Nesoid thoughtfully options an on-screen digital d-pad together with begin and choose buttons. If you&#8217;re a GI/HTC proprietor and do not would possibly shopping for apps, Nesoid is a worthy choice. Nesoid is tailor-made for retro gaming followers.</p>
<p><strong>Farm Frenzy</strong></p>
<p>Farm Frenzy is a cellular model of the well-known award-winning PC sport and is now out there for Android. It&#8217;s a simulated sport and the target of the sport is that it&#8217;s important to take care of your individual farm and undertake low key farming technique. With this sport, you may handle your farm, rear the animals and harvest their produce like eggs or wool and make merchandise like cupcakes, cheese and butter, after which lastly supply it on the market. You need to feed the animals properly and shield them from predators. This consists of, bears, which falls from the sky on the cows and it&#8217;s important to fight them, in any other case it makes your progress gradual. By monetizing this sport, you should use the cash you earned to enhance your farm, after which transfer from one puzzle to a different with rising issue. The graphics for this sport is sweet and neat. The tutorials offered on this sport presents an added benefit and serves as a priceless information as the sport unfolds. General, it is a nice, distinctive and addicting sport for the Android followers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
