<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nutshell &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/nutshell/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia 70 Cell Cellphone Evaluation &#8211; In a Nutshell</title>
		<link>/nokia-70-cell-cellphone-evaluation-in-a-nutshell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nutshell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-70-cell-phone-review-in-a-nutshell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a nutshell, the Nokia 70 is taken into account to be a cellular messaging software. With options akin to a full keyboard with a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a nutshell, the Nokia 70 is taken into account to be a cellular messaging software. With options akin to a full keyboard with a large, high-resolution shade display, it&#8217;s simply tailored for enterprise in addition to private use.</p>
<p>Commonplace options embody textual content &#038; on the spot messaging by way of SMS and MMS, using POP3, IMAP4 and SMTP as its electronic mail shopper.</p>
<p>The Nokia 70 is able to viewing electronic mail attachments together with paperwork, spreadsheets, displays and PDF&#8217;s with modifying performance. A 2.0 mega pixel digital camera is normal for the Nokia 70, permitting for capturing and incorporating photographs in revolutionary methods.</p>
<p>GPRS, EGPRS, WCDMA and WLAN are included throughout the Nokia 70 permitting for quick and versatile connectivity choices.</p>
<p>Likened to a cellular workplace, the Nokia 70 acts as an organizer with options akin to contacts with photographs, a calender, to-do record, Microsoft Outlook and Lotus Notes. As well as, workplace functions, by way of Microsoft synchronization, embody doc, spreadsheet and presentation capabilities.</p>
<p>Web connectivity options embody the Nokia Browser, JavaScript 1.3 with 1.5 assist. All kinds of automotive enhancements can be found, enabling flexibility whereas speaking on the street.</p>
<p>As well as, the Nokia 70 is loaded with superior voice options akin to Voice Assist, a devoted voice key and a loudspeaker. The Voice Assist function provides audio suggestions from the contact record, telephone logs, and the voice mailbox. The devoted voice key supplies 1 button voice recording, voice dialing and push to speak. The loudspeaker permits for palms free use and is a sensible software for convention calls.</p>
<p>The Nokia 70 provides as much as 64 MB of built-in reminiscence, permitting for the storing of add-on functions, electronic mail attachments, images and MP3 recordsdata. The Nokia 70&#8217;s excessive capability storage provides the flexibility to swap out one reminiscence card for an additional with out having to take away the battery. With using miniSD reminiscence playing cards, the Nokia 70 has the flexibility to retailer 2 GB of knowledge.</p>
<p>In abstract, the Nokia 70 is a wonderful product with superior options. In case you are available in the market for a succesful cellular messaging software, the Nokia 70 is definitely value your consideration. Good Luck!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
