<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>2016 &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/2016/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>High 5 Android Apps in 2016</title>
		<link>/high-5-android-apps-in-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2016]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[high]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-5-android-apps-in-2016/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Android Apps phenomenon has gained momentum with many helpful apps. In the present day persons are addictive to those apps and in reality, they&#8217;re [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Android Apps phenomenon has gained momentum with many helpful apps. In the present day persons are addictive to those apps and in reality, they&#8217;re utilizing these apps for a lot of vital duties of their daily life. These helpful apps have lined virtually all of the vital elements of the digital world to make the lifetime of the frequent man simple. There are thousands and thousands of apps accessible to suit your necessities, let&#8217;s talk about a few of these helpful apps right here.</p>
<p><strong>Finest Android Safety App</strong></p>
<p><strong>Avast Cellular Safety:</strong> With greater than 100 million installs this Android anti-malware program presents prolonged providers like a name blocker, app locker, privateness advisor, firewall and lot extra. It additionally offers options like RAM booster, junk cleaner, Wi-Fi scanner and many others. It secures your units in opposition to malicious web sites, hyperlinks, emails, telephone calls, SMSs and many others. It additionally offers alerts for spyware and adware and adware apps. This anti-virus engine offers full an online defend in opposition to all doable threats.</p>
<p><strong>Finest File Supervisor App</strong></p>
<p><strong>File Supervisor (File Switch):</strong> This app is obtainable by Cheetah Cellular and has extra 50 million downloads. This totally featured file administration device presents intensive providers to customers like fundamental options of reduce, copy, paste, delete, search, compress, decompress choices and plenty of superior options like cloud assist, Wi-Fi file switch and lot extra. You need to use this handy device to view recordsdata by kind (picture, audio, video, downloads and many others.) and might entry them in a single faucet via Widgets. This wonderful app presents a number of protocols to switch recordsdata simply.</p>
<p><strong>Finest Cloud Backup App</strong></p>
<p><strong>G Cloud Backup:</strong> This app is the whole bundle to your storage worries. This app presents cloud backup to retailer your any file (footage, movies, audio, contacts, paperwork, messages, name logs and many others.) on it to maintain it secure and safe. You may additional entry these recordsdata anytime anyplace. You need to use this app to simply migrate your knowledge between numerous units and to increase your system&#8217;s cupboard space. It helps all Android units together with smartphones, tablets, iPhone and iPad.</p>
<p><strong>Finest Picture Modifying App</strong></p>
<p><strong>PicsArt Picture Studio:</strong> With greater than 300 million installs PicsArt Picture studio is considered one of greatest photograph enhancing apps accessible at the moment. It&#8217;s outfitted with 100s of highly effective photograph enhancing instruments like image mixing &amp; cropping, filters and many others. and has 1000s of free clipart packs, collage templates, stickers, fonts and lot extra which makes it one of the crucial highly effective photograph enhancing instruments. It really works as a photograph editor a collage maker and a drawing device to rework your common images into murals.</p>
<p><strong>Finest Health &amp; Life-style App</strong></p>
<p><strong>7 Minute Exercise:</strong> Adored by thousands and thousands of customers all over the world this app is scientifically confirmed that will help you take care of all of your health worries. It lets you drop extra pounds, strengthen your muscle mass, enhance cardiovascular capabilities and lot extra. In its intensive options it helps Google match, provides voice steerage, presents exercise logs, adjustable circuit time and relaxation time offers notifications for each day exercise and lot extra. That is the right selection to stay wholesome and match.</p>
<p>You need to use these helpful apps to make your expertise on Android spectacular and handy. Aside from these apps one frequent drawback customers face is cluttered and unorganized cupboard space on their units. It impacts system pace and efficiency. To take care of this case you should use Android Cleaner apps for immediate and higher outcomes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
