<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>aka &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/aka/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Land Rover S1 Cellular Cellphone AKA Sonim S1-XP3 Overview</title>
		<link>/land-rover-s1-cellular-cellphone-aka-sonim-s1-xp3-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aka]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[land]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s1-xp3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sonim]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/land-rover-s1-mobile-phone-aka-sonim-s1-xp3-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you consider &#8220;Land Rover&#8221;, you may think a really robust street automobile. However now the highly regarded Sonim Applied sciences have given the purchasers [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you consider &#8220;Land Rover&#8221;, you may think a really robust street automobile. However now the highly regarded Sonim Applied sciences have given the purchasers a brand new search for the off street cell phone. It&#8217;s the Land Rover S1 that has really captured and captivated the center of many a folks. The Land Rover cellphone is very designed for all these whose life is absolutely stuffed with the extraordinarily enthusiastic and adventurous moments.</p>
<p>The automotive producer and Sonim Applied sciences have collectively launched the S1 cell phone for the tech savvy customers. The rugged high quality cellphone is made for the customers who like to play and work in outdoor. This newest S1 cell phone by Land rover has really been hailed to be the strongest cellphone accessible in the complete world after it really survived being stood on the elephant, roasted at nice levels in an oven and dropped from a really excessive constructing. So far as the reminiscence of this cellphone is anxious, it may be simply upgraded with the assistance of reminiscence card slots.</p>
<p>The Land Rover S1 options about 1500 hours battery life, 2 megapixel digicam in addition to the extra loud ring tones. Some nice specs of this cellphone embrace the one meter depth, further lengthy battery, 18 hours discuss time, simple to make use of keyboard mechanics with its buttons examined to greater than 500,000 pushes, operational beneath -20 to 55 C temperatures, IP 67 Rated, immune to punctures and excessive stress of about 400 kg.</p>
<p>The Land Rover S1 is even suitable with big number of automotive kits and headsets and is offered with the belt clip, charger and headset together with being impervious to dust, drops, shocks and water. Land Rover now appears to comply with identical idea whereas constructing the cell phones as they do to make their top quality vehicles. The Land Rover telephones are actually sturdy and one may even count on them to really face up to harsh circumstances. However the one downside of the Land Rover S1 is that it isn&#8217;t the Smartphone.</p>
<p>One of the best half about S1 is that it comes with the particular 3 years guarantee. One would possibly acknowledge the fashion and design of this S1 cell phone as just like its successor Sonim XP3. You would possibly even acknowledge its cyclopean development however the arduous case is even harder than the opposite Sonim or Land Rover telephones. So, now the Sonim S1 is mud proof with the superb waterproof know-how.</p>
<p>Land Rover has really some helpful options which make the cellphone good and simple to make use of, just like the speaker for nice ring tones that are audible in loudest of locations, means to simply join the separate antenna, improve sign energy in addition to the very good Opera Mini browser to supply the correct net utilization.</p>
<p>Different notable options of the Land Rover S1 embrace the FM radio, Bluetooth and GPS system. So, what are you ready for? Get set go and purchase your S1 right now to take pleasure in high notch high quality of a excessive tech cellphone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
