<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>managers &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/managers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>High 5 Free SMS Managers for Android</title>
		<link>/high-5-free-sms-managers-for-android/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[high]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[managers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-5-free-sms-managers-for-android/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Software program functions, shortened to Apps, have helped improve a smartphone person&#8217;s capability to multitask. It presents all the things at your fingertips. Nonetheless, there [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Software program functions, shortened to Apps, have helped improve a smartphone person&#8217;s capability to multitask. It presents all the things at your fingertips. Nonetheless, there are a number of functions that don&#8217;t introduce something new; they enhance on present features.</p>
<p>Textual content messaging or SMS has been round for ages even earlier than Android opened its eyes to the world. An SMS permits you to convey advanced messages within the least variety of phrases. A couple of apps designed for Android have revamped the standard textual content messaging characteristic. They can help you set up SMSs in your system, present backup, common inbox cleanups and blocking and security measures. There are free and paid SMS supervisor apps for Android. We&#8217;ve mentioned 5 Free SMS Managers for Android.</p>
<p><strong>1. </strong><strong>SMS Backup n2 Supervisor: </strong></p>
<p>The identify offers you a touch of the first characteristic it presents. It permits you to backup and restore textual content messages. Once you obtain and set up the appliance in your system, a backup file is created in your SD card. All textual content messages are transferred out of your telephone to this backup file thereby liberating up tons of telephone reminiscence. It backups up all the things; you may delete what you don&#8217;t want. The opposite spotlight options embody the flexibility to ship worldwide messages at a low fee, bubble type chat view and multi-language assist.</p>
<p><strong>2. </strong><strong>Gate SMS: </strong></p>
<p>Gate SMS is one other free SMS supervisor for Android gadgets that may be downloaded on the Google Play retailer. That is an app to make use of in case your service expenses unusually excessive textual content charges. It presents web gateway assist and helps you save on each textual content message you ship. It identifies the operator robotically, reminds customers of unread messages and permits you to set a message ringtone of your selection with completely different ranges of vibration. The one disadvantage is that this free SMS administration app for Android shows a number of advertisements not current within the premium model.</p>
<p><strong>3. </strong><strong>SMS Guard: </strong></p>
<p>It is annoying to be bombarded with junk messages from unknown individuals. SMS Guard stands out for its blocking characteristic. You solely have so as to add the quantity to the Deny listing. Thereafter, all messages from that quantity will robotically be eliminated to the junk field or deleted with out notifications. Not all SMS supervisor functions are suitable with older variations of Android. SMS Guard helps Android variations 1.6 and up.</p>
<p><strong>4. </strong><strong>SMS Supervisor: </strong></p>
<p>How you want there was a solution to cover personal and private messages from prying eyes! Luckily, there&#8217;s one within the type of SMS Supervisor. It lets you transfer textual content messages from the Android inbox to the appliance inbox. The password safety characteristic makes it straightforward to cover private textual content messages from others. One other good characteristic is the flexibility to allow and disable notifications for incoming and outgoing textual content messages.</p>
<p><strong>5. </strong><strong>Auto SMS Cleaner /Deleter </strong></p>
<p>In case your inbox is full of junk and is consuming into your telephone reminiscence, it is time for a cleanup. We&#8217;re not speaking about deleting single messages. This greatest free Android SMS supervisor permits you to cleans a number of message at a time. The person has to enter the 2 dates between which he desires the messages to be deleted. One needn&#8217;t fear as deleted messages could be restored later.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
