<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>dv6-1354us &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dv6-1354us/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>HP Pavilion Dv6-1354US 15.6-Inch Laptop computer &#8211; An Sincere Assessment</title>
		<link>/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-an-sincere-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dv6-1354us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pavilion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sincere]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-an-honest-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very best laptops available in the market, they&#8217;re consistently producing new laptop computer fashions that include quite a lot of new and improved options. The brand new HP Pavilion DV6-1354US is at present one in every of HP&#8217;s newest 15.6-inch laptop computer fashions available in the market. It has a 2.2Ghz Core 2 Duo processor, 4GB of RAM and a bigger 500GB onerous drive. For show, this laptop computer has a 15.6-inch LED back-lit HD display screen (with a 1366 x 768 decision). Then there&#8217;s the set of Altec Lansing audio system that runs on SRS Premium sound expertise. Different specs embody 4 USB ports, a reminiscence card reader, HDMI output, Intel Wifi Hyperlink 100GBN, and rather more</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> The HP Pavilion DV6-1354US sports activities a shiny jet-black casing that&#8217;s properly contrasted with hints of silver. For an edge, the laptop computer is embellished with some round motifs. This mannequin measure at about 14.9 x 10.15 x 1.5 inches and weighs 6.34 kilos, which is in regards to the measurement of a mean 15-inch laptop computer. General, this laptop computer sports activities HP&#8217;s signature skilled and modern look.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> Judging from its specs, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US can be nicely suited to both work or play. It even comes with a tiny (but complete) distant management to allow you to entry quite a lot of multimedia controls from a distance. For graphics rendering, this mannequin makes use of the Intel Graphics Media Accelerator 4500MHD graphics card. The 6-cell batteries on this mannequin can last as long as 4 hours on one cost, which is kind of good for a laptop computer of this measurement (and specs). All in all, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US 15.6-inch laptop computer is designed for anybody who&#8217;s on the lookout for purposeful and inexpensive full-featured laptop computer. Presently, this laptop computer is promoting for round $699 per unit, which is a good worth for this very competent laptop computer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
