<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>large &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/large/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>HP Pavilion Dv8t Evaluate &#8211; Massive and Highly effective For Enterprise</title>
		<link>/hp-pavilion-dv8t-evaluate-massive-and-highly-effective-for-enterprise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dv8t]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[effective]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[highly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[massive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pavilion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[powerful,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-pavilion-dv8t-review-large-and-powerful-for-business/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The brand new HP Pavilion dv8t, the 18.4 inch monster from HP is so smooth. The laptop computer is massive and its Espresso black floor [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The brand new HP Pavilion dv8t, the 18.4 inch monster from HP is so smooth. The laptop computer is massive and its Espresso black floor is shiny. It&#8217;s heavier than the dv7t Choose Version by 0.78 kilos at 8.77 kilos and is 1.32 inch thick. The pocket book is most splendid for enterprise actions.</p>
<p>The brand new HP Pavilion dv8t incorporates a number of unbelievable options. Its working system is Real Home windows 7 64-bit. It consists of the choice of both Intel Core i7 -720QM Quad Core processor or Intel Core i7- 820QM Quad Core Processor each able to HyperThreading identical to within the HP desktops. The system reminiscence can attain 8 GB. There may be the choice for 2 exhausting drives so you possibly can improve as much as I TB of storage. The laptop computer additionally comes with 1GB Nvidia GeForce GT 230M graphics for gaming and different functions.</p>
<p>The 18.4 inch Excessive Definition HP Extremely BrightView Infinity Show with 1920&#215;1080 pixel decision has a tremendous show. The viewing angles for this pocket book are fairly spectacular for a shiny show. The keyboard feels easy and simple whereas typing on. Nevertheless, the backlight on the opposite notebooks is lacking on this one. Maybe it&#8217;s due to the intense LCD that HP thought-about the sunshine pointless.</p>
<p>The HP Pavilion dv8t consists of SuperMulti 8X DVD+/-R/RW optical drive with choice for improve to LightScribe SuperMulti 8X DVD+/-RW. The LightScribe permits the person to design and print labels on DVDs and CDs by creating monochrome picture. It additionally has choice for Intel Wi-fi-N Card with Bluetooth for networking.</p>
<p>The pocket book additionally consists of 4 USB ports (one for eSATA), Blu-Ray, non-compulsory TV tuner, VGA output, Ethernet port, HDMI port, 1394 Firewire, 5-in-1 Media card reader, 1 ExpressCard/54 Slot, Audio output and Lock slot. With all these ports, HP Pavilion dv8t ensures that your choices for connectivity are limitless.</p>
<p>The multimedia prospects on this pocket book are very exiting. The HDMI permits the person to get pleasure from watching films on the HDTV. The SRS audio and Altec Lansing audio system are additionally spectacular. Nevertheless, the 8 Cell Lithium Ion battery lifetime of this HP Pavilion dv8t is lengthy sufficient.</p>
<p>The HP Pavilion dv8t and different HP merchandise are offered at nice low cost to shoppers who&#8217;ve HP low cost coupons. These coupons can be found on-line and you might be suggested to use for them so that you could be profit from the reductions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
