<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>nv5331u &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/nv5331u/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Gateway NV5331u 15.6-Inch Laptop computer Evaluation</title>
		<link>/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-evaluation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gateway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nv5331u]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in all probability attributable to its nice set of specs, good design and cheap price ticket. This mannequin comes with an AMD Turion Extremely M600 dual-core processor (2.4Ghz). Then there&#8217;s the 15.6-inch HD show, ATI Radeon HD 4200 graphics card, and a set of stereo audio system (with Dolby Sound applied sciences). Among the different normal options embody the 8X DVD drive, multi-gesture observe pad, 4 USB ports and a HDMI port.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Though Gateway is known for his or her budget-friendly laptop computer fashions, their desktops and laptops look something however low-cost. Gateway has an awesome design crew and virtually every bit of machine rolled out from them has a really skilled and modern look. The Gateway NV5331u sports activities a classical and curvy design. It measures at 3.97 x 16.6 x 12.4 inches in dimensions and weighs 5.84 kilos.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is mostly an awesome mid-range laptop computer mannequin that&#8217;s nice for leisure of labor functions. The HD graphic card will likely be excellent for anybody who typically watches a number of motion pictures and HD movies on their laptop computer. The 4GB of RAM and the brand new i3 processor additionally allows you to carry out a wide range of heavy duties flawlessly. This mannequin is powered by a 6-cell battery that may last as long as 2 hours and 40 minutes on one full cost. In the meanwhile, the Gateway NV5331u 15.6-inch laptop computer is retailing for simply round $699 per unit, which is a superb worth for this set of specs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
