<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>flash &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/flash/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Assessment of Free Flash Recreation: Boxhead Zombie Wars</title>
		<link>/assessment-of-free-flash-recreation-boxhead-zombie-wars/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boxhead]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[recreation:]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zombie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/review-of-free-flash-game-boxhead-zombie-wars/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Boxhead Zombie Wars is a shooter sport managed with just one stick and one button. It&#8217;s at the moment obtainable on the iPad, iPod, and [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Boxhead Zombie Wars is a shooter sport managed with just one stick and one button. It&#8217;s at the moment obtainable on the iPad, iPod, and iPhone gadgets for $2.99. It&#8217;s the Boxhead sequence&#8217; fifth installment. Earlier than it grew to become a preferred shooter sport on cellular gadgets, Boxhead Zombie Wars was an internet sport developed by Sean Cooper. The sport was printed by MEDL Cell, who additionally printed the favored Fruit Blast and Jungly Soar.</p>
<p>In Boxhead Zombie Wars, you shoot hoards of undead zombies on three maps with three issue ranges. Your main purpose is to keep away from getting killed by the zombies and keep alive so long as doable. The cellular model of Boxhead Zombie Wars means that you can use your individual music as the sport&#8217;s background music as you play. The three issue ranges modify the amount and pace of the zombies that assault you. Boxhead Zombie Wars gives loads of selection on the way you need to kill the hoards of zombies coming at you. The sport has a complete of 11 weapons. The handgun works high quality if you would like the sport to be tougher, however the shotgun is best for killing a bunch of zombies every shot. You too can name an airstrike to wipe out all of the zombies within the area. Cautious timing of the airstrike is essential if you wish to keep alive on this sport. You too can place barricades to handle the zombies&#8217; path. You too can set-up some turrets that allow you to dispatch the nasty undead. The entire weapons want ammo aside from the handgun. Well being and ammo pickups commonly seem on the map.</p>
<p>Boxhead Zombie Wars even have Devils because the mini bosses. They will breathe hearth and are very harmful. They provide an enormous level enhance when you handle to kill them. In case you choose to solely kill zombies, you possibly can select to take away Devils from the sport by turning them off within the choices menu. There are some notable points when taking part in Boxhead Zombie Wars on a handheld system. The sport&#8217;s menus are a bit clunky and typically it doesn&#8217;t reply to your contact. The default pause button was typically unresponsive so I ended up having to make use of the weapons display to pause the sport. The sport characters additionally turn out to be paralyzed for a bit when hit. This implies that you would be able to simply kill a Satan by capturing him repeatedly, or you&#8217;ll certainly die whenever you&#8217;re attacked by two zombies on the similar time. The sport additionally has a couple of bugs. One critical bug is that the sport sometimes stops after you full a stage, leaving you unable to proceed the sport.</p>
<p>Total, the sport was enjoyable to play however the value $2.99 is a bit an excessive amount of. There are a number of higher video games priced at $2.99 and you may play this sport without spending a dime on the internet with none points. Nonetheless, when you do not thoughts a couple of touchscreen points and bugs, Boxhead Zombie Wars may be a number of enjoyable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
