<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>samsung &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/samsung/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Samsung Omnia Smarthone Overview</title>
		<link>/samsung-omnia-smarthone-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[omnia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smarthone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/samsung-omnia-smarthone-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Samsung pulled out a heavyweight final 12 months once they revealed the Omnia, which has reportedly seen good gross sales via the 12 months [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Samsung pulled out a heavyweight final 12 months once they revealed the Omnia, which has reportedly seen good gross sales via the 12 months and hit prime spot in Krusell&#8217;s listing for prime 10 promoting telephones in November 2008. Combining excessive efficiency enterprise content material, nice design and wealthy multimedia expertise, the Samsung Omnia is the primary 5 megapixel digicam Home windows Cell smartphone and actually its greatest factors could be its wonderful design and multitude of options.</p>
<p>As talked about, design must be the Omnia&#8217;s biggest power. It received a slick platinum entrance, huge and simple to press name buttons, and most of all massive show which is a good bonus when utilizing GPS. The telephone matches proper within the palm of person so the grip feels snug. Plus, the Omnia is slim and light-weight, making it very snug to hold round with out having to really feel a cumbersome bulge in your pockets. General, the Omnia has a really polished look to it and this may actually please customers who go for fashion.</p>
<p>The Samsung Omnia&#8217;s different main robust level is it&#8217;s many providing in time period of features and options. One of many main options of the Omnia is the 5 megapixel digicam. Not solely does it have flash built-in and auto focus but additionally a &#8220;Extensive Dynamic Vary&#8221; mode which makes full use of the show of the telephone. As well as, the digicam has features similar to face monitoring, smile detection, digital picture stabilizer, auto-panorama shot and geotagging. The telephone has an inside reminiscence capability of 8GB and as much as 16GB, which will be elevated by way of microSD playing cards (most 16GB) for a complete capability of 32GB.</p>
<p>The Omnia additionally contains a built-in GPS receiver with A-GPS assist and since it&#8217;s A-GPS the satellite tv for pc lockdown is quicker than common GPS. Though there isn&#8217;t any GPS navigation software program, customers can at all times use the Google Maps software that&#8217;s preinstalled. Another main function is the accelerometer. Transferring on, the Samsung Omnia has nice multimedia playback capabilities; it&#8217;s the first DivX licensed Home windows Cell PDA so that you get DivX playback proper from the get go. General, multimedia playback was very passable total for each video and audio. Different multimedia options embrace the FM radio and picture browser. Connectivity sensible, the Omnia has the whole lot apart from infrared, which no one makes use of anymore lately.</p>
<p>There may be a lot to speak in regards to the usability, particularly by way of the responsiveness. The Omnia is barely sluggish, which I consider is because of the Widgets which means that eradicating it from the GUI will possible end in a superior telephone. The Omnia additionally would not include a stylus so you need to use the magnetic model between the 2 name buttons. This take a little bit of time getting used to however customers can at all times use their fingers as effectively or higher but if they&#8217;ve their very own spare stylus.</p>
<p>The Omnia has its deficiencies and its worth is usually a bit scary, reflecting the premium you must pay, however total the Samsung Omnia is a good telephone. It oozes class and elegance in addition to possessing nice options and functionalities, making it appropriate for each enterprise and leisure.</p>
<p>Execs: Large display, quick processor, massive reminiscence, excellent digicam</p>
<p>Cons: Homeless stylus</p>
<p>Scores:</p>
<p>Efficiency: 5/5<br />
<br />Options: 5/5<br />
<br />Design: 5/5<br />
<br />Worth: 4/5</p>
<p>Samsung Omnia Specs:</p>
<p>Processor: Marvell PXA312 @ 624MHz</p>
<p>Reminiscence: 8GB/16GB in-built storage</p>
<p>Working System: Home windows Cell 6.1 Skilled with TouchWiz UI</p>
<p>Frequency: HSDPA (7.2 Mbps), GSM 850/900/1800/1900, GPRS, EDGE</p>
<p>Display: 3.2&#8243; WQVGA TFT LCD (240 x 400)</p>
<p>Connectivity: Bluetooth, USB2.0, Wi-Fi, HSDPA</p>
<p>Others: 5.0 megapixel CMOS, microSD card slot, GPS</p>
<p>Dimensions: 112 x 56.9 x 12.5 mm</p>
<p>Weight: 122g</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge Overview</title>
		<link>/samsung-galaxy-s6-edge-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/samsung-galaxy-s6-edge-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Smartphone performance advances have actually reworked the units, making them very handy within the trendy world. Whether or not you&#8217;re keen on listening to music [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smartphone performance advances have actually reworked the units, making them very handy within the trendy world. Whether or not you&#8217;re keen on listening to music or catching up the most recent movies and flicks, share pictures and even different enterprise recordsdata and paperwork, now you can do all of it from any given location and at any given time when you&#8217;ve gotten a smartphone. Producers proceed to unveil extra advances with each new system they introduce out there and the longer term seems to be solely brighter for this business. The Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge is amongst the smartphones one can find out there and has change into a well-liked system due to a number of options.</p>
<p><strong><u>The Bodily Options </u></strong></p>
<p>The smartphone runs on the Android Lollipop working system and has an inside reminiscence of 32GB and 3GB RAM. Measuring 5.1 inches and weighing 132 g, it is a system that you&#8217;ll take pleasure in utilizing and carrying with you on daily basis in your wants.</p>
<p>This smartphone is the world&#8217;s first telephone with twin edge show. The show is thermoformed in such a means that it creates an built-in edge display screen that may bend to ship a differentiated pioneering design that solely goes to indicate the superior high quality of the system. The perimeters are curved for higher grips and examine enhancement. The curve gives a view that&#8217;s extra like a widescreen TV view making each expertise nice.</p>
<p>It has a close to invisible bezel on the display screen design which gives better entry to extra of the telephone display screen space and on the similar time additionally enhances the customers viewing expertise. This system has vibrant vivid photos in all mild situations and has enhanced out of doors visibility to make use in daylight atmosphere completely. It has a excessive pixel density of 577ppi to supply that final viewing expertise in any given location and at any time of day whatever the climate situations.</p>
<p><strong><u>Efficiency </u></strong></p>
<p>Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge has a fast voice command response. This can be a function that saves you loads of effort and time you may have used touching the varied buttons to entry the features and options that you simply want. You may personalize the system utilizing a nickname after which give instructions. You will discover the function very useful, particularly in conditions the place motion has been restricted.</p>
<p>Utilizing the smartphone, communication has been taken to an entire new stage. You may shade code your favourite contact on edge display screen in order that while you get notifications you possibly can inform from who they&#8217;re from utilizing the colours. It means which you could establish the contact for any e-mail, missed name or message you obtain even when the telephone is face down. The sting display screen is certainly handy and intuitive providing an expertise that has not been loved earlier than.</p>
<p><strong><u>Different options </u></strong></p>
<p>It has a extremely succesful digital camera providing good vibrant pictures which you could additionally monitor shifting topics and nonetheless have the clearest pictures ever. It has quick charging expertise with ten minutes of cost managing to serve you for at the very least 4 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Launch Assessment for Samsung Galaxy Notice 7</title>
		<link>/launch-assessment-for-samsung-galaxy-notice-7/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[launch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[note]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[notice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/release-review-for-samsung-galaxy-note-7/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Samsung is a globally famend multinational firm with its headquarters in Seoul, South Korea. The corporate has plenty of totally different product verticals sharing the [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Samsung is a globally famend multinational firm with its headquarters in Seoul, South Korea. The corporate has plenty of totally different product verticals sharing the identical model identify globally.</p>
<p>Samsung was based in 1938 and it entered the electronics business within the late 1960&#8217;s. Because the 1990&#8217;s, the corporate&#8217;s main income has been from its electronics vertical, comprising of cellphones and semiconductors.</p>
<p>Samsung Electronics is the dad or mum firm&#8217;s largest subsidiary and was the world&#8217;s largest I.T. firm within the calendar 12 months 2012 holding place quantity 4 when it comes to market capitalization.</p>
<p>The dad or mum firm, Samsung, has at all times been a robust regional powerhouse influencing a lot of South Korea&#8217;s economic system, political dynamics and social tradition. Samsung&#8217;s whole income figures accounts for near 17% of the nation&#8217;s whole GDP.</p>
<p>Samsung Telecommunications is a significant enterprise unit inside Samsung Electronics and providers product traces masking mobiles, MP3 gamers, laptop computer computer systems and so forth.</p>
<p>The timeframe submit 2007 has proved phenomenal for Samsung Telecommunication&#8217;s cellphones vertical spurring a development price of 40%. Quickly, it turned the world&#8217;s 2nd largest cellular machine producer after Apple Inc.</p>
<p>At the moment, Samsung is the main producer of good telephones working the cellular working system Google Android with a worldwide market share of 46%.</p>
<p>The newest providing from Samsung Telecommunication&#8217;s is the good cellphone mannequin, Samsung Galaxy Notice 7. In India, the Samsung Notice 7 was launched amidst a lot fanfare in August 2016.</p>
<p>When it comes to the show, the Samsung Galaxy Notice 7 ships with a 5.7 inch capacitive contact display screen delivering a crisp and clean decision of 1440&#215;2560 pixels at a PPI measuring of 518.</p>
<p>Processing energy for the Galaxy Notice 7 is delivered by means of an Exynos 8890 octa-core processor clocking 1.6 GHz.</p>
<p>The Notice 7 ships out with a RAM of 4GB whereas the inner storage is pegged at 64GB which might be expanded (as much as 256GB) by means of a microSD card.</p>
<p>For purchasers who aren&#8217;t digital camera shy, the Samsung Galaxy Notice 7 is provided with a 12 megapixel rear digital camera (with flash) coupled with a 5 megapixel entrance digital camera for selfie lovers.</p>
<p>From the software program standpoint, the Galaxy Notice 7 runs on Android Marshmallow having model 6.0.1.</p>
<p>Battery life is sort of good contemplating the unit has an influence cell equating to 3500mAh which is non-removal in nature.</p>
<p>The Notice 7 has dimensions measuring 153.50 x 73.90 x 7.90 (peak x width x thickness) and the burden is a snug 169 grams.</p>
<p>The Samsung Galaxy Notice 7 has help for a single Nano SIM card and features a plethora of recent connectivity instruments like Wi-Fi, 4G LTE, NFC, Bluetooth and GPS and so forth.</p>
<p>Onboard sensors inside the Galaxy Notice 7 cowl proximity, ambient mild, accelerometer and gyroscope. Audio headphones are supported by the Galaxy Notice 7 by means of a 3.5mm jack.</p>
<p>The Galaxy Notice 7 is offered in a spread of vibrant colours like Blue, Gold, Silver &#038; Black.</p>
<p>The Notice 7 may even are compatible with a spread of Samsung Equipment like Good Watch, wi-fi headsets and so forth.</p>
<p>Potential prospects can now place confirmed orders by means of all the most important e-commerce platforms like Flipkart, Amazon and Snapdeal.</p>
<p>The discharge of the Samsung Galaxy Notice 7 additional cements the place of Samsung Electronics as a potent rival within the intensely aggressive world marketplace for good telephones.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
