<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>update &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/update/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>All of the Finest Options of the Android Nougat Replace</title>
		<link>/all-of-the-finest-options-of-the-android-nougat-replace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[all]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nougat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[replace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[update]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/all-the-best-features-of-the-android-nougat-update/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Android Nougat is the newest replace of Google&#8217;s working system; Android.. Right here on this article we will probably be telling you when you may [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Android Nougat is the newest replace of Google&#8217;s working system; Android.. Right here on this article we will probably be telling you when you may replace Android in your telephone, pill and different gadgets, how one can profit the replace&#8217;s options. What are the professionals and cons of updating your outdated Android Lollipol or Marshmallow to Android Nougat.</p>
<p>We present you the principle new options of Android 7.0 Nougat, why it is so vital, and what mobiles will obtain this model of Google&#8217;s working system.</p>
<p>Every time a brand new model of Android seems, on this case the 7.0, the kick-off is given for all manufacturers to announce which telephones will probably be upgraded to Android Nougat. And as usually occurs on earlier events, comes the frustration whenever you see that your smartphone is not going to be up to date, otherwise you see that the replace comes too late.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, there might all the time be a doubt about the advantages of Android 7.0 over the earlier system, and if it actually price it. The reality is that with every new working system not solely come useful and aesthetic enhancements, but additionally at a safety degree, so upgrading to Android 7.0 is kind of handy.</p>
<p>What are the brand new options of Android Nougat? Many and really demanded by customers. The primary and most placing is the inclusion of the primary multiventana in Android inventory, one thing needed given the rise in display screen dimension we&#8217;ve seen lately, with the 5.5 inches more and more widespread in all Segments.</p>
<p>The arrival of digital actuality doesn&#8217;t go unnoticed by the brand new Android system, and it will embody a sequence of options that may optimize the efficiency of the smartphone along side Daydream VR, the newest digital actuality glasses from Google. Additionally included is compatibility with Vulkan, an API that may enable higher optimization of video games and purposes that require excessive graphics efficiency.</p>
<p>There are additionally enhancements within the degree of optimization and administration of accessible assets, with a twist to the Doze battery saving system, in order that now the system will save vitality from the second we flip off the display screen.</p>
<p><u><strong>Safety in Android Nougat gadgets:</strong></u></p>
<p>In fact, safety in Android 7.0 Nougat can also be enhanced by a redesign of your encryption system to extra successfully shield our information, in order that, for an instance, ransonware won&#8217;t be able to change our password In case we&#8217;ve established one to dam our telephone.</p>
<p>We even have the potential for automated updates working within the background, see the supply of the appliance set up, the direct boot, which permits a a lot quicker begin of the smartphone, or instantaneous apps, purposes that may be executed with out Should be put in in our terminal.</p>
<p>Which telephones will obtain Android 7.0</p>
<p>All these options appear sufficient causes for manufacturers to make an effort to improve a smartphone to Android 7.0. Most producers like Samsung, LG or Huawei have targeted on masking their most iconic fashions, forsaking the entry-level fashions or gadgets previous to 2016. This isn&#8217;t the case for BQ.</p>
<p>Bq_aquaris_x5_plus_1</p>
<p>BQ has introduced the listing of telephones that may obtain Android Nougat, the place we&#8217;ve been capable of see nice surprises. As we mentioned, if we speak in regards to the entry vary, there&#8217;s just about no replace adverts from any producer, so the Aquaris A4.5 and the three fashions of the brand new vary Aquaris U would be the first cell of lower than 150 € to obtain Android 7.0.</p>
<p>If we go a step above, we discover that the Aquaris X5 and the Aquaris X5 Plus will even function Android Nougat, however not solely the newest developments in BQ will function this new system, as each the Aquaris M5 and the Aquaris M5.5 (2015 fashions) obtain this replace.</p>
<p>In fact, their rivals are additionally trying to supply the newest flagships such because the Samsung Galaxy S7, Huawei P9 or the LG G5 will even function the improve to Android 7.0. The variations we see in essentially the most inexpensive ranges.</p>
<p>Whereas within the mid-range there are manufacturers that make extra effort like Motorola with its Moto G4, Huawei P9 Lite, or Samsung Galaxy A, we see as different fashions as vital because the Samsung Galaxy J3, LG K10, or the Huawei P8 Lite Is not going to obtain the brand new Android 7.0.</p>
<p>With this we see how there are manufacturers that actually care about giving an extended life to every mannequin belonging to its product vary, whereas others overlook to cowl some segments. What is obvious is that the replace to Android Nougat needs to be a figuring out issue when selecting a smartphone right now.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
