<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>comparision &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/comparision/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Android Vs. iPhone Comparision</title>
		<link>/android-vs-iphone-comparision/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comparision]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vs.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-vs-iphone-comparision/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are numerous iPhones and Android Smartphones out there, giving rise to confusion over which one could be chosen. There have been a lot of [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are numerous iPhones and Android Smartphones out there, giving rise to confusion over which one could be chosen. There have been a lot of debates, discussions about whether or not Android or an iPhone is the perfect purchase. I imagine an Android telephone is best than an iPhone.</p>
<p>The next are the explanations as to why an Android telephone is best than an iPhone:</p>
<p>1. Choice: <br />There are quite a few Android telephones and deciding on a particular Android telephone relies on many components like storage, working system, high quality of digicam, show display screen, color, and so forth.</p>
<p>2. Personalization: <br />Android is the only option if one desires a custom-made cellular. A 3rd part-app could be put in if one does not like the usual keypad. Android telephone lets one customise their predictive textual content on messages, has cloud storage for all photos, a well being app, third-party keyboards, swype texting, and so forth.</p>
<p>3. {Hardware}: <br />That is certainly one of fundamental cause for a transparent reduce argument between Android and iPhone. Specializing in two present flagship Android and iPhone mobiles, one can get higher clarification over the argument. Following is the comparability;</p>
<p>Samsung Galaxy S7 Edge (Android)</p>
<p>RAM 4GB <br />Display screen Measurement 5.5 inch <br />Display screen Decision 2560X1440 <br />Display screen Sort AMOLED IPS <br />PIXEL Density 534ppi <br />Measurement 150.9x 72.6x 7.7 mm <br />Weight 5.54 oz (157g) <br />Wi-fi/Quick Charging Sure <br />3.5mm Jack (Aux) Sure <br />Entrance-facing digicam 5 megapixels <br />Working System Android 6.0 (Marshmallow) <br />Processor Octa-core 2.3 GHz Exynos 8890</p>
<p>Apple iPhone7 Plus (iPhone)</p>
<p>3GB <br />5.5 inch <br />1920X1080 <br />401ppi <br />158.2&#215;77.9&#215;7.3mm <br />6.63 oz (192g) <br />No <br />7 megapixels <br />iOS 10 <br />Quad-core 2.3 GHz <br />Apple A10 Fusion</p>
<p>Primarily based on the above comparability Samsung Galaxy S7 Edge, launched 6 months sooner than Apple iPhone 7 Plus is of higher high quality with regards to {hardware}.</p>
<p>4. The Google Play<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Retailer: <br />In comparison with Apple App retailer, submitting an app to Google App retailer is much more possible as Apple goes by means of a tedious technique of checking whether or not your app so submitted follows their tips or not. This course of can forestall malware related by downloading an app. Alternatively Apple denies your app entry into the app retailer if chevron image has been used within the improper means thereby aiming at creating an ideal app. Nevertheless submitting an Android constructed app to Google&#8217;s App retailer is way simpler than that in Apple making it much less aggravating advert simpler to create an app.</p>
<p>5. Widgets and Multitasking: <br />Widgets are an enormous plus to Android than iOS because the Apps carried out are restricted at iOS as they are often added solely on the notification centre. Notably, Apple doesn&#8217;t have any widgets on the homepage so as to de-clutter whereas all types of Widgets like customized clock, climate, alarms, telephone name, electronic mail, messages, flashlight, and so forth., are a favorite at Android and could be arranges on the house display screen as per ones &#8216;alternative. Multitasking on Android could be very simple to make use of than at iPhone. Multitasking on Apple is considerably helpful and has not been carried out correctly whereas multitasking on Android has been helpful for fairly a very long time that makes it a winner over Apple iPhones.</p>
<p>6. Expanded Reminiscence Specification:</p>
<p>Many Android telephones have expandable reminiscence that an iPhone does not have. As a substitute Apple would want an additional funding to improve any of their telephones from 16 GB to 32 or 64 GB micro SD card into iPhone. Contemplating this, Android is once more a winner.</p>
<p>7. Detachable Battery <br />A number of of the Android telephones have a detachable battery that may be changed with a generic battery of liking. Whereas that isn&#8217;t the case in utilizing Apple iPhones as one proudly owning it has to go to an Apple retailer. A number of the Android telephones like LG G5 supply a separate battery to be used.</p>
<p>8. Sturdiness: <br />Many of the Android telephones are sturdy as they&#8217;re made from robust plastic or poly-carbonate than iPhones which are largely aluminium based mostly.</p>
<p>Primarily based upon all of the above comparisons, shopping for an Android telephone is extra advantageous than shopping for an iPhone. Lastly contemplating the market share, the market dimension of Android telephones is greater than iPhones. So it is higher to personal an Android telephone than an iPhone.</p>
<p>Thank You</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
