<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>guidelines &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/guidelines/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Cellular Pleasant Insurance coverage Company Web site Guidelines</title>
		<link>/cellular-pleasant-insurance-coverage-company-web-site-guidelines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[checklist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[company]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coverage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[friendly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[guidelines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[insurance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pleasant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[site]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/mobile-friendly-insurance-agency-website-checklist/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With over 50% of web site guests and electronic mail recipients viewing info on their cellular units, and plenty of doing so from their social [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over 50% of web site guests and electronic mail recipients viewing info on their cellular units, and plenty of doing so from their social media platforms, it is all the time a good suggestion to evaluate your insurance coverage company web site to make sure your purchasers and prospects have a optimistic web site consumer expertise. Listed here are some key areas to deal with when reviewing your insurance coverage company web site:</p>
<p><strong>Do Not Make a Separate Cellular Model of Your Web site</strong></p>
<p>A number of years in the past, your small business may need two web sites, an internet site for desktop customers and one for cellular units. This can be a actually dangerous thought in the present day, because it doubles your efforts and might annoy purchasers, prospects and search engines like google.</p>
<p><strong>Use Responsive Design Ideas</strong></p>
<p>Responsive design makes use of coding to regulate an internet site based mostly on the dimensions of the viewport. Strategies have superior shortly and also you not have to cover content material from cellular customers. You&#8217;ll be able to showcase your content material for each desktop and cellular customers.</p>
<p><strong>At all times Use Excessive-Decision Photographs</strong></p>
<p>With cellular units utilizing high-resolution retina shows, it&#8217;s crucial your web site makes use of the best decision pictures obtainable. It is suggested that cellular pictures be twice the decision of desktop pictures to accommodate for retina shows.</p>
<p><strong>Use Bigger Font Sizes</strong></p>
<p>The scale of fonts is essential with regards to cellular design. Fonts have to be massive sufficient to learn with out additional zooming. A basic rule of thumb is to maintain your fundamental font measurement round 14px.</p>
<p><strong>Button Measurement Ought to Additionally Be Massive</strong></p>
<p>Buttons must also be massive on cellular units. You don&#8217;t want to frustrate a possible buyer as a result of they tried to hit the contact button however unintentionally hit your privateness coverage. Usually, 44px by 44px is an efficient rule of thumb.</p>
<p><strong>Preserve it Easy</strong></p>
<p>A less complicated format helps guarantee there&#8217;s much less to go mistaken when sizing to suit on a cellular system. It is going to additionally make it simpler to your prospects and purchasers to seek out related info. Be sure you evaluate every key aspect in your insurance coverage company web site and asses its worth. Is every aspect positioned the place it could greatest be seen by guests?</p>
<p><b>Use the Google Cellular Pleasant Check</b></p>
<p>Use Google&#8217;s <a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" href="https://search.google.com/search-console/mobile-friendly">Mobile Friendy Test</a> to make sure your web site is cellular compliant, and doesn&#8217;t have any points stopping the location from displaying appropriately on cellular units. Google deems an internet site as mobile-friendly if their Googlebot detects the next key attributes:</p>
<p>路 Hyperlinks and buttons are simple to make use of on a cellular system</p>
<p>路 The textual content font is readable with out zooming</p>
<p>路 Web site avoids unusual cellular software program similar to Flash</p>
<p>路 The content material and pictures routinely measurement with out scrolling</p>
<p>In case your company web site wants updating and also you lack the interior assets to take action, or your company is trying to enhance inbound site visitors and insurance coverage leads, you possibly can take into account outsourcing your web site initiative to a proficient insurance coverage company advertising agency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
