<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>omnia &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/omnia/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Samsung Omnia Smarthone Overview</title>
		<link>/samsung-omnia-smarthone-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[omnia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smarthone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/samsung-omnia-smarthone-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Samsung pulled out a heavyweight final 12 months once they revealed the Omnia, which has reportedly seen good gross sales via the 12 months [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Samsung pulled out a heavyweight final 12 months once they revealed the Omnia, which has reportedly seen good gross sales via the 12 months and hit prime spot in Krusell&#8217;s listing for prime 10 promoting telephones in November 2008. Combining excessive efficiency enterprise content material, nice design and wealthy multimedia expertise, the Samsung Omnia is the primary 5 megapixel digicam Home windows Cell smartphone and actually its greatest factors could be its wonderful design and multitude of options.</p>
<p>As talked about, design must be the Omnia&#8217;s biggest power. It received a slick platinum entrance, huge and simple to press name buttons, and most of all massive show which is a good bonus when utilizing GPS. The telephone matches proper within the palm of person so the grip feels snug. Plus, the Omnia is slim and light-weight, making it very snug to hold round with out having to really feel a cumbersome bulge in your pockets. General, the Omnia has a really polished look to it and this may actually please customers who go for fashion.</p>
<p>The Samsung Omnia&#8217;s different main robust level is it&#8217;s many providing in time period of features and options. One of many main options of the Omnia is the 5 megapixel digicam. Not solely does it have flash built-in and auto focus but additionally a &#8220;Extensive Dynamic Vary&#8221; mode which makes full use of the show of the telephone. As well as, the digicam has features similar to face monitoring, smile detection, digital picture stabilizer, auto-panorama shot and geotagging. The telephone has an inside reminiscence capability of 8GB and as much as 16GB, which will be elevated by way of microSD playing cards (most 16GB) for a complete capability of 32GB.</p>
<p>The Omnia additionally contains a built-in GPS receiver with A-GPS assist and since it&#8217;s A-GPS the satellite tv for pc lockdown is quicker than common GPS. Though there isn&#8217;t any GPS navigation software program, customers can at all times use the Google Maps software that&#8217;s preinstalled. Another main function is the accelerometer. Transferring on, the Samsung Omnia has nice multimedia playback capabilities; it&#8217;s the first DivX licensed Home windows Cell PDA so that you get DivX playback proper from the get go. General, multimedia playback was very passable total for each video and audio. Different multimedia options embrace the FM radio and picture browser. Connectivity sensible, the Omnia has the whole lot apart from infrared, which no one makes use of anymore lately.</p>
<p>There may be a lot to speak in regards to the usability, particularly by way of the responsiveness. The Omnia is barely sluggish, which I consider is because of the Widgets which means that eradicating it from the GUI will possible end in a superior telephone. The Omnia additionally would not include a stylus so you need to use the magnetic model between the 2 name buttons. This take a little bit of time getting used to however customers can at all times use their fingers as effectively or higher but if they&#8217;ve their very own spare stylus.</p>
<p>The Omnia has its deficiencies and its worth is usually a bit scary, reflecting the premium you must pay, however total the Samsung Omnia is a good telephone. It oozes class and elegance in addition to possessing nice options and functionalities, making it appropriate for each enterprise and leisure.</p>
<p>Execs: Large display, quick processor, massive reminiscence, excellent digicam</p>
<p>Cons: Homeless stylus</p>
<p>Scores:</p>
<p>Efficiency: 5/5<br />
<br />Options: 5/5<br />
<br />Design: 5/5<br />
<br />Worth: 4/5</p>
<p>Samsung Omnia Specs:</p>
<p>Processor: Marvell PXA312 @ 624MHz</p>
<p>Reminiscence: 8GB/16GB in-built storage</p>
<p>Working System: Home windows Cell 6.1 Skilled with TouchWiz UI</p>
<p>Frequency: HSDPA (7.2 Mbps), GSM 850/900/1800/1900, GPRS, EDGE</p>
<p>Display: 3.2&#8243; WQVGA TFT LCD (240 x 400)</p>
<p>Connectivity: Bluetooth, USB2.0, Wi-Fi, HSDPA</p>
<p>Others: 5.0 megapixel CMOS, microSD card slot, GPS</p>
<p>Dimensions: 112 x 56.9 x 12.5 mm</p>
<p>Weight: 122g</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
