<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>glasses &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/glasses/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Evaluate of the VISION-800 3D Glasses</title>
		<link>/evaluate-of-the-vision-800-3d-glasses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glasses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision-800]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/review-of-the-vision-800-3d-glasses/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There&#8217;s a new and high-quality mannequin of video glasses, VISION-800, which has first rate technical traits, high quality picture or video, in addition to a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s a new and high-quality mannequin of video glasses, VISION-800, which has first rate technical traits, high quality picture or video, in addition to a practical picture. It options the actual bodily 3D impact, which hardly does hurt to customers&#8217; eyes. Additionally, you possibly can retailer your favourite reveals or movies in these glasses and watch them with the glasses whereas in virtually any a part of your condominium or free transferring. On the identical time, you get an entire absence of any wires due to the wi-fi know-how. Now, let&#8217;s check out some particulars concerning the VISION-800 3D glasses.</p>
<p><strong>Options</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>New interpersonal interplay: The VISION-800 glasses liberate customers from the house constraints of computer systems, supporting being utilized in any posture customers like, standing, sitting and mendacity down.</li>
<li>Actual bodily 3D (i.e. actual 3D dual-screen): In contrast the prevailing 3D TV and different show merchandise, which getting a single display screen, the brand new VISION-800 glasses immediately show the picture to customers&#8217; eyes by way of the 2 LCOS micro-monitor display screen with extra glorious 3D impact. This could be low-carbon and environmentally pleasant. What&#8217;s extra, the high-quality photos hardly do hurt to customers&#8217; eyes, extra humanism.</li>
<li>The VISION-800 adopts a 0.5-inch mild supply, even smaller than a nail, which offers an 80-inch digital display screen by way of the optical system, higher than the atypical display screen 1080P.</li>
<li>Based mostly on the MTK6582 Quad Core ARM clocked at 1.3GHz, it comes with 1GB LPDDR2 RAM and 2GB eMMc storage reminiscence.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Foremost Features</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A sensible cloud terminal: The VISION-800 is straightforward to hold. With the built-in WIFI and exterior reminiscence card, it helps for wealthy cloud functions.</li>
<li>Giant-screen actual 3D cinema: These goggles assist 3D video storage and playback, and photos real-time transmission.</li>
<li>Outfitted with a wi-fi Bluetooth mouse, it helps taking part in on-line video games.</li>
<li>For IPD adjustment, individuals with myopia want one other lens fastened within the goggles.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Abstract</strong></p>
<p>The VISION-800 glasses could be your most suitable option for having fun with the video, audio, eBook, photos and so forth by connecting the Web through WiFi. With the 80-inch 4:3 digital show and 3D stereo sound, it might give an unbelievable personal visible feast. As well as, it additionally helps TF card as much as 32G. Thus, you possibly can simply obtain your favourite film, music, video and extra to you TF card after which play them on the 80-inch display screen. I feel this may be a tremendous and attention-grabbing expertise for anybody who likes having fun with life.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
