<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>benefits &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/benefits/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Benefits Of an Android Cellphone</title>
		<link>/benefits-of-an-android-cellphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advantages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benefits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/advantages-of-an-android-phone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the planet of smartphones, Android is on high of the checklist because it&#8217;s essentially the most extensively used OS. The recognition is due to [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the planet of smartphones, Android is on high of the checklist because it&#8217;s essentially the most extensively used OS. The recognition is due to the options the OS presents. Given under are a couple of benefits provided by the OS. Learn on to know extra.</p>
<p><b>Multitasking</b></p>
<p>Multitasking is without doubt one of the finest benefits of an Android telephone. In different phrases, you are able to do a number of duties concurrently in your telephone. As an example, you may browse web sites whereas listening to your favourite music from the consolation of your room.</p>
<p><b>Ease Of Notification</b></p>
<p>You&#8217;ll get notification of every exercise that occurs in your telephone, akin to emails, messages and so forth. In different phrases, you&#8217;ll get alerts out of your telephone and you&#8217;ll miss nothing.</p>
<p><b>Straightforward Accessibility </b></p>
<p>In the event you love enjoying video games in your telephone, nothing is healthier than Android. You may obtain from tons of video games from the app retailer of Android. Many of the apps will be downloaded and put in free of charge.</p>
<p><b>Completely different Fashions</b></p>
<p>Android provides different firms the permission to make use of its OS. Since there&#8217;s a large number of Android telephones, you could have the freedom to go for a model primarily based in your wants. The standard of smartphones has gone up due to the stiff competitors amongst totally different producers.</p>
<p><b>Modified ROM </b></p>
<p>In the event you don&#8217;t love the unique show of the Android-based telephone you personal, you will get it modified in an effort to get the one you want.</p>
<p><b>Cellphone Choices </b></p>
<p>Except for multitasking, one other nice advantage of Android is that it presents a number of choices. As an example, iOS comes from Apple, however Android comes from tons of producers like Sony Ericson, HTC and Samsung, simply to call a couple of.</p>
<p><b>Greater Display screen</b></p>
<p>In the event you love large screens, chances are you&#8217;ll need to go for an Android telephone. The show of those telephones is greater than that of iPhone.</p>
<p><b>Google Maniac</b></p>
<p>In the event you love Google merchandise, Android smartphones are your finest guess. The reason being that the OS comes with a number of Google services that assist you to synch your Google account with a number of different units. In consequence, you should utilize all of Google companies, akin to Google docs, Google reader, Google maps and so forth.</p>
<p><b>Widget</b></p>
<p>Android OS presents some widgets on its residence display screen that assist you to entry the settings with none downside. So, that is one other nice advantage of proudly owning a smartphone that runs Android.</p>
<p><b>Value Efficient</b></p>
<p>If you&#8217;re uninterested in utilizing primary telephones and also you need to take pleasure in one thing higher at an reasonably priced value, chances are you&#8217;ll need to go for an Android telephone. Alternatively, Blackberry, Apple or another smartphone prices you much more than Android. You spend lots much less however get nearly all the options that you may take pleasure in with a comparatively dearer smartphone.</p>
<p>So, when you have been on the lookout for a great cost-effective smartphone, we recommend that you just try a great Android telephone. These telephones supply all of what you want with out spending an arm and a leg.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Advantages Of Utilizing An Android Smartphone</title>
		<link>/7-advantages-of-utilizing-an-android-smartphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advantages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benefits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[using?]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[utilizing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/7-benefits-of-using-an-android-smartphone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for one of the best OS? It&#8217;s possible you&#8217;ll be considering that Android is one of the best. In line with statistics, [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you looking for one of the best OS? It&#8217;s possible you&#8217;ll be considering that Android is one of the best. In line with statistics, round 80% of smartphones run Android. Given beneath are some fundamental advantages of an Android smartphone. Learn on.</p>
<p>Customizable <br />With Android, you should utilize quite a lot of widgets, which suggests you&#8217;ll be able to customise your cellphone with none downside. You may set your cellphone up the best way you need. However, iOS does not permit that a lot flexibility.</p>
<p>Android {hardware} <br />Since Android has an open nature, any firm is allowed to fabricate an Android-based smartphone. So, so far as the options are involved, you&#8217;ve numerous flexibility. iPhones are comparatively dearer. Nonetheless, you&#8217;ll be able to select from a variety of gadgets that run Android.</p>
<p>{Hardware} and software program innovation <br />Since Android is open supply, a lot of firms are making helpful improvements. As a matter of truth, there are lots of of firms and people who&#8217;re benefitting from the open nature of Android. Consequently, you&#8217;ll be able to expertise a lot of options. A few of them even had been discovered on Android earlier than they even confirmed up on Apple smartphones, reminiscent of WebP photos, WiFi Direct and so forth.</p>
<p>Apps are cheaper <br />The Google Play Retailer has much more apps than the Apple App Retailer. On high of that, the apps on PlayStore are cheaper. And a lot of the apps can be found to obtain free of charge. So, that is one other nice benefit of Android over Apple iOS. So, if you&#8217;re on a funds however wish to have essentially the most enjoyable together with your cellphone, we propose that you just search for an excellent Android-based cellphone.</p>
<p>The open ecosystem <br />Apart from the Google Play Retailer, you&#8217;ll be able to obtain apps from quite a lot of different locations. Nonetheless, try to be conscious of the dangers that you might have to take when putting in apps from another supply. However Android will simply warn you, and the ultimate determination will likely be yours.</p>
<p>Extra storage <br />In the event you purchase an iPhone, you&#8217;re going to get 16GB of space for storing. However, Android gadgets supply twice the area. Apart from this, you&#8217;ll be able to improve the space for storing additional with an SD card. You may&#8217;t take pleasure in this profit with an iPhone.</p>
<p>Higher display decision <br />So far as the Apple smartphones are involved, the primary smartphone that got here with a 1080p decision display was iPhone 6 Plus. However, Android gadgets got here with this spectacular decision display fairly earlier. Furthermore, the prevailing sequence of Android smartphone have gotten a lot farther than that. For example, should you go for the Sony Experia Z5 Premium, you&#8217;ll be able to take pleasure in a 4K display. However even the cheaper Android telephones have already got 1080p decision.</p>
<p>So, in case you have been questioning whether or not you must go for Android or iOS, we propose that you just evaluate the advantages of the 2. For this function, you&#8217;ll be able to re-read this text to know concerning the main advantages. This may assist you to take advantage of knowledgeable determination and it is possible for you to to get your arms on one of the best handset.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
