<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>prime &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/prime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Prime Six Free Apps for Streaming Motion pictures and TV Exhibits on Android</title>
		<link>/prime-six-free-apps-for-streaming-motion-pictures-and-tv-exhibits-on-android/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exhibits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[motion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pictures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[six]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[streaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-six-free-apps-for-streaming-movies-and-tv-shows-on-android/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are numerous apps that permit the Android customers stream films and TV reveals on their gadgets totally free. Right here, I&#8217;m itemizing a number [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are numerous apps that permit the Android customers stream films and TV reveals on their gadgets totally free.</p>
<p>Right here, I&#8217;m itemizing a number of the topmost apps, which can put a whole bunch of films and numerous TV reveals at your fingertips.</p>
<p><strong>SPB TV</strong></p>
<p>SPB TV is a tremendous app that gives you  mixture of content material from the world over. The house owners of Android smartphones, tablets, and Android TV can take pleasure in greater than 200 TV channels with this app.</p>
<p>To have a clean viewing expertise, you would want an LTE, Wi-Fi, 3G, or WiMAX Web connection. The app has greater than greater than 5 million customers.</p>
<p><strong>Crackle</strong></p>
<p>Crackle is a well-liked free app which to stream films and TV reveals on Android gadgets. You may get a tremendous assortment of media with this app, nonetheless, in change, you&#8217;ll have to watch the commercials in the course of the stream.</p>
<p>Among the authentic packages of Crackle authentic embody Jerry Seinfeld&#8217;s Comedians in Vehicles Getting Espresso, Sports activities Jeopardy and Joe Grime 2.</p>
<p><strong>Hulu</strong></p>
<p>Hulu allows you to watch films and premium TV reveals on their Android telephones or smartphones totally free. This app is full of the newest and traditional reveals, films, and widespread youngsters&#8217; packages.</p>
<p>Effectively, there aren&#8217;t any subscription costs of the free model of Hulu, to get full entry to app&#8217;s library you&#8217;ll have to pay $7.99 a month (with ads) or $11.99 a month (with out ads).</p>
<p><strong>Showbox </strong></p>
<p>Showbox is one other glorious app with an enormous library of over 10,000 films and TV reveals. This app additionally means that you can obtain the content material and watch it offline.</p>
<p>This app isn&#8217;t obtainable on Google Play, however you&#8217;ll be able to obtain it from its official web site. It has greater than 10 million lively customers.</p>
<p><strong>Toonmania</strong></p>
<p>Toonmania is an superior app that&#8217;s particularly developed and crafted to observe anime and cartoons with consolation. This app options an enormous choice of dubbed Anime, Cartoons, and Anime/Cartoon Motion pictures. The instinctive and clear structure of this app means that you can simply navigate all the pieces and uncover what you&#8217;re in search of.</p>
<p>At the moment, Toonmania isn&#8217;t obtainable at Google Play Retailer. Nonetheless, you&#8217;ll be able to obtain the APK file of this app from Aptoide.</p>
<p><strong>Crunchyroll:</strong></p>
<p>Crunchyroll is one other widespread app to stream Amine films and reveals on Android. This app is out there at Google Play Retailer and has greater than 5 million downloads.</p>
<p>The free model of this app function ads, however you may get an ad-free premium model for $4.99 a month with a 14-day trial.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prime VR Video games for Your Android Cellphone</title>
		<link>/prime-vr-video-games-for-your-android-cellphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[your]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-vr-games-for-your-android-phone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[VR or digital actuality is the brand new innovation by the tech world that has turn into an integral a part of virtually all kinds [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>VR or digital actuality is the brand new innovation by the tech world that has turn into an integral a part of virtually all kinds of video games on-line. Digital actuality is a 3 dimensional atmosphere that will render dwell and interactive expertise to the gamer. There video games are being designed to boost the standard of the video games and to offer an superior gaming expertise to the gamer. The extra revolutionary and user-friendly variations of those VR video games are developing in lately which are suitable sufficient even on sensible telephones.</p>
<p>Newest VR video games would help you play the sport on a number of gadgets with a single gamer identify. You possibly can play whereas commuting additionally through the use of your android telephones. The newest variations of VR video games are designed in such a method that they&#8217;d render the identical expertise as a computer, laptop computer or a play station. Now as we all know what&#8217;s a VR sport is all about let us take a look at few newest VR video games designed for android telephones,</p>
<p>• Mekorama VR &#8211; A puzzle sport the place you need to information a small robotic by means of varied ranges. At the start it is fairly easy as a result of there will likely be few stones to be moved however the problem will increase from one degree to the following. On this sport you employ the controller to maneuver the stones and present the robotic the best way to maneuver up.</p>
<p>• Hunters Gate: A sport for motion lovers &#8211; You&#8217;ll turn into a savior of the world when the world has been attacked by demons and you need to maintain them again. It is a fun-filled and graphically spectacular sport. It is a well-known rolling sport whose components make you stronger over time and can train you new abilities. For taking part in this sport it&#8217;s essential to use daydream controllers, and these controllers assist you to in retaining observe of what is occurring from above, which reduces your an excessive amount of interplay with the digital motion.</p>
<p>• Want for Pace: A VR sport for admirers of pace, the sport enhances the feeling of pace by Digital Actuality and might be the perfect racing sport for Daydream-capable sensible telephones. An thrilling trip is assured due to its impeccable graphics and breakneck-pace. Moreover that the selection of customization and automobile tuning made this sport extra enchanting and thrilling.</p>
<p>• Gun jack 2: Finish of Shift &#8211; A sport the place you&#8217;ll be sitting on cannon on our photo voltaic system and fend off the attackers who&#8217;re determined to steal the minerals from our planet. You can be having immense arsenal weapons and might management the whole lot together with your gaze.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
