<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>6086 &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/6086/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Evaluation: Nokia 6086 Cell Cellphone</title>
		<link>/evaluation-nokia-6086-cell-cellphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[6086]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/review-nokia-6086-mobile-phone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Nokia 6086 is yet one more clam shell providing from the Nokia secure, though consistent with current clam shell choices the cellphone affords greater [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Nokia 6086 is yet one more clam shell providing from the Nokia secure, though consistent with current clam shell choices the cellphone affords greater than you&#8217;ll think about on preliminary viewing. The scale of the handset are a compact 92 mm x 46 mm x 23 mm and it weighs in at a lightweight weight 84 grams, making it good for straightforward carriage, and conveniently suits into the smallest of pockets. The battery energy provide affords 240 hours GSM and 96 hours UMA standby time, with 5 hours GMS and 6 hours UMA discuss time &#8211; greater than beneficiant in immediately&#8217;s market place.</p>
<p>That is Nokia&#8217;s second entry within the modern UMA (unlicensed cell entry) market, which permits straightforward roaming entry between all the customary cell phone networks, along with a relentless WiFi connection within the related areas. One of these system is proving ever extra widespread, though the Nokia 6086 additionally helps GSM 850, GSM 900, GSM 1800, GSM 1900 in addition to UMA. The cell makes use of the highly effective EDGE software program which is the freshest available in the market place.</p>
<p>The handset itself is at the moment obtainable in Black and White and affords two LCD shows, one on the surface for name and message alerts with out opening the cellphone, in addition to the principle bigger show throughout the physique of the cellphone. Whereas the keyboard is a barely totally different fashion to the older Nokia telephones, the positioning of the keys and navigation roll key is similar.</p>
<p>The cellphone itself affords quite a lot of messaging choices from the usual SMS to MMS to the now important electronic mail facility, which is supported by the inbuilt WAP browser. The cellphone additionally affords a digital camera facility, though this isn&#8217;t as updated because it could possibly be. It does nonetheless assist Bluetooth knowledge switch, though Nokia has determined to go away out the extra widespread infra purple choice &#8211; in a transfer away from the usual. As Bluetooth is now widespread throughout most digital units, this shouldn&#8217;t be a significant challenge.</p>
<p>The Nokia 6086 additionally has quite a lot of JAVA video games pre-installed to assist with these lengthy journeys, and affords the now acquainted private organiser widespread in 99% of immediately&#8217;s cell phones. With further reminiscence ports so as to add further capability, the Nokia 6086 has the vast majority of performance required, though it isn&#8217;t a top quality mannequin &#8211; extra of an entry stage new know-how cellphone. Due out in early 2007, additional opinions will comply with.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
