<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>one &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/one/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Huawei Mate 10 Professional Vs Google Pixel 2 XL: Which One to Select?</title>
		<link>/huawei-mate-10-professional-vs-google-pixel-2-xl-which-one-to-select/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choose]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huawei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pixel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[select]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[which]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xl:]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/huawei-mate-10-pro-vs-google-pixel-2-xl-which-one-to-choose/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;re going to purchase new Android flagship prior to later, then likelihood is nice that you&#8217;ll find Google&#8217;s Pixel 2 XL. It is among [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re going to purchase new Android flagship prior to later, then likelihood is nice that you&#8217;ll find Google&#8217;s Pixel 2 XL. It is among the finest Android units on the planet, backed by a effectively famend Tech Title, &#8220;Google&#8221;.</p>
<p>However wait! There&#8217;s one other competitor which is providing some good options to their clients. The Huawei Mate 10 Professional smartphone matches up carefully with the Pixel 2 XL by Google on few high options and numerous tech specs; nonetheless, there are some key particulars that differ between them. Right here, we&#8217;re going to present you probably the most outstanding options of those two units with the comparability so you possibly can see the place one is doing higher than the opposite. So, let&#8217;s get began.</p>
<p><b>Design &amp; Show</b></p>
<p>Each the Huawei Mate 10 Professional and the Google Pixel 2 XL cellphones function few very 2017 design components. The Pixel 2 XL telephone machine has comparatively larger when it comes to dimensions that options gorgeous rounded corners and tiny bezels. <br />Huawei Mate 10 Professional does not have rounded corners although, nevertheless it does have a pleasant massive show. The Pixel 2 XL comes with the combination of glass and steel on the again. Then again, the Mate 10 Professional smartphone sticks with solely glass on the rear facet.</p>
<p>So far as show is worried, each telephones supply 6-inches massive sufficient show; nonetheless, the Pixel 2 XL has a P-OLED show, and Mate 10 Professional is backed by AMOLED show. Pixel 2 XL by Google provides barely higher show decision and density of 2880&#215;1440 and 537ppi respectively than the Huawei Mate 10 Professional&#8217;s 2160&#215;1080 pixel decision and 402ppi pixel density. Different options are nearly equivalent in each like Display safety and Display to physique ratio.</p>
<p><b>Efficiency</b></p>
<p>Google Pixel 2 XL comes with the identical 6 months previous Qualcomm Snapdragon 835 processor chip. Little question, it is among the quickest chips round however as in comparison with the newest flagship Android telephones, it is thought of as outdated. Nonetheless, it has loads to expertise super-fast and loopy smartphone expertise with 4GB sufficient RAM and newest Android 8.0 Oreo onboard.</p>
<p>And if you see the Huawei Mate 10 Professional, it has new and up to date HiSilicon Kirin 970 chip, which is much better than its predecessor. Backed by a neural processing unit inside for A.I necessities in addition to machine studying adapting function, that is really a velocity grasp, notably with 6GB of prolonged RAM.</p>
<p>All in all, the Kirin 970 compares very effectively, when it comes to velocity, efficiency, and on a regular basis utilization, to the Snapdragon 835 chip in benchmark testing.</p>
<p><b>Battery</b></p>
<p>Google Pixel 2 XL contains a robust Li-Ion battery with a capability of 3520mAh. Huawei gives much more highly effective Li-Polymer 4000mAh battery. It is a core distinction. And each telephones supply quick charging.</p>
<p><b>Digital camera</b></p>
<p>Huawei Mate 10 Professional goes with the same dual-camera strategy as you discovered within the P10 and P10 Plus telephones, with a 12 Mega Pixels main sensor and 20MP monochromatic secondary sensor. The digital camera of Mate 10 Professional quickly focuses on no matter you shoot and adjusts accordingly, because of its A.I abilities. That is really one of many main smartphone cameras in the marketplace right now, with none doubt.</p>
<p>However after we see the Pixel 2 XL Digital camera, it provides numerous new and thrilling options like laser autofocus and part detection and may ship spectacular pictures swiftly. As a consequence of Google&#8217;s state-of-the-art picture processing skills, you&#8217;ll get one thing unbelievable each time you shoot, and even in low mild situations. However nonetheless, it&#8217;s a single lens shooter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Android Smartphone: How one can Select the Finest?</title>
		<link>/android-smartphone-how-one-can-select-the-finest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[can]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choose]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[select]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-smartphone-how-to-choose-the-best/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many Smartphones have been launched within the know-how market within the latest time. It&#8217;s due to altering know-how and the software program that makes it [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many Smartphones have been launched within the know-how market within the latest time. It&#8217;s due to altering know-how and the software program that makes it troublesome for customers to choose. If  the standards for selecting the perfect out there possibility in Android Smartphone then you may be simply in a position to decide one for your self. Allow us to discover out the standards that it is advisable to know for selecting the perfect Android Smartphone.</p>
<p>Very first thing that it is advisable to take into account are the specs. Allow us to scrutinize these one after the other and discover out.</p>
<p><b>1. OS or Working System</b></p>
<p>Earlier than you resolve on selecting the most recent out there model, you first have to know that Android retains getting updates. Due to this fact, when you personal an Android that isn&#8217;t on par with the most recent software program model out there then you needn&#8217;t fear. You may improve your gadget and obtain the most recent Android model. The variations can be found on-line for downloads, you&#8217;ll be able to simply entry these by means of your gadget or login to acquire the most recent model. Newest software program model has many options, free choices and is appropriate with the brand new Smartphones. With new OS (Working System), it is possible for you to to obtain new wallpapers, get a quicker entry, have a brand new menu and different such added options.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, it&#8217;s essential to bear in mind one factor that not each Android is designed to obtain updates. Typically there are updates out there for particular OS solely whereas others are rendered out of date. For instance, you have already got Gingerbread; you may be tied to it till you get an replace for this specific model. Do not forget that software program improve will not be one thing assured. It&#8217;s higher to go for an Android model that&#8217;s able to receiving new updates and the latest model ought to be saved in thoughts whereas making a purchase order.</p>
<p><b>2. Updates</b></p>
<p>Being eager on making software program updates is comprehensible however what if you&#8217;re not in a position to deploy the identical in your gadget? One important factor is that you must go for the most recent gadget out there. Select the most recent handset out there. You may come throughout varied Xperia sequence or Galaxy sequence and so forth with totally different manufacturers. A modern out there gadget is able to accepting software program upgrades. You must control the most recent out there model to know if the mentioned producer is eager on releasing one other software program improve for that particular gadget.</p>
<p>When selecting an Android Smartphone, going for the latest model of OS is essential and when you can&#8217;t discover one with Jelly Bean, accept Ice Cream Sandwich however examine to see if the producer has promised, has launched or is engaged on releasing a Jelly Bean replace. Probably the most reliable producers in terms of gadget upgrades are HTC, Motorola, Samsung and Google. HTC has essentially the most spectacular Android upgrades of its units however Motorola (run by Android) has a fame of quick upgrades. Notice that producer updates usually include newer widgets, instruments and fixes which are geared toward bettering the general use of the gadget.</p>
<p>One other factor important to note is that it is advisable to have a ROM that able to improved efficiency and putting in apps or further instruments. If you&#8217;re searching for upgrading it then you definitely first want to make sure that personalized ROM can be found for that particular gadget. For instance, Motorola telephones have personalized ROM.</p>
<p><b>3. Consumer Interface or UI</b></p>
<p>Every Android powered gadget consists of a distinct UI. The reason being that with every producer the UI adjustments too. UI is totally different with totally different manufacturers and the options too differ from one producer to a different. If in any case you aren&#8217;t happy with the UI of your Smartphone then you&#8217;ll be able to obtain the web third get together software program like, Zeam, ADW, Go or Launcher Professional.</p>
<p><b>4. Processor</b> <br />Processor is essentially the most important part of your Smartphone. Think about this; if you&#8217;re extra of a gaming fanatic and are hooked on to 3D video games then it is advisable to have a Smartphone with excessive energy CPU processing. For those who use your Smartphone for carrying on average actions then you are able to do with a twin or a single core 1GHZ. A Smartphone powered with quad core processor is sensible to those that bask in heavy gaming and video streaming actions all through the day.</p>
<p>Another details:</p>
<p>• Select a Smartphone that has an excellent inner reminiscence like 4-8 GB when you wish to obtain apps <br />• If you&#8217;re eager about streaming movies and HD content material then a telephone with quicker processor ought to be chosen like a quad core processor <br />• For video calling facility it is advisable to discover a Smartphone with entrance dealing with digicam along with rear digicam <br />• The telephone ought to be backed up with a excessive capability mAh battery in order that it might last more</p>
<p>Holding all of the above given ideas in thoughts will make it easier to select the best-suited Android powered telephone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DJI Phantom 3 Evaluation: One of many Greatest Drones You will Ever Fly</title>
		<link>/dji-phantom-3-evaluation-one-of-many-greatest-drones-you-will-ever-fly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dji]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[drones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ever]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[greatest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[many]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[will]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[you]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[you’ll]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/dji-phantom-3-review-one-of-the-best-drones-youll-ever-fly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many totally different drones within the market, however among the best I&#8217;ve piloted is the DJI Phantom 3 Skilled. Able to 4K ultra-high [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many totally different drones within the market, however among the best I&#8217;ve piloted is the DJI Phantom 3 Skilled. Able to 4K ultra-high definition video, this drone additionally produces stay streams video to iOS and Android units in order that the pilot can see precisely what the drone is seeing. The actually distinctive function about this specific mannequin is the presence of Imaginative and prescient Positioning system, which permits for steady and predictable flight each time a GPS sign shouldn&#8217;t be accessible. After all exterior with GPS reception, this drone is able to computerized landings and takeoffs and built-in programming of no-fly zones. A DJI Phantom 3 overview wouldn&#8217;t be full with out point out of intuitive controls and stability throughout flight.</p>
<p><strong>The Professional</strong></p>
<p>The DJI Phantom 3 drone has so much going for it. Firstly, the cell gadget holder, for the telephone or pill to manage the unit, is included with the preliminary buy. As marketed, this mannequin handles fabulously, hovers completely, and delivers some spectacular 4K UHD footage. The 720p stay stream from the digital camera to the gadget was clear and really useful in controlling the 3-axis digital camera. All collectively this drone delivered some actually spectacular leads to the air.</p>
<p>As soon as the app is put in on the cell gadget, syncing with the drone and stepping into the air takes only some minutes. The battery permits for longer flights, and since video is recorded to a Micro SD card, getting the footage processed is a snap. Due to the upper decision, everybody goes to wish to maximize the scale of the cardboard to 64GB. Plus each DJI Phantom 3 overview ought to point out the 12-megapixel nonetheless footage the unit is able to taking as a result of they provide some fairly unimaginable pictures as properly.</p>
<p><strong>The Con</strong></p>
<p>I actually didn&#8217;t see any drawback with the DJI Phantom 3, besides the value. Like the opposite unmanned aerial autos available on the market, this gadget shouldn&#8217;t be a toy. For the reason that price ticket on this unit outpaces twelve-hundred bucks, anybody contemplating a purchase order might notice that it is a device. The device is ideal for top of the range video manufacturing and getting some really superb photographs. When you get previous the value tag although, there actually shouldn&#8217;t be lots of unhealthy issues to say about this drone. It delivers in each side of efficiency and use. DJI has delivered on this specific quadcopter.</p>
<p><strong>The Verdict</strong></p>
<p>The DJI Phantom 3 is an expert drone that ought to be within the arsenal of any critical hobbyist or video manufacturing firm. The user-friendly efficiency is miles above lots of the decrease priced fashions many drone pilots be taught on, and the huge technical wizardry concerned on this unit underscore that time. This mannequin is made to convey video from UAVs to the subsequent degree, and it succeeds in each means.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One other Phablet Assessment: The Apple iPhone 6S Plus Vs Samsung&#8217;s Galaxy Notice 5</title>
		<link>/one-other-phablet-assessment-the-apple-iphone-6s-plus-vs-samsungs-galaxy-notice-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[another]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[note]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[notice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[other]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phablet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[plus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung’s]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/another-phablet-review-the-apple-iphone-6s-plus-vs-samsungs-galaxy-note-5/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two super-smartphones have positioned themselves into the phablet market, and at the moment we examine an important options and specs that can assist you determine. [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two super-smartphones have positioned themselves into the phablet market, and at the moment we examine an important options and specs that can assist you determine.</p>
<p><b>Design</b><br />
<br />Each gadgets are very comparable in dimension, and each are enlarged variations of their predecessors. Similar to the 6 Plus, the iPhone 6S Plus hangs onto its modern aluminium design with curved edges and an upgraded, stronger cover-glass. This mannequin suits nicely within the hand, however is significalty heavier than the iPhone 6 because of its dimension (the 6S weighs at 192g).</p>
<p>The Notice 5 is taken into account much more comfy than the Notice 4, shaving off inches from its design and placing curved edges onto the again of the telephone as an alternative. This makes it simpler to carry, and the aluminium body offers power and a sleeker look. Lighter than the iPhone 6S Plus, this mannequin weights at 171g. Whereas the 6S Plus is definitely bigger in dimension, the Notice 5 has a greater screen-to-body ratio, with a bigger 5.7-inch display screen (in comparison with Apple&#8217;s 5.5-inches). This leads us on to the following characteristic comparability.</p>
<p><b>Display</b><br />
<br />It is good to have competitors between a vital characteristic, with each fashions utilizing totally different display screen applied sciences. Apple sticks to an IPS LCD and Samsung use its well-known AMOLED show. Because of this, the Notice 5 provides the next 2,560 x 1,440 pixel decision, making it a lot sharper with extra vibrant colors which are nice for viewing photos and video. Nevertheless, the iPhone 6S Plus comes with Apple&#8217;s new 3D Contact know-how. It is a pressure-sensitive characteristic of the display screen that reacts relying on person finger strain. For these not caring about 3D contact, the Samsung is the clear display screen winner this time.</p>
<p><b>Efficiency</b><br />
<br />Nevertheless many apps you could have open, whether or not its gaming, media recording, shopping and different intensive purposes, these two powerhouses can deal with it.<br />
<br />Inside Samsung&#8217;s Notice 5 is a 64-bit Exynos 7420 chipset, backed up by 4GB of RAM and a Mali T760 GPU. It is a clear top-quality efficiency set-up. On the iPhone 6S Plus, you have obtained Apple&#8217;s newest A9 64-bit chip and 2GB of RAM. It is nice to know Apple have lastly upgraded inner RAM this time as a way to compete. This implies smoother efficiency and fewer crashing.</p>
<p>It is essential to grasp that these numbers solely have which means when put underneath checks. A number of efficiency checks present that the iPhone 6S Plus usually beats the Notice 5 when finishing up frequent duties, comparable to opening mail attachments or power-heavy apps with others already operating within the background.</p>
<p><b>Cameras</b><br />
<br />The iPhone 6S Plus delivers a model new 12-megapixel digital camera sensor, whereas the Notice 5 boasts the identical 16-megapixel digital camera that the Galaxy S6 provides. With each gadgets, outcomes are sharp, with correct colors and improbable distinction. Low mild conditions is the place smartphone cameras don&#8217;t impress us, however this time each producers have come out on high.</p>
<p>The precise digital camera app provides extra customisation by means of Samsung&#8217;s gadget, comparable to HDR mode. Apple are inclined to hold issues fast and easy, so it lacks the extra skilled digital camera choices seen with the Notice 5.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Apple has additionally launched Reside Pictures, permitting the person to seize a few seconds&#8217; price of footage both facet of your snap. You&#8217;ll be able to then 3D Contact on the image and it will play the scene again to you.</p>
<p>Each gadgets in fact assist 4K video recording and modifying, so there is no such thing as a clear winner right here. Google search photograph comparisons for these gadgets and outcomes can communicate for themselves relying on what you are searching for.</p>
<p><b>Battery Life</b><br />
<br />It is essential to care about this characteristic. Choosing a robust gadget in principle is logical, but when its energy supply cannot assist the system nicely, then you definately&#8217;ll be subsequent to a mains plug extra usually than you suppose.</p>
<p>Specification-wise, the Notice 5 holds a bigger 3,000 mAh capability battery, whereas the 6S Plus carries a smaller-than-its-predecessor 2,750 mAh. Nevertheless, Apple&#8217;s new chip and improved effectivity makes the gadget final so long as the 6 Plus.</p>
<p>Each telephones can final the day and, if used properly, into the following. The Notice 5 does supply a extra helpful power-saving mode, permitting you to avoid wasting these additional hours simply if you want it. It additionally beats the iPhone with a wi-fi charging possibility and assist for quick charging. Each useful when you want a fast power-up.</p>
<p><b>Worth</b><br />
<br />Each gadgets are positioned on the very premium finish of the worth scale, so you will not have an interest when you&#8217;re searching for an &#8220;inexpensive&#8221; smartphone. The Notice 5 is barely cheaper in value when evaluating storage capacities, however your choice needs to be primarily based on testing each out and seeing which working system fits you finest as their specs are very comparable. At all times examine the most recent contracts from all networks and retailers that can assist you each lower your expenses and discover the proper allowance package deal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
