<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>3250 &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/3250/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia 3250 Music Cellphone Fast Assessment</title>
		<link>/nokia-3250-music-cellphone-fast-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3250]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-3250-music-phone-quick-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy because the telephone is delivery subsequent 12 months within the first quarter 2006. Estimated retail value is 350 Euros.</p>
<p>Key options:</p>
<p>&#8211; Helps MP3, M4A, WMA, AAC and eAAC+ music information</p>
<p>&#8211; 3.5mm connector for headphones</p>
<p>&#8211; 262K shade TFT show (decision of 176 x 220 pixels)</p>
<p>&#8211; Stereo FM radio</p>
<p>&#8211; Bluetooth</p>
<p>&#8211; USB 2.0</p>
<p>&#8211; Triband</p>
<p>&#8211; Talktime as much as 3 hours, music listening as much as 10 hours</p>
<p>Feedback and Conclusion</p>
<p>The Nokia 3250 is an good various should you plan to purchase a music telephone. In phrases oif technical specs and options it appears to be considerably higher than the Motorola Rokr iTunes telephone. The Motorola Rokr has USB 1.1 (can take as much as 40 minutes. to switch 100 songs), 512MB TransFlash reminiscence, and the iTunes software program is proscribed to retailer 100 songs. The Nokia 3250 makes use of the Nokia Audio Supervisor software program to switch music information from PC to telephone. This can be a clear drawback in comparison with Motorola that synch with iTunes.</p>
<p>P.S.</p>
<p>Nokia has historically been utilizing the MMC format for storage, however this telephone depends totally on microSD (TransFlash) playing cards. The microSD card relies on TransFlash(TM), which was developed by SanDisk in cooperation with Motorola and is the world&#8217;s smallest flash RAM reminiscence card format.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
