<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>video &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/video/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>High Addictive and Diverting Video games for Android Gadgets</title>
		<link>/high-addictive-and-diverting-video-games-for-android-gadgets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[addictive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[devices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[diverting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[high]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-addictive-and-diverting-games-for-android-devices/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cell video games are taking the world by storm. There&#8217;s a lengthy checklist of paid video games, however the variety of free video games is [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cell video games are taking the world by storm. There&#8217;s a lengthy checklist of paid video games, however the variety of free video games is as lengthy, if not longer. Many alternative video games can be found to cell customers. An Android sport takes many types. Some are quick sufficient to be accomplished in the course of the morning commute. Others video games provide gamers with hours on finish of thrilling sport play. The cell gaming business is profiting from accessible know-how to present the general public greater than sufficient motive to maintain falling in love with Android video games.</p>
<p>You probably have simply picked up a brand new gadget, then listed here are some extremely really useful video games in your Android cell phone. They&#8217;ve been designed to offer cell customers a method to kill time in essentially the most entertaining manner potential.</p>
<p>&#8220;Dots&#8221;</p>
<p>The challenges that gamers of &#8220;Dots&#8221; want to beat is to correctly line up dots of comparable colours as quick as they will. This very informal puzzle sport requires gamers to attract traces between dots of various colours as a way to hyperlink them collectively. It is usually fairly addictive due to the right mixture of easy necessities and the &#8220;good&#8221; quantity of problem. The participant has to work quick given the restricted period of time. It&#8217;s accessible in multiplayer mode, permitting teams of buddies to see whether or not their friends fare higher (or worse) than them. Bonuses can be found to gamers that take the time to hint closed loops. Energy-ups (all consumable) are given to gamers with sufficient quantities of gathered dots. The issue stage confronted by gamers will increase with extra sophisticated dot combos. &#8220;Dots&#8221; is kind of engaging to cell customers preferring video games which can be sharply designed and visually participating.</p>
<p>&#8220;Tremendous Monsters Ate My Condominium!&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Tremendous Monsters Ate My Condominium!&#8221; affords a bevy of neon colours and a high-speed sport play that concerned colourful house flooring that drop off at a breakneck tempo. The participant can acquire excessive scores by making the best matches and combos. Whereas gamers attempt to sustain with the primary problem, they need to not neglect the monsters standing by on the tower. They&#8217;re hungry for house flooring and must be fed solely flooring of an analogous shade. If the participant makes a mistake on this regard, the monsters go on a rampage and destroy every little thing on their path.</p>
<p>&#8220;Sky Pressure&#8221;</p>
<p>There are many video games with modern themes and revolutionary sport play. Nonetheless, many cell customers are additionally looking out for Android video games that simply permits them to blast away on the enemy. &#8220;Sky Pressure&#8221; provide its gamers an old-school blaster expertise with a 3D graphic surroundings.</p>
<p>&#8220;Useless Set off 2&#8221;</p>
<p>A primary-person cell capturing sport set in a zombie apocalypse is a positive hit amongst Android customers. &#8220;Useless Set off 2&#8221; is an efficient instance of such a sport. Apart from the excellent weapons methods and auto-fire mechanism, the sport incorporates a hideout and crafting system. Foreign money can be utilized to hurry up the time that assistants construct further firepower. The identical foreign money system facilitates upgrading of weapons on this prime quality shooter sport for cell platforms.</p>
<p>&#8220;Freeway Chase&#8221;</p>
<p>This sport is all about motion and capturing. As a police sniper, the gamer should shoot the automotive thief whereas using a helicopter. Hit your goal on the designated time as a way to go the stage. It might appear straightforward however it&#8217;s all about timing. Take up the problem and hone your capturing expertise.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finest Android Video games: Jewellust, Nesoid and Farm Frenzy</title>
		<link>/finest-android-video-games-jewellust-nesoid-and-farm-frenzy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[farm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[frenzy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jewellust,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nesoid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/best-android-games-jewellust-nesoid-and-farm-frenzy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jewellust The Android Jewellust sport navigates you to the Historic Egypt the place you may swap and break open colourful gems, discover mosaic tiles and [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Jewellust</strong></p>
<p>The Android Jewellust sport navigates you to the Historic Egypt the place you may swap and break open colourful gems, discover mosaic tiles and transfer round pyramids. The consumer has to navigate 30 ranges in 7 pyramids and an underground Temple to achieve Pharaoh&#8217;s energy. You can also make use of Santa to ship items, go 7 villages and resolve jigsaw puzzles. The sport takes you to quite a few ranges, power-ups and scores. You&#8217;ll be able to play in survival mode for prime scores, after getting expert on this sport, in any other case the consumer has to modify into marketing campaign mode, which is supposed for the novice within the sport. The sport presents wealthy graphics to take pleasure in, charming sounds and completely different shapes to mess around. The sport could be very humorous, addictive and a superb time-killing train.</p>
<p><strong>Nesoid (NES Emulator)</strong></p>
<p>Nesoid is the well-known NES/FC emulator for Android apps and it presents you virtually limitless gaming potentialities. It gives the power to play NES video games in your favourite Android telephones. However earlier than you begin enjoying video games, it&#8217;s important to obtain and play NES ROMS, after which set up it in your system. You&#8217;ll be able to retailer the video games in your Android telephone SD reminiscence card. It comprises some nice previous NES titles. Nesoid presents numerous choices to play. You&#8217;ll be able to alter the show to full display screen or native decision. It&#8217;s also possible to play NES Zapper video games utilizing the contact display screen. Nesoid thoughtfully options an on-screen digital d-pad together with begin and choose buttons. If you&#8217;re a GI/HTC proprietor and do not would possibly shopping for apps, Nesoid is a worthy choice. Nesoid is tailor-made for retro gaming followers.</p>
<p><strong>Farm Frenzy</strong></p>
<p>Farm Frenzy is a cellular model of the well-known award-winning PC sport and is now out there for Android. It&#8217;s a simulated sport and the target of the sport is that it&#8217;s important to take care of your individual farm and undertake low key farming technique. With this sport, you may handle your farm, rear the animals and harvest their produce like eggs or wool and make merchandise like cupcakes, cheese and butter, after which lastly supply it on the market. You need to feed the animals properly and shield them from predators. This consists of, bears, which falls from the sky on the cows and it&#8217;s important to fight them, in any other case it makes your progress gradual. By monetizing this sport, you should use the cash you earned to enhance your farm, after which transfer from one puzzle to a different with rising issue. The graphics for this sport is sweet and neat. The tutorials offered on this sport presents an added benefit and serves as a priceless information as the sport unfolds. General, it is a nice, distinctive and addicting sport for the Android followers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Finest Android Video games Of 2015</title>
		<link>/the-finest-android-video-games-of-2015/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-best-android-games-of-2015/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Typically, you get solely what you pay for within the sense that you simply get some good video games for cash. You could find a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Typically, you get solely what you pay for within the sense that you simply get some good video games for cash. You could find a number of incredible video games on Android, however you need to spend a bit cash and you&#8217;ll take pleasure in a number of video games in your cell phone. You may merely obtain a few of the greatest Android video games and begin enjoying them. Listed below are a few of the greatest Android video games of 2015.</p>
<p>Threes!</p>
<p>A merely ingenious recreation that&#8217;s simple to play, however that&#8217;s tough to grasp, Threes has a 4 by 4 grid and a variety of sliding tiles for the instruments that you&#8217;d be utilizing to play the sport. Every of those numbered tiles might be mixed solely with one other kind of tile. At this level, it turns into a single tile and their values add as much as its constituents. The first concept behind the sport is to maintain enjoying it. The sound results, music, and so forth. are merely the icing on the cake.</p>
<p>Monument Valley</p>
<p>There are lots of debates on whether or not Android video games might be creative and Monument Valley checks the &#8220;artwork&#8221; field. It&#8217;s a delicate and a lovely arcade journey recreation that options the makes an attempt of a lovely princess to discover monuments. Monument Valley has been crafted rigorously, thoughtfully, and the expertise all through is reflective. The structure strikes as you drag and spin the elements.</p>
<p>Drop7</p>
<p>Every so often, a puzzle recreation seems that might not merely allow you to go of it. You&#8217;ll work with puzzles on this recreation, though you would want to drop discs and will the variety of any disc not match with the disc depend in its column or row, it might explode. If you&#8217;d like the face quantity revealed, then it&#8217;s best to make the grey blocks have two adjoining explosions. It is without doubt one of the greatest Android puzzles round.</p>
<p>Indignant birds &#8211; Star Wars II</p>
<p>Right here is one thing for ardent players of Indignant Birds. The sequel to Indignant Birds &#8211; Star Wars I improves on the design concepts of the sport. The sequel to the sport comes with character packs and degree branching that permit you to swap and check out totally different methods. This recreation is an ideal match for the followers of Darth Maul. If you happen to thought that the titular birds had been method too indignant, then you will have the chance to get revenge on them proper now with this Android recreation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Android Video games &#8211; Tricks to Get the Better of It</title>
		<link>/android-video-games-tricks-to-get-the-better-of-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[better]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[get]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-games-tips-to-get-the-best-of-it/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you want to kill your free time when the one firm you have got is your Android cellphone? Do you know that Android video [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to kill your free time when the one firm you have got is your Android cellphone? Do you know that Android video games are essentially the most attention-grabbing and enjoyable stuffed stuff to cram your cellphone with? Undergo this text to know extra about these video games and their enjoyable elements.</p>
<p>Android video games are diversified into many classes; informational, instructional, capturing video games, puzzles, sports activities, racing, augmented actuality video games, location-based video games and extra. All these varieties can be found for each excessive finish and low-end Android telephones.</p>
<p>There are low specification video games for these low-end fashions so as to take pleasure in them in your finances telephones as nicely. This contains the lesser graphics content material video games that doesn&#8217;t take a lot of your house. It&#8217;s appropriate for Android telephones with low GPUs and smaller display dimension as nicely.</p>
<p>Each freemium and premium video games can be found within the shops. Premium are paid-for video games and freemium is the free video games which regularly comprise in-app buy at sure ranges. So it&#8217;s advisable to observe if somebody aside from you (like your child) is utilizing your cellphone; do not click on on these buy choices with out information.</p>
<p>To take pleasure in the perfect excessive graphics and well-designed gameplay, it&#8217;s higher to get a high-end mannequin with a much bigger display and good GPU. Even you may take pleasure in these high-quality gaming results by growing the efficiency of your low spec, finances Android telephones.</p>
<p>First and the best methodology to extend your low-end smartphone efficiency is by killing the functions which can be operating within the background earlier than you begin the sport. You should utilize a number of activity killer functions for this, as nicely. A lot of the Android telephones comprise many functions which can be of no use to a median person. These functions may be disabled which in flip will increase the efficiency of your cellphone.</p>
<p>All you might want to do is, go to settings, choose &#8216;apps&#8217;, then choose the functions to be disabled and click on the &#8216;disable&#8217; button. All these functions may be enabled sooner or later if you happen to want them. Normally, the uninstalled functions or your web browser usually leaves behind junk recordsdata. These cache information usually reduces your cellphone efficiency. To clear these information, go to &#8216;settings&#8217; and click on &#8216;storage possibility&#8217;, then choose the cached information button and press okay.</p>
<p>All the time go for a category 10 SD card to extend your cellphone&#8217;s gaming efficiency. Utilizing these SD playing cards will enhance the learn and write velocity and therefore reduces the loading time and different lags that any excessive graphics recreation would demand. These rooted Android telephones have extra amenities to extend their efficiency. The background activity killer functions work to their fullest provided that they&#8217;re in a rooted Android model. Seeder software program may be put in in a rooted Android cellphone, which reduces the lag throughout switching between functions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prime VR Video games for Your Android Cellphone</title>
		<link>/prime-vr-video-games-for-your-android-cellphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[your]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-vr-games-for-your-android-phone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[VR or digital actuality is the brand new innovation by the tech world that has turn into an integral a part of virtually all kinds [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>VR or digital actuality is the brand new innovation by the tech world that has turn into an integral a part of virtually all kinds of video games on-line. Digital actuality is a 3 dimensional atmosphere that will render dwell and interactive expertise to the gamer. There video games are being designed to boost the standard of the video games and to offer an superior gaming expertise to the gamer. The extra revolutionary and user-friendly variations of those VR video games are developing in lately which are suitable sufficient even on sensible telephones.</p>
<p>Newest VR video games would help you play the sport on a number of gadgets with a single gamer identify. You possibly can play whereas commuting additionally through the use of your android telephones. The newest variations of VR video games are designed in such a method that they&#8217;d render the identical expertise as a computer, laptop computer or a play station. Now as we all know what&#8217;s a VR sport is all about let us take a look at few newest VR video games designed for android telephones,</p>
<p>• Mekorama VR &#8211; A puzzle sport the place you need to information a small robotic by means of varied ranges. At the start it is fairly easy as a result of there will likely be few stones to be moved however the problem will increase from one degree to the following. On this sport you employ the controller to maneuver the stones and present the robotic the best way to maneuver up.</p>
<p>• Hunters Gate: A sport for motion lovers &#8211; You&#8217;ll turn into a savior of the world when the world has been attacked by demons and you need to maintain them again. It is a fun-filled and graphically spectacular sport. It is a well-known rolling sport whose components make you stronger over time and can train you new abilities. For taking part in this sport it&#8217;s essential to use daydream controllers, and these controllers assist you to in retaining observe of what is occurring from above, which reduces your an excessive amount of interplay with the digital motion.</p>
<p>• Want for Pace: A VR sport for admirers of pace, the sport enhances the feeling of pace by Digital Actuality and might be the perfect racing sport for Daydream-capable sensible telephones. An thrilling trip is assured due to its impeccable graphics and breakneck-pace. Moreover that the selection of customization and automobile tuning made this sport extra enchanting and thrilling.</p>
<p>• Gun jack 2: Finish of Shift &#8211; A sport the place you&#8217;ll be sitting on cannon on our photo voltaic system and fend off the attackers who&#8217;re determined to steal the minerals from our planet. You can be having immense arsenal weapons and might management the whole lot together with your gaze.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
