<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ios &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ios/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Methods to Unfreeze Your Android and iOS Telephones</title>
		<link>/methods-to-unfreeze-your-android-and-ios-telephones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[methods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unfreeze]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[your]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/how-to-unfreeze-your-android-and-ios-phones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Your Smartphone just isn&#8217;t precisely your pc even after you utilize it for varied functions. Nonetheless nonetheless there are some widespread troubles that you simply [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your Smartphone just isn&#8217;t precisely your pc even after you utilize it for varied functions. Nonetheless nonetheless there are some widespread troubles that you simply may undergo like frozen telephone. Even if you&#8217;re utilizing an iOS gadget or an Android primarily based telephone the issue is widespread. This can be very annoying if you undergo such hassle and infrequently you have no idea what to do. Listed here are just a few ideas for unfreezing your iPhone and your Android telephone.</p>
<p><b>Methods to unfreeze your iPhone</b></p>
<p>• Usually freezes occur attributable to app hassle that leaves your telephone frozen. Right now you must force-close. If you&#8217;re utilizing iOS 7 then double faucet on Residence button to disclose app switcher inside the multitask bar, then scroll left to find the app that&#8217;s frozen, swipe as much as fling it off the display. For these utilizing iOS 6 Residence button-&gt; App Switcher-&gt;maintain down on the App icon and when it wriggles faucet the &#8211; button to close it down.</p>
<p>• In case your iPhone goes bonkers and wouldn&#8217;t allow you to entry app switcher then the most suitable choice that you&#8217;ve is to restart your telephone. Press and maintain the Sleep Button positioned on the high of your telephone until you see Slide to Energy Off slider seem. Slide to proper to energy down the telephone. To energy again your telephone you then must press down the Sleep Button once more until the Apple emblem seems.</p>
<p>• If you&#8217;re dealing with a state of affairs the place your iPhone is non-responsive to your faucets then you must force-restart it. Press and maintain down the Sleep button + Residence Button until you possibly can see the Apple emblem on the display. After a couple of minutes your iPhone can be up and operating as earlier than.</p>
<p>• One other method of getting previous your freezing iPhone is to go for manufacturing facility reset or the default settings. Nonetheless, take warning as you may lose all of your knowledge in your telephone so it&#8217;s advisable to take an information backup previous to making an attempt manufacturing facility reset. Settings-&gt;Common-&gt;Reset-&gt;Reset All Settings. Now as quickly as you&#8217;re by way of with all this your telephone will return to the manufacturing facility settings and every thing together with your apps and extra software program can be wiped off.</p>
<p>• You may also go for iTunes restore by plugging your telephone by way of USB into your system. A listing of gadgets will seem from which you must choose your telephone. Abstract tab-&gt;Restore iPhone possibility, a backup of all of the settings will start. As quickly because it finishes obtain and set up contemporary iOS after which apply the default setting. To revive your knowledge go to Backups -&gt; Restore Backup.</p>
<p><b>Methods to unfreeze your Android telephone?</b></p>
<p><b>Pressure-close an app:</b></p>
<p>• Initially you must drive shut the app that&#8217;s inflicting hassle, Swipe to disclose the tab-&gt;Choose the app you need to kill by tapping the cease button. If you&#8217;re not in a position to view the app within the given listing then go to the higher proper nook and search for Present Cached Processes.</p>
<p>• You possibly can even try a drive shutdown maintain and press down energy button + quantity up button until the display turns off. Energy on by urgent the ability button. If you&#8217;re having hassle utilizing the quantity up button then use the quantity down button.</p>
<p>• In case your Android has a detachable battery then you possibly can take away the again cowl of your telephone and pull out the battery. After just a few seconds substitute the battery and shut the battery cowl, now flip again your telephone. Nonetheless, bear in mind to make use of this methodology when anything just isn&#8217;t working in unfreezing your Android Cellphone.</p>
<p>• One other method of unfreezing your telephone is to check out the strategy of manufacturing facility reset. Restoring your telephone again to the manufacturing facility default may provide help to eliminate the telephone freeze hassle. Nonetheless, earlier than you start the method of manufacturing facility reset you must take a backup of your telephone by connecting it to your system by way of USB.</p>
<p>• For manufacturing facility reset go to Settings-&gt;Backup-&gt;Reset and find Manufacturing facility knowledge reset, faucet it. A affirmation is required for continuing additional. After you might have confirmed the method of manufacturing facility reset will start.</p>
<p>Enterprise the above-mentioned steps will make sure that you rid your telephone of the telephone freeze hassle. Nonetheless, if it once more occurs then you must get in contact with a tech professional.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
