<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>love &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/love/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Apple iPhone 4 Overview &#8211; Love Trend, Love iPhone</title>
		<link>/apple-iphone-4-overview-love-trend-love-iphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-iphone-4-review-love-fashion-love-iphone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Apple has captured folks&#8217;s consideration with its fashionable merchandise for a very long time. It is a good distance for the reason that launch of [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Apple has captured folks&#8217;s consideration with its fashionable merchandise for a very long time. It is a good distance for the reason that launch of first iPhone. We all know that Apple iPhone 4 is a wonderful cell phone which continues the recent consideration of iPhone 3, its predecessor. Nonetheless, Apple continues to be must face the fierce competitors that there are numerous decisions for the customs like HTC, Samsung, and Motorola for the reason that market has advanced vastly previously 12 months. Nonetheless, we can not deny that iPhone 4 is among the hottest cell phones all over the world.</p>
<p>It is well-known that Apple is known for its fashionable design, which is absolutely mirrored within the trend IPhone4. No doubly, iPhone 4 is a stupendous and superb cell phone with fancy look and nice features. The decision of it&#8217;s 960 x 640 pixels. As for the looks, this cell phone has a contact display screen with an ordinary residence button. In addition to, it has a VGA digital camera within the entrance. As for the configuration, this cell phone has 512 MB RAM (random entry reminiscence), which is a superb enchancment to the iPhone 3, which solely has 256 MB RAM. Which means this cellphone could have higher expertise. As well as, this cellphone has a 5 mega pixel digital camera, which can show you how to file all of the memorable moments. With the entrance digital camera, you may make video calls along with your beloved and different pals. It&#8217;s a necessity to say that Wi-Fi is supported by this cellphone.</p>
<p>This iPhone has two units and two colours from which you&#8217;ll select. It&#8217;s obtainable in 16 GB and 32 GB, black and white. What&#8217;s extra, there are numerous iPhone covers and circumstances available in the market, by which you&#8217;ll enhance and personalize your iPhone. Since iPhone is so common and fantastic, it is going to be your first selection to point out your trend fashion. Be part of within the trend group along with your trend iPhone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
