<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>icing &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/icing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia N97 &#8211; The Good Icing on the Cake</title>
		<link>/nokia-n97-the-good-icing-on-the-cake/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[icing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[n97]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[perfect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-n97-the-perfect-icing-on-the-cake/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When cell phones are involved individuals do not dare to compromise at any price. This mentality of the individuals all the time forces the cell [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When cell phones are involved individuals do not dare to compromise at any price. This mentality of the individuals all the time forces the cell phone producers to supply one thing progressive frequently. On this regard, the Nokia performs with the each altering attitudes of the individuals.</p>
<p>In reality, this model could be very effectively liable for setting new developments within the society. Its newest providing to the cell group was the N sequence fashions. Virtually each mannequin of this style was a ripple creator proper from the day of launch. Earlier this firm provided the Nokia N96 to the individuals which gained a lot of appreciation by the cell phone customers all all over the world. As a matter of reality, the N sequence fashions turned the pattern setters relaxed. Nevertheless, as mentioned earlier individuals do not stay occupied with something for very long time. They&#8217;re ruled y the insatiable urge for food and to match their excessive degree tastes can also be not a children play. However, sure Nokia is aware of how one can play with this situation and in addition to be the rating winner on the identical time. This time it designed a category aside gadget which steadily gained momentum among the many customers. This gadget was launched within the title of Nokia N97. Assessment of this gadget turned the highest story of many of the on-line cell associated websites as a consequence of varied causes.</p>
<p>Truly, the specs with which this handset got here loaded with are simply unbelievable. By studying the Nokia N97 evaluate the general public assume it to be a hearsay with the assistance of which Nokia is attempting to create unmatched requirements out there. However, fairly apparently, this firm wiped off all these speculations and allegations to take care of the reliability and the reliable issue. Thus it launched the Nokia N97 cell phone full of a lot of options to face tall in opposition to all odds. This cell phone elegantly boasts of specs reminiscent of 5 mega pixels digicam, WAP browser, quite a few connectivity choices, built-in GPS navigation options and attractive media participant and many others.</p>
<p>Thus, this handset has balanced each the leisure and the communication options in a superb method. Most significantly, the impeccable battery of this gadget has the potential to give you lengthy hours of talktime i.e., 4 hours 40 minutes and 430 hours of stand by time.</p>
<p>Nokia has brilliantly targeted on the designing a part of this gadget additionally. The subtle design of this gadget complimented by the complete QWERTY keyboard brilliantly balances smartness and class relaxed.</p>
<p>Moreover, the accelerometer sensor for automated rotation would allow you to entry the functionalities of this handset from any course. Truly, this feature is intuitive in nature which might amazingly sense the course of the handset. Simply after sensing the course of the cell phone, this superior choice finally modifications the show routinely. The 32 GB inside reminiscence of this Nokia N97 cell phone would increase your brows fairly clearly. However, sure its a reality, this handset comes powered with such large storage capability. This mammoth storage capability would by no means help you hassle in regards to the storage constraints.</p>
<p>The 5 mega pixels digicam is one other necessary characteristic of this cell phone, which has additional been complimented by options like Carl Zeiss optics and auto-focus and many others. With this digicam cellphone you possibly can even get pleasure from video recording capabilities with none stress and that too at a velocity of 30 frames per second. Moreover, in case you are taken with dwell interplay then the extra secondary video name digicam would effectively serve your objective. This high-tech choice would comfortably allow you to observe the expressions of the involved particular person with whom you might be interacting. Final however not the least, the GPS navigation characteristic of this handset would allow you to be the very best information of your self as with the help of this characteristic, you possibly can comfortably monitor your most popular location relaxed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
