<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>options &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/options/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>All of the Finest Options of the Android Nougat Replace</title>
		<link>/all-of-the-finest-options-of-the-android-nougat-replace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[all]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nougat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[replace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[update]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/all-the-best-features-of-the-android-nougat-update/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Android Nougat is the newest replace of Google&#8217;s working system; Android.. Right here on this article we will probably be telling you when you may [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Android Nougat is the newest replace of Google&#8217;s working system; Android.. Right here on this article we will probably be telling you when you may replace Android in your telephone, pill and different gadgets, how one can profit the replace&#8217;s options. What are the professionals and cons of updating your outdated Android Lollipol or Marshmallow to Android Nougat.</p>
<p>We present you the principle new options of Android 7.0 Nougat, why it is so vital, and what mobiles will obtain this model of Google&#8217;s working system.</p>
<p>Every time a brand new model of Android seems, on this case the 7.0, the kick-off is given for all manufacturers to announce which telephones will probably be upgraded to Android Nougat. And as usually occurs on earlier events, comes the frustration whenever you see that your smartphone is not going to be up to date, otherwise you see that the replace comes too late.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, there might all the time be a doubt about the advantages of Android 7.0 over the earlier system, and if it actually price it. The reality is that with every new working system not solely come useful and aesthetic enhancements, but additionally at a safety degree, so upgrading to Android 7.0 is kind of handy.</p>
<p>What are the brand new options of Android Nougat? Many and really demanded by customers. The primary and most placing is the inclusion of the primary multiventana in Android inventory, one thing needed given the rise in display screen dimension we&#8217;ve seen lately, with the 5.5 inches more and more widespread in all Segments.</p>
<p>The arrival of digital actuality doesn&#8217;t go unnoticed by the brand new Android system, and it will embody a sequence of options that may optimize the efficiency of the smartphone along side Daydream VR, the newest digital actuality glasses from Google. Additionally included is compatibility with Vulkan, an API that may enable higher optimization of video games and purposes that require excessive graphics efficiency.</p>
<p>There are additionally enhancements within the degree of optimization and administration of accessible assets, with a twist to the Doze battery saving system, in order that now the system will save vitality from the second we flip off the display screen.</p>
<p><u><strong>Safety in Android Nougat gadgets:</strong></u></p>
<p>In fact, safety in Android 7.0 Nougat can also be enhanced by a redesign of your encryption system to extra successfully shield our information, in order that, for an instance, ransonware won&#8217;t be able to change our password In case we&#8217;ve established one to dam our telephone.</p>
<p>We even have the potential for automated updates working within the background, see the supply of the appliance set up, the direct boot, which permits a a lot quicker begin of the smartphone, or instantaneous apps, purposes that may be executed with out Should be put in in our terminal.</p>
<p>Which telephones will obtain Android 7.0</p>
<p>All these options appear sufficient causes for manufacturers to make an effort to improve a smartphone to Android 7.0. Most producers like Samsung, LG or Huawei have targeted on masking their most iconic fashions, forsaking the entry-level fashions or gadgets previous to 2016. This isn&#8217;t the case for BQ.</p>
<p>Bq_aquaris_x5_plus_1</p>
<p>BQ has introduced the listing of telephones that may obtain Android Nougat, the place we&#8217;ve been capable of see nice surprises. As we mentioned, if we speak in regards to the entry vary, there&#8217;s just about no replace adverts from any producer, so the Aquaris A4.5 and the three fashions of the brand new vary Aquaris U would be the first cell of lower than 150 € to obtain Android 7.0.</p>
<p>If we go a step above, we discover that the Aquaris X5 and the Aquaris X5 Plus will even function Android Nougat, however not solely the newest developments in BQ will function this new system, as each the Aquaris M5 and the Aquaris M5.5 (2015 fashions) obtain this replace.</p>
<p>In fact, their rivals are additionally trying to supply the newest flagships such because the Samsung Galaxy S7, Huawei P9 or the LG G5 will even function the improve to Android 7.0. The variations we see in essentially the most inexpensive ranges.</p>
<p>Whereas within the mid-range there are manufacturers that make extra effort like Motorola with its Moto G4, Huawei P9 Lite, or Samsung Galaxy A, we see as different fashions as vital because the Samsung Galaxy J3, LG K10, or the Huawei P8 Lite Is not going to obtain the brand new Android 7.0.</p>
<p>With this we see how there are manufacturers that actually care about giving an extended life to every mannequin belonging to its product vary, whereas others overlook to cowl some segments. What is obvious is that the replace to Android Nougat needs to be a figuring out issue when selecting a smartphone right now.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Greatest Virus Safety for Android Overview &#8211; What Options to Search for in Smartphone Safety</title>
		<link>/greatest-virus-safety-for-android-overview-what-options-to-search-for-in-smartphone-safety/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[greatest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[look]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[what]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/best-virus-protection-for-android-overview-what-features-to-look-for-in-smartphone-protection/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tablets and telephones are extra than simply gadgets that individuals carry round. They comprise a variety of private details about their customers. They&#8217;ll get contaminated [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tablets and telephones are extra than simply gadgets that individuals carry round. They comprise a variety of private details about their customers. They&#8217;ll get contaminated with viruses identical to a pc can. Many individuals ask the query &#8220;What&#8217;s the greatest virus safety for android?&#8221; There are totally different apps and instruments to select from. It is attainable to guard a tool from all forms of malicious information, together with adware, spy ware, malware, phishing emails, and so forth.</p>
<p>First off, you may wish to verify and see in case your present pc antivirus software program additionally gives licenses for different gadgets similar to your Android telephones. If you wish to swap software program or really feel that the safety will likely be insufficient, then take the steps essential to decide on new safety software program.</p>
<p>Resolve whether or not or not a free app will likely be sufficient in your wants. Free variations of antivirus software program do not supply all-inclusive safety. A full, premium suite however will supply instruments like firewalls, VPN, safety towards ransomware, digital camera safety, parental controls, and so forth. Make an inventory of the options you want and begin seeking to see which safety suite gives these options. This would be the greatest virus safety for Android.</p>
<p>One more reason you may wish to go for greater than a free program is as a result of the free software program usually comes with &#8220;extras&#8221; that you just actually don&#8217;t desire, like advertisements and plug-ins. The poorly designed virus safety apps are generally simply as annoying as viruses and adware itself.</p>
<p><u><strong>What&#8217;s Mandatory within the Greatest Virus Safety for Android</strong></u></p>
<p>It is essential that you&#8217;ve malware detection instruments in your Android machine. This is without doubt one of the largest safety issues many smartphone customers face. One other important characteristic to search for is a monitoring / location finder. Having antitheft controls on an Android telephone could be very, essential. You may wish to have the perfect monitoring instruments to find and monitor a misplaced or stolen telephone. Even in case you are all the time cautious with it, there may be all the time the likelihood that any person else may come up with it. Within the occasion that it&#8217;s unrecoverable, you must be capable to remotely lock and wipe the non-public contents off of it. Some Professional variations of antivirus packages embrace a &#8220;seize&#8221; characteristic that truly takes pictures of the thief.</p>
<p>Getting spam messages and undesirable calls is extraordinarily annoying. It is laborious to have a peaceable day whenever you preserve getting spam telephone calls. It is much more annoying whenever you&#8217;re ready for an necessary telephone name from an affiliate or cherished one, and you retain getting spam. You will not have to fret about getting these obnoxious calls and textual content messages with the fitting safety features.</p>
<p>So, what&#8217;s the greatest virus safety for Android? Many individuals advocate Avast Cell Safety. It is extremely rated on Google Play and has over 100 million installs. You possibly can attempt Avast at no cost.</p>
<p>Get monetary savings on the <a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" href="https://translate.google.com/website?sl=ar&amp;tl=en&amp;ajax=1&amp;u=https://www.bestpcsecurity.com/avast/">best virus protection for Android</a> by utilizing Avast coupon codes. The corporate recurrently provides out reductions and promo gives to smartphone customers, residence pc customers, companies, and so on.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HP ProBook 650 G3 Evaluation &#8211; A Should-Have Enterprise Pocket book With Safety and Collaboration Options</title>
		<link>/hp-probook-650-g3-evaluation-a-should-have-enterprise-pocket-book-with-safety-and-collaboration-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[650]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[book]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[collaboration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[must-have]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[notebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pocket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[probook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[should-have]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[with]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-probook-650-g3-review-a-must-have-business-notebook-with-security-and-collaboration-features/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is a sensible choice of a enterprise pocket book with its clean system efficiency, simple deployment, and security measures. You possibly can rely on [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is a sensible choice of a enterprise pocket book with its clean system efficiency, simple deployment, and security measures. You possibly can rely on getting essentially the most out of your funding with the HP ProBook 650 G3, as its configurations help all of as we speak&#8217;s technological necessities. It may be described as a 15.6-inch mid-range enterprise laptop computer.</p>
<p>The 15.6-inch show has anti-glare and LED-backlit know-how. The bottom / least expensive configuration choice has a show decision of 1366 x 768, however you&#8217;ll be able to go for a greater one for those who select a distinct configuration. It additionally comes with a 720p HD digital camera for video-chatting. The stereo audio system and microphone are built-in.</p>
<p>Even at peak efficiency, the pocket book doesn&#8217;t overheat. All the parts keep comparatively low, it doesn&#8217;t matter what sorts of duties you&#8217;ve operating. The premium keyboard is designed to be spill-resistant and straightforward to look after. The touchpad has an on / off button and helps two-way scrolling, two-finger zooming, tapping, and a wide range of different gestures.</p>
<p>The general design of the HP ProBook 650 G3 is good, and it has a beginning weight of 5.1-lbs, making it an average-sized enterprise pocket book. With particular security measures comparable to HP BIOSphere, you&#8217;ve every thing it&#8217;s worthwhile to forestall downtime and information breaches. Theft prevention is supplied with TPM 2.0 know-how, HP Fingerprint Sensor, Password Supervisor, and the lock slot, though the lock itself is bought individually.</p>
<p><u><strong>HP ProBook 650 G3 Specs</strong></u></p>
<p>The bottom mannequin comes with the next:</p>
<p>&bull; Twin-core Intel Core i5 processor (seventh era) 2.5 Ghz / as much as 3.1 Ghz with turbo enhance</p>
<p>&bull; 2 SODIMM reminiscence slots / one occupied with 4GB DDR4 2133 SDRAM</p>
<p>&bull; 128 GB SSD drive M.2 SATA TLC</p>
<p>&bull; Intel HD built-in graphics (620)</p>
<p>&bull; DVD-writer optical drive</p>
<p>&bull; Home windows 10 Professional OS 64</p>
<p>There are alternatives to go along with a extra highly effective processor and develop the reminiscence for those who require extra.</p>
<p>It comes with every thing you want for collaboration, regardless of the place you&#8217;re taking the laptop computer to: HP Audio Increase, Noise Cancellation Software program, Skype, 720p webcam, and so on. The three-cell, 48-WH Li-Ion prismatic battery has a protracted life and might run for a number of hours. The ability provide is supplied through a 65-W Good AC adapter.</p>
<p>You get the latest dual-band wi-fi AC (2×2) know-how mixed with Bluetooth 4.2 for networking. The laptop computer gives help for SD, SDXC, and SDHC card studying. Connectivity is straightforward because of the two USB 3.0 (one for charging) ports, 1 Sort-C USB port, DIsplayPort, VGA port, and extra.</p>
<p>Total, the HP ProBook 650 G3 is a superb selection for any skilled or enterprise person who needs an reasonably priced pocket book.</p>
<p>HP gives notebooks and tablets to swimsuit the necessity of any enterprise person. The ProBook collection positively options a number of the greatest notebooks &#8211; and they&#8217;re all reasonably priced because of HP low cost gives. Get your self a <a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" href="https://www.dealectronic.com/hp/">HP ProBook 650 G3</a> coupon and get began along with your order.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fero Iris Fast Overview, Options and Specs</title>
		<link>/fero-iris-fast-overview-options-and-specs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iris]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[specs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/fero-iris-quick-review-features-and-specs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Fero Iris is a low-end smartphone with an Iris scanner and 4G LTE built-in. It encompasses a smooth design, the kind that may match [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Fero Iris is a low-end smartphone with an Iris scanner and 4G LTE built-in. It encompasses a smooth design, the kind that may match completely in your pocket and may additionally be nice for dealing with</p>
<p>Within the show division, the telephone spots a 5.0inch IPS LCD which is sweet for viewing textual content and media consumption. The viewing angles must be simply fantastic. We won&#8217;t actually say a lot about working the telephone outside.</p>
<p>Within the efficiency side, it&#8217;s fitted with a MTK6737 Quad Core processor, clocked at 1.3 GHz. That is positively a processor for a low-end smartphone however for essentially the most half, it must be quick sufficient. 1GB of ram and 8GB on-board storage is what this system is delivery with, which isn&#8217;t that a lot of a shock contemplating the value however you possibly can additional increase the storage utilizing a 32GB microSD in case you like that additional house in your telephone. Additionally it is a twin sim smartphone.</p>
<p>It has an 8MP rear digital camera and a 2MP front-facing digital camera that doubles because the Iris scanner. For selfie fanatic, you would possibly need to look elsewhere for that dream entrance dealing with digital camera however in case you&#8217;re eager about excessive degree safety at an inexpensive worth, then that is for you. Though, we&#8217;ve not actually examined the Iris scanner to understand how correct it&#8217;s in recognising your Iris.</p>
<p>2,500mAh is what you get right here which can not me very interesting to heavy customers nevertheless it nonetheless will get the job accomplished. you won&#8217;t need to stray far-off out of your charger although.</p>
<p>Take a look at the complete specs of the Fero Iris under;</p>
<p>Community Connectivity:<br />
<br />WLAN: Wi-Fi 802.11 b/g/n, dual-band, Wi-Fi Direct, hotspot<br />
<br />Community: 2G 850/900/1800/1900 MHz, 3G 2100 MHz, LTE BAND 3/ BAND 7/ BAND 20/ BAND 40<br />
<br />Bluetooth: v4.0</p>
<p>Platform:<br />
<br />OS: Android OS, v6.0 (Marshmallow)<br />
<br />Chipset: MTK6737<br />
<br />CPU: 1.3 GHz, Quad Core</p>
<p>Physique:<br />
<br />Dimension: 144*72*9 mm<br />
<br />Weight: 137 gms<br />
<br />SIM: Twin SIM (Micro-SIM, twin stand-by)<br />
<br />Construct: Titanium based mostly metallic again panel</p>
<p>Show:<br />
<br />Kind: IPS capacitive touchscreen, 16M colours<br />
<br />Dimension: 5 inch<br />
<br />Display Decision: 1280×720 HD</p>
<p>Digicam:<br />
<br />Major: 8 MP, LED flash<br />
<br />Secondary: 2 MP with IRIS Scanner<br />
<br />Multi contact: Sure</p>
<p>Reminiscence:<br />
<br />Card Slot: microSD, as much as 32 GB (devoted slot)<br />
<br />Inner: 8 GB, 1 GB RAM</p>
<p>Sound:<br />
<br />Alert sorts: MIDI/MP3/AAC/WAV<br />
<br />Loudspeaker: Sure<br />
<br />3.5mm jack: Sure</p>
<p>Battery<br />
<br />Capability: 2,500 mAh, Detachable<br />
<br />Kind: Li-Ion</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Information to Nokia 1600 Cellular Cellphone Opinions and Options</title>
		<link>/information-to-nokia-1600-cellular-cellphone-opinions-and-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1600]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[information]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opinions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/guide-to-nokia-1600-mobile-phone-reviews-and-features/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nokia cell phones have come a great distance with their ever altering and creating options and enticing designs. Amongst different contract cell phones, Nokia cell [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Nokia cell phones</b> have come a great distance with their ever altering and creating options and enticing designs. Amongst different contract cell phones, Nokia cell phones have turn out to be fairly widespread all through the entire UK . There are various fashions in Nokia cell phones to swimsuit the wants and expectations of the cell phone customers. Amongst its numerous different cell phones, Nokia 1600 is attuned in numerous designs and primary options.</p>
<p><b>Nokia 1600</b> is a light-weight cell phone which seems elegant with its compact dimension and chrome detailing. Nokia 1600 has a easy keypad, although, the numbers are divided into two sections, but it is fairly simpler to make use of. The consumer interface is nice sufficient for small shade show. Its shade display does not have changeable colours like Nokia 1100.Like every other widespread Nokia cell phones; Nokia 1600 gives numerous excellent options with SMS, polyphonic ring tones with MP3 grade sound, wallpapers, themes and screensavers. It has a talking alarm to remind you about essential issues. In case you like to hearken to some cool melodies then there are some twenty polyphonic ring tones with MP3 sound high quality.</p>
<p>Nokia 1600 is a light-weight weight cellphone, however you are able to do a lot with it. It has a hands-free speaker cellphone and you may simply use the menus. Nokia 1600 is mostly a consumer pleasant cellphone because it lets you do simple messaging fairly conveniently. Its cellphone e book can retailer as much as 200 contacts. Nokia 1600 has an inexpensive reminiscence which lets you retailer about 60 messages. In case you like to play some good cellular video games then Nokia 1600 gives you three cool video games Soccer League, Snake Xenias, and Fast Roll.</p>
<p>Nokia 1600 would swimsuit to all of your primary wishes, you need in a cell phone. So, get related with others with a small but stunning Nokia 1600 [http://www.mobilerainbow.org/nokia/nokia-1600.html]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
