<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>google &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/google/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Huawei Mate 10 Professional Vs Google Pixel 2 XL: Which One to Select?</title>
		<link>/huawei-mate-10-professional-vs-google-pixel-2-xl-which-one-to-select/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choose]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huawei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pixel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[select]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[which]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xl:]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/huawei-mate-10-pro-vs-google-pixel-2-xl-which-one-to-choose/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;re going to purchase new Android flagship prior to later, then likelihood is nice that you&#8217;ll find Google&#8217;s Pixel 2 XL. It is among [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re going to purchase new Android flagship prior to later, then likelihood is nice that you&#8217;ll find Google&#8217;s Pixel 2 XL. It is among the finest Android units on the planet, backed by a effectively famend Tech Title, &#8220;Google&#8221;.</p>
<p>However wait! There&#8217;s one other competitor which is providing some good options to their clients. The Huawei Mate 10 Professional smartphone matches up carefully with the Pixel 2 XL by Google on few high options and numerous tech specs; nonetheless, there are some key particulars that differ between them. Right here, we&#8217;re going to present you probably the most outstanding options of those two units with the comparability so you possibly can see the place one is doing higher than the opposite. So, let&#8217;s get began.</p>
<p><b>Design &amp; Show</b></p>
<p>Each the Huawei Mate 10 Professional and the Google Pixel 2 XL cellphones function few very 2017 design components. The Pixel 2 XL telephone machine has comparatively larger when it comes to dimensions that options gorgeous rounded corners and tiny bezels. <br />Huawei Mate 10 Professional does not have rounded corners although, nevertheless it does have a pleasant massive show. The Pixel 2 XL comes with the combination of glass and steel on the again. Then again, the Mate 10 Professional smartphone sticks with solely glass on the rear facet.</p>
<p>So far as show is worried, each telephones supply 6-inches massive sufficient show; nonetheless, the Pixel 2 XL has a P-OLED show, and Mate 10 Professional is backed by AMOLED show. Pixel 2 XL by Google provides barely higher show decision and density of 2880&#215;1440 and 537ppi respectively than the Huawei Mate 10 Professional&#8217;s 2160&#215;1080 pixel decision and 402ppi pixel density. Different options are nearly equivalent in each like Display safety and Display to physique ratio.</p>
<p><b>Efficiency</b></p>
<p>Google Pixel 2 XL comes with the identical 6 months previous Qualcomm Snapdragon 835 processor chip. Little question, it is among the quickest chips round however as in comparison with the newest flagship Android telephones, it is thought of as outdated. Nonetheless, it has loads to expertise super-fast and loopy smartphone expertise with 4GB sufficient RAM and newest Android 8.0 Oreo onboard.</p>
<p>And if you see the Huawei Mate 10 Professional, it has new and up to date HiSilicon Kirin 970 chip, which is much better than its predecessor. Backed by a neural processing unit inside for A.I necessities in addition to machine studying adapting function, that is really a velocity grasp, notably with 6GB of prolonged RAM.</p>
<p>All in all, the Kirin 970 compares very effectively, when it comes to velocity, efficiency, and on a regular basis utilization, to the Snapdragon 835 chip in benchmark testing.</p>
<p><b>Battery</b></p>
<p>Google Pixel 2 XL contains a robust Li-Ion battery with a capability of 3520mAh. Huawei gives much more highly effective Li-Polymer 4000mAh battery. It is a core distinction. And each telephones supply quick charging.</p>
<p><b>Digital camera</b></p>
<p>Huawei Mate 10 Professional goes with the same dual-camera strategy as you discovered within the P10 and P10 Plus telephones, with a 12 Mega Pixels main sensor and 20MP monochromatic secondary sensor. The digital camera of Mate 10 Professional quickly focuses on no matter you shoot and adjusts accordingly, because of its A.I abilities. That is really one of many main smartphone cameras in the marketplace right now, with none doubt.</p>
<p>However after we see the Pixel 2 XL Digital camera, it provides numerous new and thrilling options like laser autofocus and part detection and may ship spectacular pictures swiftly. As a consequence of Google&#8217;s state-of-the-art picture processing skills, you&#8217;ll get one thing unbelievable each time you shoot, and even in low mild situations. However nonetheless, it&#8217;s a single lens shooter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
