<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>last &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/last/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia 6265i Evaluate &#8211; The Newest And Final Nokia CDMA Telephone</title>
		<link>/nokia-6265i-evaluate-the-newest-and-final-nokia-cdma-telephone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[6265i]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cdma]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[final]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[last]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[newest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-6265i-review-the-latest-and-last-nokia-cdma-phone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Nokia 6265i is the newest and final CDMA telephone you may see designed from Nokia. Earlier this 12 months Nokia introduced that it&#8217;ll not [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Nokia 6265i is the newest and final CDMA telephone you may see designed from Nokia. Earlier this 12 months Nokia introduced that it&#8217;ll not be designing CDMA telephones, for one motive or one other. Regardless, Nokia actually is aware of how one can exit with a bang. The Nokia 6265i might be among the finest CDMA telephones that Nokia has to supply.</p>
<p>The Nokia 6265i incorporates a distinctive and engaging slider design. The Nokia&#8217;s high and backside slide open and closed. When closed, the telephone naturally saves area and conceals the telephone&#8217;s keypad.</p>
<p>The two megapixel digicam mounted on the Nokia 6265i takes glorious high quality images and first rate video. The digicam options flash, zoom, and night time mode. Images taken outdoor with this Nokia digicam telephone are mentioned to have the highest quality. The digicam lens offers good autofocus and the standard of the images intently rivals that of a digital digicam. Moreover, you may simply customise your telephone and use the images you are taking because the background in your telephone.</p>
<p>The display screen is sweet and vivid TFT with 262k colours (18 bit). The decision is nice at 240 x 320 pixels.</p>
<p>For the newest leisure options, the Nokia 6265 additionally helps video ringtones and streaming video. Interface options simply changeable font colours, which is enjoyable too.</p>
<p>The Nokia 6265i offers nice tone steadiness and gives you a mean earpiece quantity, although it may very well be a tad louder for my tastes.</p>
<p>The built-in reminiscence for the Nokia 6265i is first rate at round 24 mb, however you may most likely wish to increase to as much as 2 GB with the mini SD slot.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
