<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>15-inch &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/15-inch/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>15-inch Laptop computer Critiques &#8211; Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer</title>
		<link>/15-inch-laptop-computer-critiques-apple-macbook-professional-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[critiques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc118ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/15-inch-laptop-reviews-apple-macbook-pro-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from varied distinguished expertise publications. One in every of their favourite fashions was the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer.</p>
<p>The Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A has a 2.53Ghz Intel Core 2 processor. It comes with 4GB of DDR3 RAM and a 250GB onerous drive. It runs on the Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard working system and has a 15.40inch TFT display. It&#8217;s a LED back-lit and shiny display, with a 1440 x 900 decision. For graphics, it makes use of the NVIDIA GeForce 8400M graphics card.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Like the brand new era of Apple computer systems, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is sleeker than the older fashions and have an uni-body aluminum casing. It&#8217;s 14.3 x 9.8 x 0.9 inches in dimensions and 5.5 kilos in weight. General, it has a clear look, with the DVD SuperDrive on the correct facet and all of the connectors/ports on the left.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b>Though you will get an everyday Home windows OS laptop computer available in the market with comparable specs with a lesser value, let me simply say straight out that the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A performs significantly better than many different common laptops of its class.</p>
<p>For starters, the inbuilt battery within the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A can last as long as 7 hours on a single cost. We will likely be fortunate to get 3 hours out of an everyday laptop computer of this measurement. Working graphics &#8216;heavy&#8217; functions and multitasking was additionally a dream on this mannequin. The efficiency speeds in our exams have been manner higher than any of the non-Apple laptops that we now have examined. At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is priced at round $1699 every, an excellent value for a laptop computer of this stature.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A 15-Inch Laptop computer Evaluate</title>
		<link>/apple-macbook-professional-mc372ll-a-15-inch-laptop-computer-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc372ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-macbook-pro-mc372ll-a-15-inch-laptop-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some courageous souls have known as the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A a benchmark within the extremely fashionable MacBook collection. These are some fairly daring claims, [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some courageous souls have known as the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A a benchmark within the extremely fashionable MacBook collection. These are some fairly daring claims, however the whole lot I find out about this installment of the MacBook Professional collection says that these souls might be on to one thing. This transient laptop computer evaluation will try to interrupt down among the information.</p>
<p><b>Key Options</b></p>
<p>This mannequin presents a pile of particular options to flesh out the entire bundle. The options embody however are usually not restricted to:</p>
<p>· 2.53GHz Intel Core i5 dual-core processor<br />· 500GB SATA arduous drive clocked at 5,400rpm<br />· 4GB DDR3 RAM that may be expanded to 8GB<br />· 8x slot-loading DVD participant with double layer help<br />· iSight digicam for video chatting and extra<br />· two USB 2.0 ports<br />· DisplayPort video outlet with optionally available adapters</p>
<p><b>Go Professional</b></p>
<p>Together with these intensive options, the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A lined on this laptop computer evaluation has a few skilled specs properly value taking a better take a look at. For a extra advanced and regarded take a look at the MacBook Professional, head all the way down to your native retailer and ask for a &#8220;take a look at drive.&#8221;</p>
<p>The graphics switching is one thing that catches my eye, as an example. This kind of graphics flexibility cannot be taken too evenly, because it features each for model functions and conservation functions. Any laptop computer evaluation value its salt would word that the graphics switching slides effortlessly between the 2 processors (NVIDIA GeForce GT 330M and Intel HD graphics).</p>
<p>With a button-less multi-touch track-pad made from glass, the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A isn&#8217;t just a classy excuse. There is not any button, which clears up house for extra sliding and gliding. This offers you extra space to run and extra room to fastidiously discover your images and web sites with the best of ease.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
