<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>clamshell &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/clamshell/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia 6125 Clamshell Evaluation</title>
		<link>/nokia-6125-clamshell-evaluation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[6125]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[clamshell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-6125-clamshell-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Extra technically talking the Nokia 6125 is a Sequence 40 third Version cellphone. So it isn&#8217;t a smartphone, nevertheless it sensible mid-range cellphone! The most [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extra technically talking the Nokia 6125 is a Sequence 40 third Version cellphone. So it isn&#8217;t a smartphone, nevertheless it sensible mid-range cellphone! The most important distinction between a Sequence 40 cellphone and a S60 cellphone (a smartphone) is which you can set up purposes  to a smartphone.</p>
<p><b>Nokia 6125 Digital camera</b><br />
<br />The 1.3 megapixel digicam has a greater decision than the one 12 months outdated Nokia 6630 smartphone. The decision for the Nokia 6125 is 1280 x 1024 pixels and this is excellent for a mid-range cellphone.</p>
<p><b>The Display</b><br />
<br />The 6125 major show is OK &#8211; it&#8217;s an lively TFT show that helps as much as 260 000 colors. The cellphone has 2 shows and the exterior display is a CSTN show that helps as much as 65 000 colors.</p>
<p>The show has the Lively Standby function prevuously out there on smartphones solely. Lively Stanby permits entry to favourite purposes or calendar entries straight from the idle display.</p>
<p><b>Extra 6125 Options</b><br />
<br />Messaging cababilities embrace MMS, IM (prompt messaging), push to speak, Nokia Xpress audio messaging and e-mail. A brand new fascinating function is the help for Flash and the Macromedia Flash Participant.</p>
<p><b>Is This a Music Cellphone?</b><br />
<br />The cellphone has a MP3 participant that performs common music codecs (MP3, MP4, eAAC+ and WMA). Music recordsdata could be saved on a hotswappable microSD reminiscence card.</p>
<p>The 6125 has Bluetooth and you need to use wi-fi stereo headsets on the cellphone</p>
<p><b>We Say</b><br />
<br />The 6125 might not have the most recent appear like the Razr, however provides many superior options for a mid-range Nokia. The flight mode issomething most mid-range telephones are lacking, however that is out there on the 6125.</p>
<p>Photos: Nokia 6125 photographs [http://www.nokiainfo.net/blog/index.php?itemid=67]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
