<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>trend &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/trend/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Cell Recreation Pattern</title>
		<link>/the-cell-recreation-pattern/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pattern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[recreation:]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-mobile-game-trend/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Just lately, cellular gaming has been gaining a slightly giant share by way of income. Gaming consoles/platforms and on-line gaming giants have dominated the sport trade for [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just lately, cellular gaming has been gaining a slightly giant share by way of income. Gaming consoles/platforms and on-line gaming giants have dominated the sport trade for the final many years, however with the large cellular gaming insurgents, change is certainly coming and alter is welcome particularly for avid avid gamers and lovers.</p>
<p>Cell video games income forecast is predicted to extend as much as $45 billion by 2018. Asia has been the chief within the trade since 2013, and is predicted to dominate the trade by as much as 50% complete income. Business Analyst Vincent van Deelen said, &#8220;That is merely not the case. We&#8217;re additionally emphasizing that the current outcomes of particular person excessive profile corporations reminiscent of Rovio, King, DeNA and GREE will not be essentially indicative of the state of the cellular market as a complete. It isn&#8217;t in our curiosity to inflate market figures, however the laborious info have compelled us to regulate our estimates upward. We&#8217;ve maintained our year-on-year development charges towards 2017, finally resulting in a $40Bn+ market share.&#8221;</p>
<p>On this regard, cellular recreation gamers have efficiently gained giant share out there like most gaming console and on-line gaming corporations. Certainly, that is excellent news for recreation improvement corporations and their shareholders to place extra focus and emphasis on this rising pattern. Android video games are additionally anticipated to be predictably increased within the coming years. Although, it&#8217;s nonetheless a indisputable fact that iOS rakes in additional income than Google Play regardless of the latter having huge obtain for freemium mannequin kind of video games. However in a worldwide perspective, Chinese language app shops and android recreation downloads and income far exceeded iOS final 2014. North America, Europe and different Asian international locations, reminiscent of Japan and South Korea have additionally ventured within the international pattern. Studies present that cellular video games now account for almost 40% of the nation&#8217;s complete digital video games income. With elevated competitors, smaller corporations are additionally getting inventive with the introduction of e-sports, multi-screen gaming and HTML5 cellular gaming, and the ultimate pattern is the rising recognition of downloading Android video games for TV-based gaming. The highest 7 corporations  within the cellular gaming trade compete for the discharge of high quality video games to dominate additional and to not get left behind within the scene. These are a few of the most downloaded recreation apps:</p>
<p>1. aa</p>
<p>2. Agar.io</p>
<p>3. Indignant Birds</p>
<p>4. Indignant Birds Rio</p>
<p>5. Indignant Birds Seasons</p>
<p>6. Indignant Birds House</p>
<p>7. Indignant Birds Star Wars</p>
<p>8. Indignant Birds Star Wars 2</p>
<p>9. Indignant Birds Go!</p>
<p>10. Indignant Birds 2</p>
<p>11. Ant Smasher: Greatest Free Recreation</p>
<p>12. Archery Grasp 3D</p>
<p>13. Asphalt 8: Airborne</p>
<p>14. Unhealthy Piggies</p>
<p>15. Unhealthy Piggies HD</p>
<p>16. Banana Kong</p>
<p>17. Basketball Stars</p>
<p>18. Blossom Blast Saga</p>
<p>19. Increase Seashore</p>
<p>20. Courageous Frontier</p>
<p>21. Bubble Witch Saga</p>
<p>22. Bubble Witch 2 Saga</p>
<p>23. Sweet Crush Saga</p>
<p>24. Sweet Crush Soda Saga</p>
<p>25. Vehicles: Quick as Lightning</p>
<p>26. Fort Conflict: Age of Legends</p>
<p>27. Conflict of Clans</p>
<p>28. Conflict of Kings</p>
<p>29. Conflict Royale</p>
<p>30. Colour Change</p>
<p>31. Legal Case</p>
<p>32. Crossy Street</p>
<p>33. CSR Racing</p>
<p>34. Deer Hunter</p>
<p>35. Despicable Me</p>
<p>36. Diamond Sprint</p>
<p>37. Diamond Digger Saga</p>
<p>38. Do not Faucet The White Tile</p>
<p>39. Dragon Metropolis</p>
<p>40. Drag Racing Traditional</p>
<p>41. Dream League</p>
<p>42. Dumb Methods to Die</p>
<p>43. Dumb Methods to Die 2: The Video games</p>
<p>44. Excessive Automobile Driving Simulator</p>
<p>45. Quick Racing 3D</p>
<p>46. Frozen Freefall</p>
<p>47. Geometry Sprint</p>
<p>48. Geometry Sprint Lite</p>
<p>49. Farm Heroes Saga</p>
<p>50. FIFA 15 Final</p>
<p>51. Circulate Free</p>
<p>52. Fruit Ninja Free</p>
<p>53. Glow Hockey</p>
<p>54. Hay Day</p>
<p>55. Hearthstone Heroes of Warcraft</p>
<p>56. Hill Climb Racing</p>
<p>57. Hungry Shark</p>
<p>58. Jetpack Joyride</p>
<p>59. Jewels Saga</p>
<p>60. Magic Rush: Heroes</p>
<p>61. Minecraft: Pocket Version</p>
<p>62. MORTAL KOMBAT X</p>
<p>63. My Speaking Angela</p>
<p>64. My Speaking Tom</p>
<p>65. Pou</p>
<p>66. 8 Ball Pool</p>
<p>67. Pet Rescue Saga</p>
<p>68. Piano Tiles 2 (Do not Faucet&#8230;2)</p>
<p>69. Vegetation vs. Zombies</p>
<p>70. Vegetation vs. Zombies 2</p>
<p>71. Actual Racing 3</p>
<p>72. Rating! Hero</p>
<p>73. Shadow Combat 2</p>
<p>74. SimCity BuildIt</p>
<p>75. Skater Boy</p>
<p>76. Slither.io</p>
<p>77. Smash Hit</p>
<p>78. Smurfs&#8217; Village</p>
<p>79. Solitaire</p>
<p>80. Sonic Sprint</p>
<p>81. Spider-man Limitless</p>
<p>82. Stack</p>
<p>83. Star Lady</p>
<p>84. Star Wars: Galaxy of Heroes</p>
<p>85. Subway Surfers</p>
<p>86. Summoners Struggle</p>
<p>87. Speaking Tom Bubble Shooter</p>
<p>88. Temple Run</p>
<p>89. Temple Run 2</p>
<p>90. Texas Holdem Poker Deluxe</p>
<p>91. The Simpsons: Tapped Out</p>
<p>92. Throne Rush</p>
<p>93. Site visitors Racer</p>
<p>94. Site visitors Rider</p>
<p>95. Trivia Crack</p>
<p>96. Vector</p>
<p>97. Zombie Tsunami</p>
<p>98. Z Struggle</p>
<p>99. 2048</p>
<p>100. 2048 Quantity</p>
<p>It is a clear indicator that cellular gaming market share is anticipated to develop within the coming years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple iPhone 4 Overview &#8211; Love Trend, Love iPhone</title>
		<link>/apple-iphone-4-overview-love-trend-love-iphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-iphone-4-review-love-fashion-love-iphone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Apple has captured folks&#8217;s consideration with its fashionable merchandise for a very long time. It is a good distance for the reason that launch of [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Apple has captured folks&#8217;s consideration with its fashionable merchandise for a very long time. It is a good distance for the reason that launch of first iPhone. We all know that Apple iPhone 4 is a wonderful cell phone which continues the recent consideration of iPhone 3, its predecessor. Nonetheless, Apple continues to be must face the fierce competitors that there are numerous decisions for the customs like HTC, Samsung, and Motorola for the reason that market has advanced vastly previously 12 months. Nonetheless, we can not deny that iPhone 4 is among the hottest cell phones all over the world.</p>
<p>It is well-known that Apple is known for its fashionable design, which is absolutely mirrored within the trend IPhone4. No doubly, iPhone 4 is a stupendous and superb cell phone with fancy look and nice features. The decision of it&#8217;s 960 x 640 pixels. As for the looks, this cell phone has a contact display screen with an ordinary residence button. In addition to, it has a VGA digital camera within the entrance. As for the configuration, this cell phone has 512 MB RAM (random entry reminiscence), which is a superb enchancment to the iPhone 3, which solely has 256 MB RAM. Which means this cellphone could have higher expertise. As well as, this cellphone has a 5 mega pixel digital camera, which can show you how to file all of the memorable moments. With the entrance digital camera, you may make video calls along with your beloved and different pals. It&#8217;s a necessity to say that Wi-Fi is supported by this cellphone.</p>
<p>This iPhone has two units and two colours from which you&#8217;ll select. It&#8217;s obtainable in 16 GB and 32 GB, black and white. What&#8217;s extra, there are numerous iPhone covers and circumstances available in the market, by which you&#8217;ll enhance and personalize your iPhone. Since iPhone is so common and fantastic, it is going to be your first selection to point out your trend fashion. Be part of within the trend group along with your trend iPhone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
