<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>&quot;gardeno&quot; &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/gardeno/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Scaffolding Towers Evaluate: The &#034;Gardeno&#034; Cell Work Platform</title>
		<link>/scaffolding-towers-evaluate-the-gardeno-cell-work-platform/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA["gardeno"]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[platform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scaffolding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[towers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/scaffolding-towers-review-the-gardeno-mobile-work-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When you concentrate on the phrase &#8220;scaffolding tower,&#8221; chances are high you consider the kind massive scaffolding techniques you see deployed on a development web [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you concentrate on the phrase &#8220;scaffolding tower,&#8221; chances are high you consider the kind massive scaffolding techniques you see deployed on a development web site. Whereas it is true that scaffolding towers are used extensively in development, as an avid DIYer, I&#8217;ve typically wished there was a scaled down mannequin designed to be used by home-owners, particularly within the backyard. Effectively, my wait is over. I&#8217;ve discovered the right answer: the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; cell work platform. Learn on to be taught extra.</p>
<p>Concerning the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; Cell Work Platform</p>
<p>Since I&#8217;ve a reasonably intensive backyard, I am at all times on the lookout for merchandise that may expedite its care. That is an exceptionally secure and powerful mini scaffold designed with gardeners in thoughts. The &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; is mounted on two massive (10in) pneumatic tyres, so it is fairly simple to maneuver over many kinds of surfaces, onerous or delicate. By the best way, a pneumatic tyre is one which&#8217;s stuffed with air, reasonably than being stable. Fitted with impartial screw jacks at every nook, together with sturdy metal foot pads which can be 6in in diameter, the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; is straightforward to degree. The footpads stop sinking if the platform is situated on delicate floor. The platform adjusts to 4 heights: 50cms (20in), 80cms (32in), 110cms (44in), and 140cms (55in). The platform is sturdily constructed from plywood, which tends to be stronger than plain wooden planks. Surrounding the platform is a powerful metal body to which it&#8217;s securely mounted.</p>
<p>Options and Specs</p>
<p>The &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; will help a most load of 200kg (31.5st). Keep in mind that this ranking contains each the load of the particular person and the load of any instruments or supplies which can be current. Once I was looking for a piece platform, I discovered many fashions to be fairly tough to deal with. One of many causes I selected this one is that it is amazingly mild and thus very simple for one particular person to deal with. I merely use the inbuilt handles to wheel it to a brand new location in my backyard, very very similar to a wheelbarrow and never a lot heavier. Fairly effectively balanced! For sturdiness, the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; is completed in powerful epoxy-based powder coat over heavy responsibility development that makes use of sturdy 32mm (1.25in) high quality tubular metal.</p>
<p>Extra in regards to the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; Work Platform</p>
<p>You must know that this product requires some minor meeting, however no instruments are required. Simply observe the straightforward directions. Whenever you&#8217;re executed utilizing the &#8220;Gardeno,&#8221; simply take away just a few pins to pack it flat for simple storage, even in small areas. The platform dimension is a beneficiant 115cms x 42cms (45in x 16.5in). I have been in a position to attain working heights of as much as 3.5m (11ft6), so it is nice for trimming small timber and the ivy that grows on my home. Anticipate to pay about £85.00 for the versatile &#8220;Gardeno.&#8221; The value ought to embody VAT and free supply.</p>
<p>For anybody with an in depth backyard or an inventory of DIY tasks that require working at peak, the &#8220;Gardeno&#8221; cell work platform is a flexible different to massive scaffolding towers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
