<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>15.4-inch &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/15-4-inch/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>15-inch Laptop computer Critiques &#8211; Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer</title>
		<link>/15-inch-laptop-computer-critiques-apple-macbook-professional-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[critiques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc118ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/15-inch-laptop-reviews-apple-macbook-pro-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from varied distinguished expertise publications. One in every of their favourite fashions was the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer.</p>
<p>The Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A has a 2.53Ghz Intel Core 2 processor. It comes with 4GB of DDR3 RAM and a 250GB onerous drive. It runs on the Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard working system and has a 15.40inch TFT display. It&#8217;s a LED back-lit and shiny display, with a 1440 x 900 decision. For graphics, it makes use of the NVIDIA GeForce 8400M graphics card.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Like the brand new era of Apple computer systems, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is sleeker than the older fashions and have an uni-body aluminum casing. It&#8217;s 14.3 x 9.8 x 0.9 inches in dimensions and 5.5 kilos in weight. General, it has a clear look, with the DVD SuperDrive on the correct facet and all of the connectors/ports on the left.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b>Though you will get an everyday Home windows OS laptop computer available in the market with comparable specs with a lesser value, let me simply say straight out that the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A performs significantly better than many different common laptops of its class.</p>
<p>For starters, the inbuilt battery within the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A can last as long as 7 hours on a single cost. We will likely be fortunate to get 3 hours out of an everyday laptop computer of this measurement. Working graphics &#8216;heavy&#8217; functions and multitasking was additionally a dream on this mannequin. The efficiency speeds in our exams have been manner higher than any of the non-Apple laptops that we now have examined. At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is priced at round $1699 every, an excellent value for a laptop computer of this stature.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL-A 15.4-Inch Laptop computer &#8211; An Sincere Evaluate</title>
		<link>/apple-macbook-professional-mb470ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer-an-sincere-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mb470ll-a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sincere]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-macbook-pro-mb470ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-an-honest-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In case your love Apple designs and have some further money to spare, you shouldn&#8217;t hesitate to get your self an Apple product. Whether or [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In case your love Apple designs and have some further money to spare, you shouldn&#8217;t hesitate to get your self an Apple product. Whether or not it&#8217;s an MP3 participant, a desktop or a laptop computer, each Apple machine is head and shoulders above different manufacturers in some ways. After all, the additional options do include a heavy premium (a a lot greater price ticket).</p>
<p>At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer is one among my favourite notebooks out there. Though I like this mannequin primarily for its beauty, its lovely exterior does disguise many highly effective options on the within. For starters, it&#8217;s powered by a 2.4Ghz processor from Intel an has 250GB of storage. It additionally comes with 2GB of DDR3 RAM (max of 4GB) and NVDIA GeForce 9400 graphic playing cards.</p>
<p>Weighing at simply 5.5 kilos, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer fairly gentle for a 15-inch mannequin. Like all of the fashions within the newest MacBook vary, it has a light-weight aluminum body and an exquisite 15-inch shiny LED show. Regardless of feeling just a little lighter than typical, it feels very stable and sturdy.</p>
<p>The brand new Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer additionally has a brand new improved glass monitor pad that&#8217;s 40% bigger and comes with Apple&#8217;s multi-touch characteristic. It has a brand new lithium-polymer battery that may give as much as 5 hours of use on a single cost. The keyboard additionally sports activities a few new options. Typing on it feels actually good and it has back-lights that will help you sort in the dead of night.</p>
<p>As talked about earlier, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer has a reasonably steep price ticket. Is it price its value? Many options on this mannequin may be discovered on many cheaper fashions (from different manufacturers) out there. The premium that you just pay for the MacBook can be for its leading edge design, user-friendly interface and the priceless &#8216;cool-factor&#8217;. In my books, it&#8217;s completely price it!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
