<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>audio &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/audio/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Low cost Entry Degree Excessive High quality Subwoofer &#8211; JL Audio 8W0-4 Evaluate</title>
		<link>/low-cost-entry-degree-excessive-high-quality-subwoofer-jl-audio-8w0-4-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[8w0-4]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cheap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cost]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[degree]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[entry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[excessive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[high]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[level]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[low]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[subwoofer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/cheap-entry-level-high-quality-subwoofer-jl-audio-8w0-4-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Most shoppers should not fanatics. Which means you are most likely in search of a product that will get you by with worth, high quality, [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most shoppers should not fanatics. Which means you are most likely in search of a product that will get you by with worth, high quality, and efficiency. You could not essentially require your product to be one of the best of one of the best or the very best performing one available on the market. For those who&#8217;re a automotive audio fan however not essentially an fanatic, you most likely need a subwoofer that would produce bass, sufficient to make your automotive rumble or improve the deep low degree frequencies of your sound system.</p>
<p>If that is you, then the JL Audio 8W0-4 is your subwoofer of selection. It is an 8&#8243; subwoofer that packs fairly a punch. It&#8217;s able to placing out 150 watts of most energy and 75 watts of RMS steady energy. At first sight, the 8&#8243; will not be probably the most intimidating subwoofer cosmetically, nevertheless, it might certainly produce glorious high quality bass outputs because of its design.</p>
<p>The woofer consists of a polypropylene cone with a sealed polypropylene mud cap, a normal automotive subwoofer and speaker cone composition that ensures rigidity in addition to consistency in any ambient surroundings. The cone is surrounded by a big foam edge that permits the subwoofer to take care of glorious centering whereas acting at excessive excursions. Beneath the cone lies the large progressive roll flat spider that permits the 8W0-4 to make sure a superior mechanical management and placement.</p>
<p>For structural integrity assist, the <a target="_new" rel="nofollow noopener" href="http://www.sonicelectronix.com/item_12352_JL+Audio+8W0-4.html">JL Audio 8W0-4</a> contains a vented reinforcement collar, or VRC which acts like a pillar beneath a bridge performing as assist whereas absorbing performance-related power. The final function that should be identified is the 6-layer voice coil wiring on a former that&#8217;s recognized within the automotive trade world as Kapton. The results of this function is the flexibility for the subwoofer to deal with large thermal power with out shedding efficiency or damaging itself in the course of the power switch.</p>
<p>One other good factor concerning the 8W0-4 is the truth that its compact dimension doesn&#8217;t sometimes require a sealed field quantity bigger than 0.375 cubic toes or a ported field quantity bigger than 0.75 cubic toes. Which means the <a target="_new" rel="nofollow noopener" href="http://www.sonicelectronix.com/jl-audio-car-audio.html">JL Car Audio</a>8W0-4 is great for small area installations like compact automobiles or hatchbacks.</p>
<p>With options like this and its extremely reasonably priced low worth at lower than $40, how might any automotive audio novices go up a <a target="_new" rel="nofollow noopener" href="http://carsubwoofer.blogspot.com/">car subwoofer</a> deal like this?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JL Audio 8W7 Assessment</title>
		<link>/jl-audio-8w7-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[8w7]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/jl-audio-8w7-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The JL Audio 8W7 is the 8-inch model of its&#8217;s W7 line. The W7 sequence is JL Audio&#8217;s most up-to-date automobile subwoofer launch and is [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The JL Audio 8W7 is the 8-inch model of its&#8217;s W7 line. The W7 sequence is JL Audio&#8217;s most up-to-date automobile subwoofer launch and is named essentially the most technologically superior out of any of the JL Audio merchandise. The complete line options six new, patented applied sciences by no means earlier than seen within the lineup, principally as a result of not one of the earlier merchandise, remade in a second model or not, may even relate; JL Audio constructed the W7 sequence from scratch and never from a earlier mannequin. The W7 sequence focuses on sound high quality and quantity on the identical time; that&#8217;s, JL Audio desires to see how loud they&#8217;ll flip the celebration up with out having to sacrifice the sound.</p>
<p>The 8-inch model has drawn quite a few optimistic critiques from automobile audio specialists and main organizations. Automotive Sound and Efficiency calls it the &#8220;finest rattling 8-inch subwoofer ever made&#8221;. It is small, but highly effective, and the 8-inch subwoofer has by no means been made so properly in so lengthy. It is actually no marvel that it is getting rave critiques. JL Audio has actually taken benefit of the scenario and introduced the little ones to personal the larger ones.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s reported that this 8-inch model virtually did not make it to the ultimate lineup. The twenty first century is considering that greater is certainly higher, however that is not the case right here. The smallest model, a dimension hardly ever seen within the strains of different firms, has confirmed to be simply as highly effective as the opposite, extra fashionable sizes. Whereas the competitors is racing to see how massive it might make subwoofers with out dropping energy and high quality, They immediately dropped a smaller dimension, which broke the stereotype that smaller subwoofers will not do a lot good in any respect.</p>
<p>A characteristic that appears insignificant at first, the proprietor&#8217;s guide is definitely fairly essential when it comes right down to the precise set up and optimization of the JL Audio 8W7. Many take into account it is proprietor&#8217;s guide top-of-the-line, as a result of it not solely consists of the usual enclosure suggestions and specs, but in addition consists of advisable amplifiers to pair up with the 8W7 and tricks to get one of the best out of the system by way of tweaking with out busting it.</p>
<p>Total, if you wish to downsize from a 10-inch or 12-inch subwoofer, or wish to strive one thing completely different that is laborious to search out in the marketplace, the JL Audio 8W7 is a pleasant place to start out. It takes all the pieces individuals love in regards to the 10 and 12 inch items, upgrades it, and repackages it as an 8 inch. Critically, in order for you one thing that is much more highly effective than many different subwoofers in the marketplace, you will wish to select the W7 line. However in order for you one thing that is compact and does the identical, you will wish to select the 8W7.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
