<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>edge &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/edge/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge Overview</title>
		<link>/samsung-galaxy-s6-edge-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/samsung-galaxy-s6-edge-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Smartphone performance advances have actually reworked the units, making them very handy within the trendy world. Whether or not you&#8217;re keen on listening to music [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smartphone performance advances have actually reworked the units, making them very handy within the trendy world. Whether or not you&#8217;re keen on listening to music or catching up the most recent movies and flicks, share pictures and even different enterprise recordsdata and paperwork, now you can do all of it from any given location and at any given time when you&#8217;ve gotten a smartphone. Producers proceed to unveil extra advances with each new system they introduce out there and the longer term seems to be solely brighter for this business. The Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge is amongst the smartphones one can find out there and has change into a well-liked system due to a number of options.</p>
<p><strong><u>The Bodily Options </u></strong></p>
<p>The smartphone runs on the Android Lollipop working system and has an inside reminiscence of 32GB and 3GB RAM. Measuring 5.1 inches and weighing 132 g, it is a system that you&#8217;ll take pleasure in utilizing and carrying with you on daily basis in your wants.</p>
<p>This smartphone is the world&#8217;s first telephone with twin edge show. The show is thermoformed in such a means that it creates an built-in edge display screen that may bend to ship a differentiated pioneering design that solely goes to indicate the superior high quality of the system. The perimeters are curved for higher grips and examine enhancement. The curve gives a view that&#8217;s extra like a widescreen TV view making each expertise nice.</p>
<p>It has a close to invisible bezel on the display screen design which gives better entry to extra of the telephone display screen space and on the similar time additionally enhances the customers viewing expertise. This system has vibrant vivid photos in all mild situations and has enhanced out of doors visibility to make use in daylight atmosphere completely. It has a excessive pixel density of 577ppi to supply that final viewing expertise in any given location and at any time of day whatever the climate situations.</p>
<p><strong><u>Efficiency </u></strong></p>
<p>Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge has a fast voice command response. This can be a function that saves you loads of effort and time you may have used touching the varied buttons to entry the features and options that you simply want. You may personalize the system utilizing a nickname after which give instructions. You will discover the function very useful, particularly in conditions the place motion has been restricted.</p>
<p>Utilizing the smartphone, communication has been taken to an entire new stage. You may shade code your favourite contact on edge display screen in order that while you get notifications you possibly can inform from who they&#8217;re from utilizing the colours. It means which you could establish the contact for any e-mail, missed name or message you obtain even when the telephone is face down. The sting display screen is certainly handy and intuitive providing an expertise that has not been loved earlier than.</p>
<p><strong><u>Different options </u></strong></p>
<p>It has a extremely succesful digital camera providing good vibrant pictures which you could additionally monitor shifting topics and nonetheless have the clearest pictures ever. It has quick charging expertise with ten minutes of cost managing to serve you for at the very least 4 hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
