<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>choice &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/choice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Is the Android a Good Selection For a Smartphone?</title>
		<link>/is-the-android-a-good-selection-for-a-smartphone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[selection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/is-the-android-a-good-choice-for-a-smartphone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Completely &#8211; the Android is each bit as highly effective as a BlackBerry, Home windows Cell, and even an iPhone. It&#8217;s true that Google is [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Completely &#8211; the Android is each bit as highly effective as a BlackBerry, Home windows Cell, and even an iPhone. It&#8217;s true that Google is the first promoter of the Android OS however that is an Open System &#8211; which means that ultimately there will likely be numerous apps out there for the Android.</p>
<p>As you start so as to add apps to your telephone a superb place to begin is with Google Apps There are 4 (4) Google apps out there for many cell gadgets at no cost. They&#8217;re Google Search, Google Maps, Google Gmail, and YouTube. These Apps are highly regarded and have been round longer than the Android. They&#8217;ve been optimized for the Android platform however you can see that the Google Apps can be found for many different platforms. Prior to now I used these on a Home windows Cell machine and have the Google Apps anchored to my At present Display.</p>
<p>The subsequent logical query is that this: What else can an Android do apart from Google Apps? I lately obtained my palms on a T Cell G1 and have been downloading some &#8220;free&#8221; video games and apps for this cool Android gadget. There&#8217;s a lot to select from however you can see that it takes time and persistence to search out something price retaining.</p>
<p>Your finest guess is to begin with contemplating what you wish to take Cell. If you&#8217;re like most individuals and are into social networking, you then clearly wish to bookmark the cell websites for Fb and Twitter. There are additionally many different classes of third Celebration apps comparable to Food plan &amp; Health, Journey &amp; Leisure, Work &amp; College, and many others.</p>
<p>For instance, if you&#8217;re into weight-reduction plan or bodily health you can see some apps out there for the Android however the choices are extra restricted than that for the BlackBerry or Home windows Cell platforms. That is primarily as a result of the Android OS platform has not been out lengthy sufficient for builders to transform their current merchandise.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
