<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>xiaomi &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/xiaomi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Xiaomi XiaoFang Evaluate</title>
		<link>/xiaomi-xiaofang-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xiaofang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xiaomi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/xiaomi-xiaofang-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Have you ever ever heard of the recent product, Xiaomi XiaoFang? This can be a sensible WiFi IP digital camera, which primarily options 1080P Full [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever ever heard of the recent product, Xiaomi XiaoFang? This can be a sensible WiFi IP digital camera, which primarily options 1080P Full HD video, enhanced 9m evening imaginative and prescient, and cell sound detection. What&#8217;s extra, it helps diversified purposes. And now, let&#8217;s examine it intimately.</p>
<p><strong>Design and Efficiency</strong></p>
<p>This sensible digital camera seems like a dice with a aspect size of 5cm. And it weighs solely 100g, compact and transportable. It helps the reminiscence card of as much as 64GB and is powered by 5V / 1A energy provide.</p>
<p>As for the lens, with using a 1/2.7 inch CMOS sensor, it gives 1920&#215;1080 full HD decision, helps as much as 8 instances digital zoom and distortion correction algorithm. And it adopts evening imaginative and prescient enhancement expertise, F/2.0 iris lens with IR-CUT computerized twin filters, and infrared LED uniform fill gentle in order that the utmost visible distance is as much as 9m.</p>
<p>Extra fascinating is that the magnetic base might be adsorbed on the metallic floor in order that the 2 XiaoFang cameras might be mixed by way of the magnetic absorption, routinely composing the 180° wide-angle display. For safety, it takes the strategy of a mixture of RSA encryption, https encryption, and Xiaomi Mi Cloud knowledge encryption.</p>
<p>Specs:</p>
<ul>
<li>360° view</li>
<li>1080p video taking pictures</li>
<li>Supporting an 8x digital Magic Zoom</li>
<li>IR-CUT computerized double filter</li>
<li>Supporting Evening Imaginative and prescient, max 9 meters</li>
<li>Utilizing together with your cellphone App</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Purposes</strong></p>
<p>In a way, XiaoFang breaks the definition boundaries of a sensible digital camera. As an illustration, it helps connecting to the cell energy and the cell phone instantly. And the info transmission is smoother when the included hotspot has been connecting to the cellphone within the non-network scene. What&#8217;s extra, this digital camera might be an car recorder. It not solely helps delay images, clever cell detection, sound monitoring but in addition can determine the smoke/CO alarm particular alarm sound. As soon as the suspicious circumstances occurred, it will document the video routinely, and push alarm notifications quickly.</p>
<p><strong>Abstract</strong></p>
<p>As we will see, the digital camera will tackle the position of data sensor sooner or later wave of dwelling intelligentization. The XiaoFang digital camera solely helps the Mi dwelling APP. Sooner or later, Xiaomi XiaoFang will play a giant position within the sensible dwelling system, because the auxiliary gear for different sensible units. By accumulating and recognizing the sound and picture within the dwelling, this digital camera would supply the datum basis of the entire sensible dwelling system.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xiaomi Mi Word 2 Evaluate</title>
		<link>/xiaomi-mi-word-2-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[note]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[word]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xiaomi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/xiaomi-mi-note-2-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Xiaomi firm has unveiled the brand new product Xiaomi Mi Word 2, a robust competitor for Samsung Galaxy Word 7. On this article, I&#8217;ll inform [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Xiaomi firm has unveiled the brand new product Xiaomi Mi Word 2, a robust competitor for Samsung Galaxy Word 7. On this article, I&#8217;ll inform you one thing about it. And the content material entails 4 components, together with display, digital camera, battery and specs.</p>
<p><strong>Twin Curved-Edge OLED Show</strong></p>
<p>The twin curved-edge display is the spotlight of Xiaomi Mi Word 2, and this is similar design of Samsung Galaxy Word 7. This 5.7-inch versatile OLED show brings not solely good visible enjoyment but additionally a wider visual field. Extremely-thin versatile OLED show options 77.2% screen-to-body ratio, 110% NTSC coloration gamut and 100,000: 1 distinction ratio. And it even might be learn below the solar.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the 3D glass curves seamlessly on left and proper widening the visual field. With the versatile substrate of OLED show, it will possibly match below the bends of 3D curved glass. 7-series aluminum steel body connects the back and front coated glass, which reveals the symmetrical aesthetic.</p>
<p><strong>22.56MP Excessive-Decision Digital camera</strong></p>
<p>The Mi Word 2 is configured with a high-resolution 22.56MPback digital camera, which comes with the IMX318 Exmor RSTM stacked picture sensor. And it options PDAF part detection, distinction autofocus and 32s lengthy publicity photographs. Devoted 3-axis gyroscope brings high-speed jitter detection and compensation in actual time.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it comes with an 8MP entrance digital camera with Beautify 3.0 know-how, assembly the necessity of those that prefer to take selfies of their each day life. And the autofocus operate brings a wonderful taking pictures feeling.</p>
<p><strong>4070mAh Excessive-Capability Battery</strong></p>
<p>It&#8217;s powered by an enormous capability 4070mAh Lithium-Polymer battery, and it helps QC3.0 quick cost know-how.</p>
<p><strong>Xiaomi Mi Word 2 Specs</strong></p>
<p>Model: Xiaomi</p>
<p>Mannequin: Mi Word 2</p>
<p>Gadget Kind: Android Smartphone</p>
<p>CPU: Quad-Core Twin cluster Kryo 2×2.35GHz + 2×2.0GHz</p>
<p>Chipset: Qualcomm Snapdragon 821</p>
<p>GPU: Qualcomm Adreno 530</p>
<p>Digital camera: 22.56 Megapixels with Twin-LED and AF Rear Digital camera | 8 Megapixel Entrance digital camera</p>
<p>Reminiscence: RAM- 4GB/6GB | ROM 64GB/128GB Exterior Reminiscence Not Supported</p>
<p>Show: Display screen measurement 5.7 inches OLED QHD (1080×1920 Pixels)</p>
<p>Battery: Non-Detachable 4,070 mAh Lithium-Polymer</p>
<p>SIM: Twin SIM (Nano + Nano)</p>
<p>Sensors: Proximity Sensor, Accelerometer, Ambient Mild, Fingerprint, Compass, Gyroscope, Barometer, Corridor</p>
<p>Colour: Black, Silver</p>
<p>Working System: Android 6.0 Marshmallow with MIUI V8</p>
<p>Dimensions: 156.2 x 77.3 x 7.6 mm</p>
<p>Weight: 166 Grams</p>
<p><strong>Abstract</strong></p>
<p>This new product Xiaomi Mi Word 2 has an impressive look design. It has three variations, together with 64GB storage, 128GB storage and International version. In the event you prefer it, you possibly can have a attempt!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
