<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>built &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/built/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>iSAFE Backpacks and Baggage &#8211; The Solely Backpack With a Constructed In Cellular Private Security Alarm &#8211; A Overview</title>
		<link>/isafe-backpacks-and-baggage-the-solely-backpack-with-a-constructed-in-cellular-private-security-alarm-a-overview/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alarm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backpack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backpacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baggage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bags]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[built]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[constructed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[isafe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[only]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[private]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solely]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[with]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/isafe-backpacks-and-bags-the-only-backpack-with-a-built-in-mobile-personal-safety-alarm-a-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve been satisfied of the efficacy of non-public safety merchandise since September of 2008 but it surely was solely September of this 12 months (2011) [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been satisfied of the efficacy of non-public safety merchandise since September of 2008 but it surely was solely September of this 12 months (2011) that I turned conscious of the iSAFE Backpacks and Baggage. I used to be truly stunned that I did not consider such a product earlier than. In spite of everything, I do know of a number of private alarms in varied codecs &#8211; ones that double as a keychain, others slot in a handbag, some to position on a window or door and plenty of extra. Though these alarms make the required noise to name consideration to 1&#8217;s want for assist in a harmful state of affairs and are comparatively cheap, they&#8217;re additionally straightforward to depart at dwelling or straightforward to misplace or lose.</p>
<p>The iSAFE bag, then again, is the primary patented backpack and bag with a built-in cell private safety alarm system. With the pull of a twine positioned on the iSafe backpack&#8217;s shoulder strap, the consumer can set off two excessive pitched screaming sirens (louder than most automobile alarms) and a high-intensity strobe mild to name consideration to their harmful state of affairs and the necessity for instant assist. To deactivate the alarm merely reinsert the pin. Reflectors on the shoulder strap present night-time visibility for added security.</p>
<p>The baggage are made from very sturdy nylon, are water and shock resistant, have robust zippers that won&#8217;t simply injury and open and shut easily. The i SAFE backpacks have a number of sturdy and roomy compartments to retailer every thing youngsters, youngsters, school college students, and adults would possibly wish to carry together with a person compartment for a cellphone or iPod. There&#8217;s even sufficient room for a laptop computer laptop.</p>
<p>As well as, the iSAFE backpack is made extra snug to put on by the froth padding and S-shaped shoulder straps which offer good again assist. The adjustable chest strap prevents the backpack from being simply taken away.</p>
<p>The alarm is powered by two 9V batteries and, if wanted, will run constantly for 2 hours. If the consumer turns into misplaced throughout a hike they&#8217;ll run the alarm constantly for the 2 hours or change it on and off to preserve battery energy. Nevertheless, due to its electrical elements, the iSafe backpack can&#8217;t be submerged in water.</p>
<p>iSafe luggage begin at simply $59.99 and have the identical high quality, options, pockets and sturdiness of main backpack and bag suppliers like Jansport, L.L. Bean, Northface and Targus. iSAFE Backpacks and Messenger luggage can be found in Blue, Black, Pink, Plaid, Geometric, Multicolor, and Brand design materials.</p>
<p>The iSafe backpack is good for youngsters who wish to shield themselves from bullies or predators lurking the streets, hikers who could have to sign for assist, anybody strolling by a darkish parking storage or lot, joggers, accident victims, and anybody else in search of an added sense of safety. As a mum or dad, I positive really feel calmer and safer understanding that my baby takes the iSAFE Backpack each time they depart the home.</p>
<p>One could marvel if these luggage will go airport safety checks. At the moment it&#8217;s suggested that the batteries be eliminated earlier than going by safety and permitting a bit of further time on the airport for the safety folks to examine the bag completely.</p>
<p>Should you register your iSafe bag buy on-line or over the cellphone, you may change your backpack for a brand new one for 50% the unique worth. You are able to do this annually, and there&#8217;s no restrict to what number of occasions you may change your backpack.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
