<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>laptop &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/laptop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>15-inch Laptop computer Critiques &#8211; Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer</title>
		<link>/15-inch-laptop-computer-critiques-apple-macbook-professional-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[critiques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc118ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/15-inch-laptop-reviews-apple-macbook-pro-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from varied distinguished expertise publications. One in every of their favourite fashions was the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer.</p>
<p>The Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A has a 2.53Ghz Intel Core 2 processor. It comes with 4GB of DDR3 RAM and a 250GB onerous drive. It runs on the Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard working system and has a 15.40inch TFT display. It&#8217;s a LED back-lit and shiny display, with a 1440 x 900 decision. For graphics, it makes use of the NVIDIA GeForce 8400M graphics card.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Like the brand new era of Apple computer systems, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is sleeker than the older fashions and have an uni-body aluminum casing. It&#8217;s 14.3 x 9.8 x 0.9 inches in dimensions and 5.5 kilos in weight. General, it has a clear look, with the DVD SuperDrive on the correct facet and all of the connectors/ports on the left.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b>Though you will get an everyday Home windows OS laptop computer available in the market with comparable specs with a lesser value, let me simply say straight out that the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A performs significantly better than many different common laptops of its class.</p>
<p>For starters, the inbuilt battery within the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A can last as long as 7 hours on a single cost. We will likely be fortunate to get 3 hours out of an everyday laptop computer of this measurement. Working graphics &#8216;heavy&#8217; functions and multitasking was additionally a dream on this mannequin. The efficiency speeds in our exams have been manner higher than any of the non-Apple laptops that we now have examined. At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is priced at round $1699 every, an excellent value for a laptop computer of this stature.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HP Pavilion Dv6-1354US 15.6-Inch Laptop computer &#8211; An Sincere Assessment</title>
		<link>/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-an-sincere-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dv6-1354us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pavilion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sincere]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-an-honest-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very best laptops available in the market, they&#8217;re consistently producing new laptop computer fashions that include quite a lot of new and improved options. The brand new HP Pavilion DV6-1354US is at present one in every of HP&#8217;s newest 15.6-inch laptop computer fashions available in the market. It has a 2.2Ghz Core 2 Duo processor, 4GB of RAM and a bigger 500GB onerous drive. For show, this laptop computer has a 15.6-inch LED back-lit HD display screen (with a 1366 x 768 decision). Then there&#8217;s the set of Altec Lansing audio system that runs on SRS Premium sound expertise. Different specs embody 4 USB ports, a reminiscence card reader, HDMI output, Intel Wifi Hyperlink 100GBN, and rather more</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> The HP Pavilion DV6-1354US sports activities a shiny jet-black casing that&#8217;s properly contrasted with hints of silver. For an edge, the laptop computer is embellished with some round motifs. This mannequin measure at about 14.9 x 10.15 x 1.5 inches and weighs 6.34 kilos, which is in regards to the measurement of a mean 15-inch laptop computer. General, this laptop computer sports activities HP&#8217;s signature skilled and modern look.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> Judging from its specs, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US can be nicely suited to both work or play. It even comes with a tiny (but complete) distant management to allow you to entry quite a lot of multimedia controls from a distance. For graphics rendering, this mannequin makes use of the Intel Graphics Media Accelerator 4500MHD graphics card. The 6-cell batteries on this mannequin can last as long as 4 hours on one cost, which is kind of good for a laptop computer of this measurement (and specs). All in all, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US 15.6-inch laptop computer is designed for anybody who&#8217;s on the lookout for purposeful and inexpensive full-featured laptop computer. Presently, this laptop computer is promoting for round $699 per unit, which is a good worth for this very competent laptop computer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gateway NV5331u 15.6-Inch Laptop computer Evaluation</title>
		<link>/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-evaluation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gateway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nv5331u]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in all probability attributable to its nice set of specs, good design and cheap price ticket. This mannequin comes with an AMD Turion Extremely M600 dual-core processor (2.4Ghz). Then there&#8217;s the 15.6-inch HD show, ATI Radeon HD 4200 graphics card, and a set of stereo audio system (with Dolby Sound applied sciences). Among the different normal options embody the 8X DVD drive, multi-gesture observe pad, 4 USB ports and a HDMI port.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Though Gateway is known for his or her budget-friendly laptop computer fashions, their desktops and laptops look something however low-cost. Gateway has an awesome design crew and virtually every bit of machine rolled out from them has a really skilled and modern look. The Gateway NV5331u sports activities a classical and curvy design. It measures at 3.97 x 16.6 x 12.4 inches in dimensions and weighs 5.84 kilos.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is mostly an awesome mid-range laptop computer mannequin that&#8217;s nice for leisure of labor functions. The HD graphic card will likely be excellent for anybody who typically watches a number of motion pictures and HD movies on their laptop computer. The 4GB of RAM and the brand new i3 processor additionally allows you to carry out a wide range of heavy duties flawlessly. This mannequin is powered by a 6-cell battery that may last as long as 2 hours and 40 minutes on one full cost. In the meanwhile, the Gateway NV5331u 15.6-inch laptop computer is retailing for simply round $699 per unit, which is a superb worth for this set of specs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Laptop computer Evaluate &#8211; Dell Alienware M15x</title>
		<link>/laptop-computer-evaluate-dell-alienware-m15x/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alienware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[m15x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/laptop-review-dell-alienware-m15x/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A laptop computer devoted for die-hard followers of utmost gaming, the Dell Alienware M15x often known as the Space 51 M15x. It is really a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A laptop computer devoted for die-hard followers of utmost gaming, the Dell Alienware M15x often known as the Space 51 M15x. It is really a revamp of the outdated Space 51 M15x laptop computer that first got here out with the Intel Core 2 Excessive X9000 2.8GHz (6MB Cache, 800MHz FSB) powering its system. This processor has a excessive potential because it made different gaming laptops seem like as sluggish as a turtle. It additionally has the Dell turbo enhance know-how that enhances its processing unit.</p>
<p>At the moment, the Dell Alienware M15x comes with three processor choices &#8211; the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i3 cell processor for laptops is the primary stage of Intel&#8217;s new processor household, adopted by the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 cell processor mannequin and the brand new Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 processor. The Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 is the most recent and strongest processor of all time, however the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 will not be going to lose lots in processing prowess.</p>
<p>This Dell Alienware M15x laptop computer with Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 has two prototypes: the Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 540M 2.53GHz (3.06GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache) and the Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 430M 2.26GHz (2.53GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache). Each CPUs run on two cores, however might outrun different twin core processors, together with its predecessors. That&#8217;s the reason, even with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5, this alienware laptop computer is taken into account unusually massive and highly effective within the gaming world and is poised to turn out to be one of many favorites of hardcore avid gamers with budgets not sufficient to accumulate the same laptop computer with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 in it.</p>
<p>The Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 processor on the Dell Alienware M15x function: Intel&reg; Turbo Increase Know-how, Intel&reg; Hyper-Threading Know-how and helps Enhanced Intel SpeedStep&reg; Know-how. This method permits any Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 processor to run at a sooner clock charge whereas doing large processing duties.</p>
<p>To go with its pace and energy, this Dell Alienware Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 model is loaded with 4GB to a most of 8GB DDR3 RAM with FSB of 1066MHz and 1333Mhz respectively. This ensures very easy efficiency even when accessing memory-hungry purposes. One other vital recognition is the show rendering heavy graphics purposes turns into a breeze with its devoted graphics card because the Dell Alienware M15x is put in with 1GB NVIDIA&reg; GeForce&reg; GTX 260M or an non-obligatory 512MB NVIDIA&reg; GeForce&reg; GT 240M video card.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 model is out there with a gamer-like chassis and there are three colours to select from &#8212; Nebula Crimson, Cosmic Black and Lunar Shadow. It could actually retailer as much as 250 GB of digital information and if storage will not be sufficient, the laptop computer has a BD-ROM/DVD/-RW drive to burn information with.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 model additionally comes with a full HD show with a decision of 1920 x 1080 pixels &#8211; preferrred not just for gaming but in addition for multimedia expertise.</p>
<p><strong>Specs:</strong></p>
<p>Central Processing Unit</p>
<ul>
<li>Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 540M 2.53GHz (3.06GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache)</li>
<li>Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 430M 2.26GHz (2.53GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache)</li>
</ul>
<p>Learn Entry Reminiscence</p>
<ul>
<li>4 GB</li>
</ul>
<p>Storage Drive</p>
<ul>
<li>SATA 250GB Onerous Drive 7,200 rpm</li>
</ul>
<p>Optical Drive</p>
<ul>
<li>BD-ROM/DVD /-RW</li>
</ul>
<p>Show Dimension</p>
<ul>
<li>15.6 inches</li>
</ul>
<p>Native Decision</p>
<ul>
<li>1920 x 1080</li>
</ul>
<p>Dimension</p>
<ul>
<li>Top: 1.92 inches x Width: 14.88 inches x 12.15 inches</li>
</ul>
<p>Graphics Card</p>
<ul>
<li>Nvidia GeForce GTX 260M with 1 GB VRAM</li>
</ul>
<p>Weight</p>
<ul>
<li>9.0 kilos</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Professionals</strong></p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x with Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 only a notch much less highly effective than the one with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x with Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 is actually admirable with its superior graphics, full HD show and a Blu-Ray prepared drive.</p>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<p>This Alienware comes with an Inside Excessive-Definition 5.1 Encompass Sound Audio system that delivers sound adequately. With a weight of 9 kilos, some individuals may discover the Dell Alienware M15x too heavy. This does not have an HDMI port, solely a firewire port.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A 15-Inch Laptop computer Evaluate</title>
		<link>/apple-macbook-professional-mc372ll-a-15-inch-laptop-computer-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc372ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-macbook-pro-mc372ll-a-15-inch-laptop-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some courageous souls have known as the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A a benchmark within the extremely fashionable MacBook collection. These are some fairly daring claims, [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some courageous souls have known as the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A a benchmark within the extremely fashionable MacBook collection. These are some fairly daring claims, however the whole lot I find out about this installment of the MacBook Professional collection says that these souls might be on to one thing. This transient laptop computer evaluation will try to interrupt down among the information.</p>
<p><b>Key Options</b></p>
<p>This mannequin presents a pile of particular options to flesh out the entire bundle. The options embody however are usually not restricted to:</p>
<p>· 2.53GHz Intel Core i5 dual-core processor<br />· 500GB SATA arduous drive clocked at 5,400rpm<br />· 4GB DDR3 RAM that may be expanded to 8GB<br />· 8x slot-loading DVD participant with double layer help<br />· iSight digicam for video chatting and extra<br />· two USB 2.0 ports<br />· DisplayPort video outlet with optionally available adapters</p>
<p><b>Go Professional</b></p>
<p>Together with these intensive options, the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A lined on this laptop computer evaluation has a few skilled specs properly value taking a better take a look at. For a extra advanced and regarded take a look at the MacBook Professional, head all the way down to your native retailer and ask for a &#8220;take a look at drive.&#8221;</p>
<p>The graphics switching is one thing that catches my eye, as an example. This kind of graphics flexibility cannot be taken too evenly, because it features each for model functions and conservation functions. Any laptop computer evaluation value its salt would word that the graphics switching slides effortlessly between the 2 processors (NVIDIA GeForce GT 330M and Intel HD graphics).</p>
<p>With a button-less multi-touch track-pad made from glass, the Apple MacBook Professional MC372LL/A isn&#8217;t just a classy excuse. There is not any button, which clears up house for extra sliding and gliding. This offers you extra space to run and extra room to fastidiously discover your images and web sites with the best of ease.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL-A 15.4-Inch Laptop computer &#8211; An Sincere Evaluate</title>
		<link>/apple-macbook-professional-mb470ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer-an-sincere-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mb470ll-a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sincere]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/apple-macbook-pro-mb470ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-an-honest-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In case your love Apple designs and have some further money to spare, you shouldn&#8217;t hesitate to get your self an Apple product. Whether or [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In case your love Apple designs and have some further money to spare, you shouldn&#8217;t hesitate to get your self an Apple product. Whether or not it&#8217;s an MP3 participant, a desktop or a laptop computer, each Apple machine is head and shoulders above different manufacturers in some ways. After all, the additional options do include a heavy premium (a a lot greater price ticket).</p>
<p>At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer is one among my favourite notebooks out there. Though I like this mannequin primarily for its beauty, its lovely exterior does disguise many highly effective options on the within. For starters, it&#8217;s powered by a 2.4Ghz processor from Intel an has 250GB of storage. It additionally comes with 2GB of DDR3 RAM (max of 4GB) and NVDIA GeForce 9400 graphic playing cards.</p>
<p>Weighing at simply 5.5 kilos, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer fairly gentle for a 15-inch mannequin. Like all of the fashions within the newest MacBook vary, it has a light-weight aluminum body and an exquisite 15-inch shiny LED show. Regardless of feeling just a little lighter than typical, it feels very stable and sturdy.</p>
<p>The brand new Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer additionally has a brand new improved glass monitor pad that&#8217;s 40% bigger and comes with Apple&#8217;s multi-touch characteristic. It has a brand new lithium-polymer battery that may give as much as 5 hours of use on a single cost. The keyboard additionally sports activities a few new options. Typing on it feels actually good and it has back-lights that will help you sort in the dead of night.</p>
<p>As talked about earlier, the Apple MacBook Professional MB470LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer has a reasonably steep price ticket. Is it price its value? Many options on this mannequin may be discovered on many cheaper fashions (from different manufacturers) out there. The premium that you just pay for the MacBook can be for its leading edge design, user-friendly interface and the priceless &#8216;cool-factor&#8217;. In my books, it&#8217;s completely price it!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
