<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>sms &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sms/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>High 5 Free SMS Managers for Android</title>
		<link>/high-5-free-sms-managers-for-android/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[high]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[managers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/top-5-free-sms-managers-for-android/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Software program functions, shortened to Apps, have helped improve a smartphone person&#8217;s capability to multitask. It presents all the things at your fingertips. Nonetheless, there [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Software program functions, shortened to Apps, have helped improve a smartphone person&#8217;s capability to multitask. It presents all the things at your fingertips. Nonetheless, there are a number of functions that don&#8217;t introduce something new; they enhance on present features.</p>
<p>Textual content messaging or SMS has been round for ages even earlier than Android opened its eyes to the world. An SMS permits you to convey advanced messages within the least variety of phrases. A couple of apps designed for Android have revamped the standard textual content messaging characteristic. They can help you set up SMSs in your system, present backup, common inbox cleanups and blocking and security measures. There are free and paid SMS supervisor apps for Android. We&#8217;ve mentioned 5 Free SMS Managers for Android.</p>
<p><strong>1. </strong><strong>SMS Backup n2 Supervisor: </strong></p>
<p>The identify offers you a touch of the first characteristic it presents. It permits you to backup and restore textual content messages. Once you obtain and set up the appliance in your system, a backup file is created in your SD card. All textual content messages are transferred out of your telephone to this backup file thereby liberating up tons of telephone reminiscence. It backups up all the things; you may delete what you don&#8217;t want. The opposite spotlight options embody the flexibility to ship worldwide messages at a low fee, bubble type chat view and multi-language assist.</p>
<p><strong>2. </strong><strong>Gate SMS: </strong></p>
<p>Gate SMS is one other free SMS supervisor for Android gadgets that may be downloaded on the Google Play retailer. That is an app to make use of in case your service expenses unusually excessive textual content charges. It presents web gateway assist and helps you save on each textual content message you ship. It identifies the operator robotically, reminds customers of unread messages and permits you to set a message ringtone of your selection with completely different ranges of vibration. The one disadvantage is that this free SMS administration app for Android shows a number of advertisements not current within the premium model.</p>
<p><strong>3. </strong><strong>SMS Guard: </strong></p>
<p>It is annoying to be bombarded with junk messages from unknown individuals. SMS Guard stands out for its blocking characteristic. You solely have so as to add the quantity to the Deny listing. Thereafter, all messages from that quantity will robotically be eliminated to the junk field or deleted with out notifications. Not all SMS supervisor functions are suitable with older variations of Android. SMS Guard helps Android variations 1.6 and up.</p>
<p><strong>4. </strong><strong>SMS Supervisor: </strong></p>
<p>How you want there was a solution to cover personal and private messages from prying eyes! Luckily, there&#8217;s one within the type of SMS Supervisor. It lets you transfer textual content messages from the Android inbox to the appliance inbox. The password safety characteristic makes it straightforward to cover private textual content messages from others. One other good characteristic is the flexibility to allow and disable notifications for incoming and outgoing textual content messages.</p>
<p><strong>5. </strong><strong>Auto SMS Cleaner /Deleter </strong></p>
<p>In case your inbox is full of junk and is consuming into your telephone reminiscence, it is time for a cleanup. We&#8217;re not speaking about deleting single messages. This greatest free Android SMS supervisor permits you to cleans a number of message at a time. The person has to enter the 2 dates between which he desires the messages to be deleted. One needn&#8217;t fear as deleted messages could be restored later.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ship Textual content Messages Free &#8211; 5 Free SMS Websites Reviewed</title>
		<link>/ship-textual-content-messages-free-5-free-sms-websites-reviewed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviewed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[send]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sites]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[text]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[textual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[websites]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/send-text-messages-free-5-free-sms-sites-reviewed/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Free textual content messaging websites have been round since earlier than 2000. In that point, some good (and a few dangerous) free SMS providers have [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Free textual content messaging websites</strong> have been round since earlier than 2000.</p>
<p>In that point, some good (and a few dangerous) free SMS providers have come and gone! Fortunately, there are nonetheless tons of of the way you are able to do free internet SMS. However what follows is a brief, up-to-date record of 5 beneficial free SMS websites, reviewed.</p>
<p>Which imply now you can confidently ship textual content messages free whether or not you reside in USA, UK, India, Pakistan, or wherever on this planet!</p>
<p>So with out additional ado, right here goes with my private alternative of nice methods to &#8216;ship textual content message from laptop&#8217;, wherever you reside on this planet&#8230;</p>
<p><strong>1. TextYourBuddy.com &#8211; USA</strong></p>
<p>Most of the free textual content messaging websites in America, USA, work by permitting you to ship e-mail to SMS. And I imagine that is how the favored TextYourBuddy.com works too. So this simply means you want to know the cell phone community of the particular person you are sending your textual content message to.</p>
<p>It is advisable to register to make use of TextYourBuddy.com, however this implies you may obtain replies on-line too. And you may also retailer your favorite contacts in an deal with guide. Present restrict on texts is 50 SMS per 30 days.</p>
<p>TextYourBuddy.com additionally works for different international locations on this planet, too, it appears.</p>
<p><strong>2. eSeMeS.co.uk &#8211; UK</strong></p>
<p>That is fairly a brand new free SMS service, on-line in 2010 I feel. It is free for UK customers solely (however you may ship low cost SMS to different components of the world if you happen to purchase credit). That is an easy-to-use and quick option to ship free SMS messages to UK (British) cell phone customers.</p>
<p>No registration is required to make use of this service.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s hope eSeMeS.co.uk sticks round as a result of it is simply among the best, most dependable SMS websites on the market proper now.</p>
<p><strong>3. 160By2 &#8211; India</strong>*</p>
<p>Sending textual content messages in India may be very common. Which implies there are a lot of, many free SMS textual content messaging websites and providers that can help you ship free texts in India.</p>
<p>Among the finest free textual content messaging providers &#8211; and one which&#8217;s been round since 2007 &#8211; is 160by2.com. It is advisable to register, however it permits you to ship a number of messages per day. There&#8217;s even a cellular app (software) that allows you to ship free SMS by way of your cellphone.</p>
<p>* Be aware: 160by2.com additionally works if you wish to ship free messages to Kuwait, UAE, Saudi Arabia, Singapore, Philippines, and Malaysia</p>
<p><strong>4. LoOp &#8211; Pakistan</strong></p>
<p>This straightforward-to-use web site permits you to ship free SMS to any Cellular community in Pakistan; i.e. to Warid, Ufone, Zong, Mobilink and Telenor. Textual content messages will be as much as 130 characters in size solely.</p>
<p>Easy as that, actually. It does look to have been upgraded, not too long ago, to permit folks to ship and obtain free textual content messages even if you happen to do not dwell in Pakistan. This has not been examined at time of writing, although.</p>
<p><strong>5. SMScity.nl &#8211; Worldwide</strong></p>
<p>If not one of the free internet SMS websites listed are of use to you, since you dwell in a rustic not listed up to now, then SMScity.nl is the free SMS service for you.</p>
<p>And that is as a result of it permits you to ship SMS messages free wherever you reside. You&#8217;ll be able to solely ship a couple of free SMS messages per day, however it&#8217;s doable to earn additional free SMS credit if mandatory.</p>
<p>&#8212;</p>
<p>So there you will have it &#8211; among the finest websites to ship textual content messages free on-line, briefly reviewed, together with international locations like USA, UK, India, Pakistan and worldwide.</p>
<p>Here is to you and blissful on-line texting to your family and friends no matter a part of the world you (and so they) dwell in.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
