<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>can &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/can/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Android Smartphone: How one can Select the Finest?</title>
		<link>/android-smartphone-how-one-can-select-the-finest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[can]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[choose]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[select]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-smartphone-how-to-choose-the-best/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many Smartphones have been launched within the know-how market within the latest time. It&#8217;s due to altering know-how and the software program that makes it [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many Smartphones have been launched within the know-how market within the latest time. It&#8217;s due to altering know-how and the software program that makes it troublesome for customers to choose. If  the standards for selecting the perfect out there possibility in Android Smartphone then you may be simply in a position to decide one for your self. Allow us to discover out the standards that it is advisable to know for selecting the perfect Android Smartphone.</p>
<p>Very first thing that it is advisable to take into account are the specs. Allow us to scrutinize these one after the other and discover out.</p>
<p><b>1. OS or Working System</b></p>
<p>Earlier than you resolve on selecting the most recent out there model, you first have to know that Android retains getting updates. Due to this fact, when you personal an Android that isn&#8217;t on par with the most recent software program model out there then you needn&#8217;t fear. You may improve your gadget and obtain the most recent Android model. The variations can be found on-line for downloads, you&#8217;ll be able to simply entry these by means of your gadget or login to acquire the most recent model. Newest software program model has many options, free choices and is appropriate with the brand new Smartphones. With new OS (Working System), it is possible for you to to obtain new wallpapers, get a quicker entry, have a brand new menu and different such added options.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, it&#8217;s essential to bear in mind one factor that not each Android is designed to obtain updates. Typically there are updates out there for particular OS solely whereas others are rendered out of date. For instance, you have already got Gingerbread; you may be tied to it till you get an replace for this specific model. Do not forget that software program improve will not be one thing assured. It&#8217;s higher to go for an Android model that&#8217;s able to receiving new updates and the latest model ought to be saved in thoughts whereas making a purchase order.</p>
<p><b>2. Updates</b></p>
<p>Being eager on making software program updates is comprehensible however what if you&#8217;re not in a position to deploy the identical in your gadget? One important factor is that you must go for the most recent gadget out there. Select the most recent handset out there. You may come throughout varied Xperia sequence or Galaxy sequence and so forth with totally different manufacturers. A modern out there gadget is able to accepting software program upgrades. You must control the most recent out there model to know if the mentioned producer is eager on releasing one other software program improve for that particular gadget.</p>
<p>When selecting an Android Smartphone, going for the latest model of OS is essential and when you can&#8217;t discover one with Jelly Bean, accept Ice Cream Sandwich however examine to see if the producer has promised, has launched or is engaged on releasing a Jelly Bean replace. Probably the most reliable producers in terms of gadget upgrades are HTC, Motorola, Samsung and Google. HTC has essentially the most spectacular Android upgrades of its units however Motorola (run by Android) has a fame of quick upgrades. Notice that producer updates usually include newer widgets, instruments and fixes which are geared toward bettering the general use of the gadget.</p>
<p>One other factor important to note is that it is advisable to have a ROM that able to improved efficiency and putting in apps or further instruments. If you&#8217;re searching for upgrading it then you definitely first want to make sure that personalized ROM can be found for that particular gadget. For instance, Motorola telephones have personalized ROM.</p>
<p><b>3. Consumer Interface or UI</b></p>
<p>Every Android powered gadget consists of a distinct UI. The reason being that with every producer the UI adjustments too. UI is totally different with totally different manufacturers and the options too differ from one producer to a different. If in any case you aren&#8217;t happy with the UI of your Smartphone then you&#8217;ll be able to obtain the web third get together software program like, Zeam, ADW, Go or Launcher Professional.</p>
<p><b>4. Processor</b> <br />Processor is essentially the most important part of your Smartphone. Think about this; if you&#8217;re extra of a gaming fanatic and are hooked on to 3D video games then it is advisable to have a Smartphone with excessive energy CPU processing. For those who use your Smartphone for carrying on average actions then you are able to do with a twin or a single core 1GHZ. A Smartphone powered with quad core processor is sensible to those that bask in heavy gaming and video streaming actions all through the day.</p>
<p>Another details:</p>
<p>• Select a Smartphone that has an excellent inner reminiscence like 4-8 GB when you wish to obtain apps <br />• If you&#8217;re eager about streaming movies and HD content material then a telephone with quicker processor ought to be chosen like a quad core processor <br />• For video calling facility it is advisable to discover a Smartphone with entrance dealing with digicam along with rear digicam <br />• The telephone ought to be backed up with a excessive capability mAh battery in order that it might last more</p>
<p>Holding all of the above given ideas in thoughts will make it easier to select the best-suited Android powered telephone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
