<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>quick &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/quick/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Fero Iris Fast Overview, Options and Specs</title>
		<link>/fero-iris-fast-overview-options-and-specs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iris]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[specs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/fero-iris-quick-review-features-and-specs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Fero Iris is a low-end smartphone with an Iris scanner and 4G LTE built-in. It encompasses a smooth design, the kind that may match [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Fero Iris is a low-end smartphone with an Iris scanner and 4G LTE built-in. It encompasses a smooth design, the kind that may match completely in your pocket and may additionally be nice for dealing with</p>
<p>Within the show division, the telephone spots a 5.0inch IPS LCD which is sweet for viewing textual content and media consumption. The viewing angles must be simply fantastic. We won&#8217;t actually say a lot about working the telephone outside.</p>
<p>Within the efficiency side, it&#8217;s fitted with a MTK6737 Quad Core processor, clocked at 1.3 GHz. That is positively a processor for a low-end smartphone however for essentially the most half, it must be quick sufficient. 1GB of ram and 8GB on-board storage is what this system is delivery with, which isn&#8217;t that a lot of a shock contemplating the value however you possibly can additional increase the storage utilizing a 32GB microSD in case you like that additional house in your telephone. Additionally it is a twin sim smartphone.</p>
<p>It has an 8MP rear digital camera and a 2MP front-facing digital camera that doubles because the Iris scanner. For selfie fanatic, you would possibly need to look elsewhere for that dream entrance dealing with digital camera however in case you&#8217;re eager about excessive degree safety at an inexpensive worth, then that is for you. Though, we&#8217;ve not actually examined the Iris scanner to understand how correct it&#8217;s in recognising your Iris.</p>
<p>2,500mAh is what you get right here which can not me very interesting to heavy customers nevertheless it nonetheless will get the job accomplished. you won&#8217;t need to stray far-off out of your charger although.</p>
<p>Take a look at the complete specs of the Fero Iris under;</p>
<p>Community Connectivity:<br />
<br />WLAN: Wi-Fi 802.11 b/g/n, dual-band, Wi-Fi Direct, hotspot<br />
<br />Community: 2G 850/900/1800/1900 MHz, 3G 2100 MHz, LTE BAND 3/ BAND 7/ BAND 20/ BAND 40<br />
<br />Bluetooth: v4.0</p>
<p>Platform:<br />
<br />OS: Android OS, v6.0 (Marshmallow)<br />
<br />Chipset: MTK6737<br />
<br />CPU: 1.3 GHz, Quad Core</p>
<p>Physique:<br />
<br />Dimension: 144*72*9 mm<br />
<br />Weight: 137 gms<br />
<br />SIM: Twin SIM (Micro-SIM, twin stand-by)<br />
<br />Construct: Titanium based mostly metallic again panel</p>
<p>Show:<br />
<br />Kind: IPS capacitive touchscreen, 16M colours<br />
<br />Dimension: 5 inch<br />
<br />Display Decision: 1280×720 HD</p>
<p>Digicam:<br />
<br />Major: 8 MP, LED flash<br />
<br />Secondary: 2 MP with IRIS Scanner<br />
<br />Multi contact: Sure</p>
<p>Reminiscence:<br />
<br />Card Slot: microSD, as much as 32 GB (devoted slot)<br />
<br />Inner: 8 GB, 1 GB RAM</p>
<p>Sound:<br />
<br />Alert sorts: MIDI/MP3/AAC/WAV<br />
<br />Loudspeaker: Sure<br />
<br />3.5mm jack: Sure</p>
<p>Battery<br />
<br />Capability: 2,500 mAh, Detachable<br />
<br />Kind: Li-Ion</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9800 9mm Thick QWERTY Telephone &#8211; Fast Assessment</title>
		<link>/9800-9mm-thick-qwerty-telephone-fast-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[9800]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[9mm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qwerty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thick]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/9800-9mm-thick-qwerty-phone-quick-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Design is likely one of the components which might be considered to set telephone&#8217;s aside from their opponents. So with this as a information, does [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Design is likely one of the components which might be considered to set telephone&#8217;s aside from their opponents. So with this as a information, does the China made 9800 stand out or fall to the wayside?</p>
<p>The 9800 telephone sports activities an unlucky product mannequin moniker. On this case, the telephone implies that it&#8217;s presupposed to be primarily based on Blackberry&#8217;s 9800. On this case nevertheless, the makers deviated from the usual China copy components, and created a telephone semi unique in design. In truth, one may virtually say that it appears to be like good?</p>
<p>Listed here are the China made 9800&#8217;s primary specs.</p>
<p>At 9mm (.35 inches) thickness, it is likely one of the thinnest telephones to have been launched from China.<br />
<br />Enter is finished by way of its full QWERTY keyboard with raised keys, however the display screen just isn&#8217;t touchscreen succesful.<br />
<br />Together with the battery, this telephone&#8217;s weight is available in at a light-weight 115 grams.<br />
<br />Complete measurements are (LxWxH) 113x56x9mm.<br />
<br />The scale of the display screen is 2.2 inches, has a decision of 240&#215;320, and is created from TFT.<br />
<br />This telephone is unlocked, with entry to any of the 4 GSM bands.<br />
<br />Twin SIM card ports together with twin standby are in-built.<br />
<br />It comes constructed with CE customary PCP plastic for its outer casing.<br />
<br />Acess to the web from the telephones performed by way of WAP 2.0 and GPRS.<br />
<br />Battery life on standby clocks in at 70 to 90 hours on standby.<br />
<br />Extra packages or video games could be put in by downloading and putting in java apps to the java platform.<br />
<br />Extras embrace: a digicam, a camcorder, an eBook reader, an analog TV receiver, a FM radio, and a MP3 participant and MP4 participant.<br />
<br />Multimedia contains: MP3 participant/ MP4 participant/ digicam/ digital camcorder/ eBook reader/ TV with analog reception/ FM radio.<br />
<br />It comes included with a fake leather-based case that features an additional battery for extending the battery life an extra 20 hours on standby.</p>
<p>So listed here are a couple of of my ideas concerning the professionals and cons of the China telephone 9800.</p>
<p>Professionals<br />
<br />The design is actually beautiful with properly rounded edges, a really slim profile, and a weight that&#8217;s subsequent to nothing.<br />
<br />For each defending the telephone and increasing the battery life, the included telephone case is an efficient deal.<br />
<br />Pre-installed apps are each helpful and good to have, and with the flexibility so as to add extra, the telephone can doubtlessly have many extra capabilities.<br />
<br />Although missing in flash, the OS could be very nicely constructed and really straightforward to make use of.<br />
<br />The QWERTY keys are raised from the telephone and are straightforward and intuitive to press.<br />
<br />One would assume {that a} telephone that appears like this might be much more costly than its 73 greenback price ticket.</p>
<p>Cons<br />
<br />Having no entry to sooner web choices (3G or EDGE) means looking is slower than many individuals would really like.<br />
<br />The display screen would have been significantly better if that they had made the dimensions a bit greater.</p>
<p>This telephone, although named after the Blackberry 9800, goes its personal course by way of design, and efficiently made a fairly enticing and really usable telephone.</p>
<p>Value. US$72.84</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nokia 3250 Music Cellphone Fast Assessment</title>
		<link>/nokia-3250-music-cellphone-fast-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3250]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-3250-music-phone-quick-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy because the telephone is delivery subsequent 12 months within the first quarter 2006. Estimated retail value is 350 Euros.</p>
<p>Key options:</p>
<p>&#8211; Helps MP3, M4A, WMA, AAC and eAAC+ music information</p>
<p>&#8211; 3.5mm connector for headphones</p>
<p>&#8211; 262K shade TFT show (decision of 176 x 220 pixels)</p>
<p>&#8211; Stereo FM radio</p>
<p>&#8211; Bluetooth</p>
<p>&#8211; USB 2.0</p>
<p>&#8211; Triband</p>
<p>&#8211; Talktime as much as 3 hours, music listening as much as 10 hours</p>
<p>Feedback and Conclusion</p>
<p>The Nokia 3250 is an good various should you plan to purchase a music telephone. In phrases oif technical specs and options it appears to be considerably higher than the Motorola Rokr iTunes telephone. The Motorola Rokr has USB 1.1 (can take as much as 40 minutes. to switch 100 songs), 512MB TransFlash reminiscence, and the iTunes software program is proscribed to retailer 100 songs. The Nokia 3250 makes use of the Nokia Audio Supervisor software program to switch music information from PC to telephone. This can be a clear drawback in comparison with Motorola that synch with iTunes.</p>
<p>P.S.</p>
<p>Nokia has historically been utilizing the MMC format for storage, however this telephone depends totally on microSD (TransFlash) playing cards. The microSD card relies on TransFlash(TM), which was developed by SanDisk in cooperation with Motorola and is the world&#8217;s smallest flash RAM reminiscence card format.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
