<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>15.6-inch &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/15-6-inch/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>HP Pavilion Dv6-1354US 15.6-Inch Laptop computer &#8211; An Sincere Assessment</title>
		<link>/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-an-sincere-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dv6-1354us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[honest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pavilion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sincere]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-pavilion-dv6-1354us-15-6-inch-laptop-an-honest-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> I&#8217;ve all the time admired HP for producing a wide array of highly effective but inexpensive laptops. Of their effort to provide the very best laptops available in the market, they&#8217;re consistently producing new laptop computer fashions that include quite a lot of new and improved options. The brand new HP Pavilion DV6-1354US is at present one in every of HP&#8217;s newest 15.6-inch laptop computer fashions available in the market. It has a 2.2Ghz Core 2 Duo processor, 4GB of RAM and a bigger 500GB onerous drive. For show, this laptop computer has a 15.6-inch LED back-lit HD display screen (with a 1366 x 768 decision). Then there&#8217;s the set of Altec Lansing audio system that runs on SRS Premium sound expertise. Different specs embody 4 USB ports, a reminiscence card reader, HDMI output, Intel Wifi Hyperlink 100GBN, and rather more</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> The HP Pavilion DV6-1354US sports activities a shiny jet-black casing that&#8217;s properly contrasted with hints of silver. For an edge, the laptop computer is embellished with some round motifs. This mannequin measure at about 14.9 x 10.15 x 1.5 inches and weighs 6.34 kilos, which is in regards to the measurement of a mean 15-inch laptop computer. General, this laptop computer sports activities HP&#8217;s signature skilled and modern look.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> Judging from its specs, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US can be nicely suited to both work or play. It even comes with a tiny (but complete) distant management to allow you to entry quite a lot of multimedia controls from a distance. For graphics rendering, this mannequin makes use of the Intel Graphics Media Accelerator 4500MHD graphics card. The 6-cell batteries on this mannequin can last as long as 4 hours on one cost, which is kind of good for a laptop computer of this measurement (and specs). All in all, the HP Pavilion DV6-1354US 15.6-inch laptop computer is designed for anybody who&#8217;s on the lookout for purposeful and inexpensive full-featured laptop computer. Presently, this laptop computer is promoting for round $699 per unit, which is a good worth for this very competent laptop computer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gateway NV5331u 15.6-Inch Laptop computer Evaluation</title>
		<link>/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-computer-evaluation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.6-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gateway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nv5331u]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/gateway-nv5331u-15-6-inch-laptop-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is at present (on the time of writing) probably the most fashionable 15.6-inch laptops available in the market. That is in all probability attributable to its nice set of specs, good design and cheap price ticket. This mannequin comes with an AMD Turion Extremely M600 dual-core processor (2.4Ghz). Then there&#8217;s the 15.6-inch HD show, ATI Radeon HD 4200 graphics card, and a set of stereo audio system (with Dolby Sound applied sciences). Among the different normal options embody the 8X DVD drive, multi-gesture observe pad, 4 USB ports and a HDMI port.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Though Gateway is known for his or her budget-friendly laptop computer fashions, their desktops and laptops look something however low-cost. Gateway has an awesome design crew and virtually every bit of machine rolled out from them has a really skilled and modern look. The Gateway NV5331u sports activities a classical and curvy design. It measures at 3.97 x 16.6 x 12.4 inches in dimensions and weighs 5.84 kilos.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b> The Gateway NV5331u is mostly an awesome mid-range laptop computer mannequin that&#8217;s nice for leisure of labor functions. The HD graphic card will likely be excellent for anybody who typically watches a number of motion pictures and HD movies on their laptop computer. The 4GB of RAM and the brand new i3 processor additionally allows you to carry out a wide range of heavy duties flawlessly. This mannequin is powered by a 6-cell battery that may last as long as 2 hours and 40 minutes on one full cost. In the meanwhile, the Gateway NV5331u 15.6-inch laptop computer is retailing for simply round $699 per unit, which is a superb worth for this set of specs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
