<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>today &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/today/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Android Telephones Right now</title>
		<link>/android-telephones-right-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[now]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[right]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[today]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-phones-today/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Android is a cell phone working system developed by the search supplier Google. Used on all kinds of sensible telephones, Android is at the moment [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Android is a cell phone working system developed by the search supplier Google. Used on all kinds of sensible telephones, Android is at the moment one of the best promoting cellular working system on this planet. Android is an open supply OS, letting anybody develop their very own software program (similar to functions or video games) to be run on Android platforms. The Android OS can be utilized in pill computer systems, with the most recent model being Android 3.0. Whereas the Android OS has been in use since 2008, common updates and assist for Google retains Android the modern system it&#8217;s right this moment.</p>
<p>Cell phones working the Android working system all have the same set of options supplied by the OS. The Android OS is made to be run on sensible telephones, telephones which might run a wide range of Java based mostly functions that give the telephone added performance. Along with fundamental telephone and textual content/media messaging service, Android telephones have a wide range of net based mostly providers and functions. Android telephones are related with the proprietor&#8217;s Google account, permitting entry to Gmail and Google Calendar in addition to a wide range of different functions. Along with wi-fi web and Bluetooth connectivity, Android telephones permit for wi-fi tethering &#8211; utilizing the telephone as a modem to attach a laptop computer laptop to the web. All android telephones permit for streaming video, with the most recent fashions ready to hook up with the 4G community and video conferencing utilizing Google Discuss. Probably the most well-known facet of the Android platform is entry to the Android Market. Just like the Apple App Retailer, the Android Market permits customers to obtain functions and video games for his or her telephone, a lot of that are free.</p>
<p>The primary Android telephone to be launched was the G1, developed by HTC and launched in 2008. Working Android 1.0, this telephone had lots of the options at the moment present in Android telephones, together with synchronization with the person&#8217;s Google account and the Android Marketplace for downloading telephone apps. Since then, there have been many updates to the Android working system &#8211; main updates are given the identify of a dessert. The most recent model of Android for cell phones is Android 2.3.4, Gingerbread. Designed to be used on 4G telephones with elevated efficiency and pace, Gingerbread gives higher video playback and assist for entrance going through cameras for video conferencing.</p>
<p>The Android working system permits telephones to be produced by many producers. With the present technology of 4G telephones, the main producers are Motorola and Samsung. Motorola is the creator of the Droid line of telephones &#8211; a collection that have been made fashionable by their availability with Verizon service in the US. The Droid X2, the most recent mannequin within the Droid collection, features a multi-touch interface, 8 GB of reminiscence together with an 8 GB micro SD card for storage, and an 8 megapixel digital camera with inbuilt video recorder. Samsung is the opposite main producer of Android telephones and have collaborated with Google on the Nexus S. The Nexus was the primary telephone to make use of the brand new Gingerbread working system and included a strong processor and 512 MB of RAM. The Nexus S has 16 GB of inside storage and may entry the 4G community utilizing a Dash service plan. Different firms similar to HTC produce Android telephones as effectively, giving the buyer all kinds of selections when attempting to decide on one of the best Android telephone for his or her wants.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
