<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>mc118ll/a &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mc118ll-a/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>15-inch Laptop computer Critiques &#8211; Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch Laptop computer</title>
		<link>/15-inch-laptop-computer-critiques-apple-macbook-professional-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop-computer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[15.4-inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[critiques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macbook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mc118ll/a]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/15-inch-laptop-reviews-apple-macbook-pro-mc118ll-a-15-4-inch-laptop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Specs: The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Specs:</b> The brand new era of Apple MacBooks have acquired raving opinions from critics all over the world and obtain many Editor&#8217;s Alternative Awards from varied distinguished expertise publications. One in every of their favourite fashions was the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A 15.4-inch laptop computer.</p>
<p>The Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A has a 2.53Ghz Intel Core 2 processor. It comes with 4GB of DDR3 RAM and a 250GB onerous drive. It runs on the Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard working system and has a 15.40inch TFT display. It&#8217;s a LED back-lit and shiny display, with a 1440 x 900 decision. For graphics, it makes use of the NVIDIA GeForce 8400M graphics card.</p>
<p><b>Design:</b> Like the brand new era of Apple computer systems, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is sleeker than the older fashions and have an uni-body aluminum casing. It&#8217;s 14.3 x 9.8 x 0.9 inches in dimensions and 5.5 kilos in weight. General, it has a clear look, with the DVD SuperDrive on the correct facet and all of the connectors/ports on the left.</p>
<p><b>Options &amp; Efficiency:</b>Though you will get an everyday Home windows OS laptop computer available in the market with comparable specs with a lesser value, let me simply say straight out that the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A performs significantly better than many different common laptops of its class.</p>
<p>For starters, the inbuilt battery within the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A can last as long as 7 hours on a single cost. We will likely be fortunate to get 3 hours out of an everyday laptop computer of this measurement. Working graphics &#8216;heavy&#8217; functions and multitasking was additionally a dream on this mannequin. The efficiency speeds in our exams have been manner higher than any of the non-Apple laptops that we now have examined. At the moment, the Apple MacBook Professional MC118LL/A is priced at round $1699 every, an excellent value for a laptop computer of this stature.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
