<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>music &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/music/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Newest Android Telephones Providing Hello-Fi and Good Music</title>
		<link>/the-newest-android-telephones-providing-hello-fi-and-good-music/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hello-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hi-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[newest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[providing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-latest-android-phones-offering-hi-fi-and-smart-music/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their fundamental theme. Their motto for the Indian viewers is to Play Hello-fi and Stay Good. The providing was one-of-its-kind within the nation and proved to be a boon for music lovers. Addressing the mid-range market, the manufacturing firms launched music-based android telephones within the worth vary of INR 15,000 to twenty,000.</p>
<p><strong>Comfortable Listening on Funtouch OS</strong></p>
<p>The collection was designed solely for Indian clients to expertise Hello-fi music within the thinnest doable metallic physique with a customized Funtouch OS. These fastidiously crafted, smooth and light-weight handsets are full of specs to enrich the enthusiastic, energetic and passionate Indian youth of at the moment.</p>
<p><strong>Limitless Downloads with Expandable Reminiscence</strong></p>
<p>To supply sooner pace that matches the superior sound high quality of those gadgets, they&#8217;re geared up with a Funtouch 2.1 (based mostly on Android Lollipop 5.0) Working System. They&#8217;re powered by a 64-bit Octa-Core Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a space for storing of 16GB ROM and 2GB RAM expandable as much as 128GB. The expansive storage capability helps you to obtain limitless music, video games and films, and permits you to surf and share with ease.</p>
<p><strong>Go on with the Lengthy-Lasting Battery</strong></p>
<p>The musical expertise is healthier when you might have a long-lasting 2300mAh battery with stamina mode, permitting your android telephone to go on and on for fairly lengthy. Including to the delight is an ultra-slim and curvy physique that blends completely with its eagle eye engineering precision.</p>
<p><strong>Double Twin Audio Audio system</strong></p>
<p>The handsets have double twin sound programs together with two skilled degree 5 magnetic circuit audio system to choose up the slightest of sounds and supply minimal distortion. For the reason that producers are devoted to making sure one of the best sound high quality, they&#8217;ve a novel audio speaker at each ends of the telephone. Simply 0.4mm in diameter, the 140 dots speaker creates an final sound expertise.</p>
<p><strong>Get rid of Disturbing Noises with Professional-Stage Audio Chip</strong></p>
<p>One other characteristic that makes these telephones good is the skilled degree Hello-fi chip. It might play tunes over 105dB and beneath -95dB with the least doable sound distortion. It might produce high-fidelity high quality with a twin chip audio decoding programme to reinforce your general sound expertise. To make the expertise even higher, android telephone manufacturing firms are finishing up analysis and growth in areas associated to enhancement of audio high quality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nokia 3250 Music Cellphone Fast Assessment</title>
		<link>/nokia-3250-music-cellphone-fast-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3250]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-3250-music-phone-quick-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You would say it´s a funds model of the N91 and aimed for the mass markets. Nokia 3250 is not going to preserve Santa busy because the telephone is delivery subsequent 12 months within the first quarter 2006. Estimated retail value is 350 Euros.</p>
<p>Key options:</p>
<p>&#8211; Helps MP3, M4A, WMA, AAC and eAAC+ music information</p>
<p>&#8211; 3.5mm connector for headphones</p>
<p>&#8211; 262K shade TFT show (decision of 176 x 220 pixels)</p>
<p>&#8211; Stereo FM radio</p>
<p>&#8211; Bluetooth</p>
<p>&#8211; USB 2.0</p>
<p>&#8211; Triband</p>
<p>&#8211; Talktime as much as 3 hours, music listening as much as 10 hours</p>
<p>Feedback and Conclusion</p>
<p>The Nokia 3250 is an good various should you plan to purchase a music telephone. In phrases oif technical specs and options it appears to be considerably higher than the Motorola Rokr iTunes telephone. The Motorola Rokr has USB 1.1 (can take as much as 40 minutes. to switch 100 songs), 512MB TransFlash reminiscence, and the iTunes software program is proscribed to retailer 100 songs. The Nokia 3250 makes use of the Nokia Audio Supervisor software program to switch music information from PC to telephone. This can be a clear drawback in comparison with Motorola that synch with iTunes.</p>
<p>P.S.</p>
<p>Nokia has historically been utilizing the MMC format for storage, however this telephone depends totally on microSD (TransFlash) playing cards. The microSD card relies on TransFlash(TM), which was developed by SanDisk in cooperation with Motorola and is the world&#8217;s smallest flash RAM reminiscence card format.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
