<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tricks &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/tricks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Android Video games &#8211; Tricks to Get the Better of It</title>
		<link>/android-video-games-tricks-to-get-the-better-of-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[better]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[get]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tricks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-games-tips-to-get-the-best-of-it/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you want to kill your free time when the one firm you have got is your Android cellphone? Do you know that Android video [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to kill your free time when the one firm you have got is your Android cellphone? Do you know that Android video games are essentially the most attention-grabbing and enjoyable stuffed stuff to cram your cellphone with? Undergo this text to know extra about these video games and their enjoyable elements.</p>
<p>Android video games are diversified into many classes; informational, instructional, capturing video games, puzzles, sports activities, racing, augmented actuality video games, location-based video games and extra. All these varieties can be found for each excessive finish and low-end Android telephones.</p>
<p>There are low specification video games for these low-end fashions so as to take pleasure in them in your finances telephones as nicely. This contains the lesser graphics content material video games that doesn&#8217;t take a lot of your house. It&#8217;s appropriate for Android telephones with low GPUs and smaller display dimension as nicely.</p>
<p>Each freemium and premium video games can be found within the shops. Premium are paid-for video games and freemium is the free video games which regularly comprise in-app buy at sure ranges. So it&#8217;s advisable to observe if somebody aside from you (like your child) is utilizing your cellphone; do not click on on these buy choices with out information.</p>
<p>To take pleasure in the perfect excessive graphics and well-designed gameplay, it&#8217;s higher to get a high-end mannequin with a much bigger display and good GPU. Even you may take pleasure in these high-quality gaming results by growing the efficiency of your low spec, finances Android telephones.</p>
<p>First and the best methodology to extend your low-end smartphone efficiency is by killing the functions which can be operating within the background earlier than you begin the sport. You should utilize a number of activity killer functions for this, as nicely. A lot of the Android telephones comprise many functions which can be of no use to a median person. These functions may be disabled which in flip will increase the efficiency of your cellphone.</p>
<p>All you might want to do is, go to settings, choose &#8216;apps&#8217;, then choose the functions to be disabled and click on the &#8216;disable&#8217; button. All these functions may be enabled sooner or later if you happen to want them. Normally, the uninstalled functions or your web browser usually leaves behind junk recordsdata. These cache information usually reduces your cellphone efficiency. To clear these information, go to &#8216;settings&#8217; and click on &#8216;storage possibility&#8217;, then choose the cached information button and press okay.</p>
<p>All the time go for a category 10 SD card to extend your cellphone&#8217;s gaming efficiency. Utilizing these SD playing cards will enhance the learn and write velocity and therefore reduces the loading time and different lags that any excessive graphics recreation would demand. These rooted Android telephones have extra amenities to extend their efficiency. The background activity killer functions work to their fullest provided that they&#8217;re in a rooted Android model. Seeder software program may be put in in a rooted Android cellphone, which reduces the lag throughout switching between functions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
