<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>e72 &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/e72/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Nokia E72 Cell Telephone Evaluate</title>
		<link>/nokia-e72-cell-telephone-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e72]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-e72-mobile-phone-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Nokia E72 is an improve to the earlier E71 collection which features a quicker processor, extra reminiscence and higher digital camera. The E72 doubles [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Nokia E72 is an improve to the earlier E71 collection which features a quicker processor, extra reminiscence and higher digital camera. The E72 doubles the reminiscence of E71 to 250MB. The digital camera has been upgraded to 5MP up from 3.2megapixels from its predecessor. The efficiency of the E72 is fairly spectacular on condition that it now features a quicker 600MHz processor versus the 369Mhz processor within the E71. Connectivity capabilities embody 3G, WiFi, Bluetooth and GPS.</p>
<p>The E72 has a 320X240 show which encompasses a mild sensor which adjusts display screen brightness primarily based on ambient mild.</p>
<p>The total QUERTY keyboard is straightforward to make use of. The buttons have simply the correct amount of tactile suggestions. One other function is that within the centre of the D-pad is an optical trackpad or Optical Navi key as Nokia calls it. The trackpad would detect finger swipes throughout its floor and interprets this into menu navigation or strikes a cursor when viewing a webpage. This function is much like the one in Samsung Omnia and the Blackberry Daring.</p>
<p>The next objects are included customary within the field:- a USB cable, AC adaptor, a wi-fi stereo headset, a delicate cleansing material, a 4GB micro SD card, a carrying case, strap a software program CD and reference materials. It additionally has wonderful e-mail integration with Gmail, Yahoo mail and in addition has help for POP and IMAP4 along with Nokia Messaging, ActiveSync, Lotus Notes Traveler and Mail for Change.</p>
<p>The included internet browser referred to as Nokia MiniMap may be very competent. There are numerous show choices comparable to full display screen mode and web page overview mode. It additionally helps flash which permits you amongst different issues to observe YouTube movies.</p>
<p>The E72 additionally comes with a set of productiveness software. You possibly can view and edit Microsoft Workplace information utilizing the Quickoffice software. Different functions included are a enterprise card scanner, a file supervisor, a dictionary, a PDF viewer, a zipper supervisor, a dictionary, a calculator and extra. The consumer may also be capable to obtain free or paid functions from Nokia&#8217;s Ovi Retailer.</p>
<p>This cellphone is not only all enterprise; it additionally features a media participant which helps WMA, AAC, AAC, eAAC, MP3 and AMR-NB information. Along with this it additionally helps podcasts, web radio and in addition has an built-in FM tuner. For video playback, the E72 consists of the Actual Participant software program which helps WMV, RV, MP4 and H.263/3GPP video information. The Nokia E72 retails at round RM1115.00 in Malaysia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
