<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>m15x &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/m15x/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Laptop computer Evaluate &#8211; Dell Alienware M15x</title>
		<link>/laptop-computer-evaluate-dell-alienware-m15x/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alienware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[laptop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[m15x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/laptop-review-dell-alienware-m15x/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A laptop computer devoted for die-hard followers of utmost gaming, the Dell Alienware M15x often known as the Space 51 M15x. It is really a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A laptop computer devoted for die-hard followers of utmost gaming, the Dell Alienware M15x often known as the Space 51 M15x. It is really a revamp of the outdated Space 51 M15x laptop computer that first got here out with the Intel Core 2 Excessive X9000 2.8GHz (6MB Cache, 800MHz FSB) powering its system. This processor has a excessive potential because it made different gaming laptops seem like as sluggish as a turtle. It additionally has the Dell turbo enhance know-how that enhances its processing unit.</p>
<p>At the moment, the Dell Alienware M15x comes with three processor choices &#8211; the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i3 cell processor for laptops is the primary stage of Intel&#8217;s new processor household, adopted by the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 cell processor mannequin and the brand new Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 processor. The Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 is the most recent and strongest processor of all time, however the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 will not be going to lose lots in processing prowess.</p>
<p>This Dell Alienware M15x laptop computer with Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 has two prototypes: the Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 540M 2.53GHz (3.06GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache) and the Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 430M 2.26GHz (2.53GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache). Each CPUs run on two cores, however might outrun different twin core processors, together with its predecessors. That&#8217;s the reason, even with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5, this alienware laptop computer is taken into account unusually massive and highly effective within the gaming world and is poised to turn out to be one of many favorites of hardcore avid gamers with budgets not sufficient to accumulate the same laptop computer with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7 in it.</p>
<p>The Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 processor on the Dell Alienware M15x function: Intel&reg; Turbo Increase Know-how, Intel&reg; Hyper-Threading Know-how and helps Enhanced Intel SpeedStep&reg; Know-how. This method permits any Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 processor to run at a sooner clock charge whereas doing large processing duties.</p>
<p>To go with its pace and energy, this Dell Alienware Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 model is loaded with 4GB to a most of 8GB DDR3 RAM with FSB of 1066MHz and 1333Mhz respectively. This ensures very easy efficiency even when accessing memory-hungry purposes. One other vital recognition is the show rendering heavy graphics purposes turns into a breeze with its devoted graphics card because the Dell Alienware M15x is put in with 1GB NVIDIA&reg; GeForce&reg; GTX 260M or an non-obligatory 512MB NVIDIA&reg; GeForce&reg; GT 240M video card.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x Intel&reg; Core(TM) i5 model is out there with a gamer-like chassis and there are three colours to select from &#8212; Nebula Crimson, Cosmic Black and Lunar Shadow. It could actually retailer as much as 250 GB of digital information and if storage will not be sufficient, the laptop computer has a BD-ROM/DVD/-RW drive to burn information with.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 model additionally comes with a full HD show with a decision of 1920 x 1080 pixels &#8211; preferrred not just for gaming but in addition for multimedia expertise.</p>
<p><strong>Specs:</strong></p>
<p>Central Processing Unit</p>
<ul>
<li>Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 540M 2.53GHz (3.06GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache)</li>
<li>Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 430M 2.26GHz (2.53GHz Turbo Mode, 3MB Cache)</li>
</ul>
<p>Learn Entry Reminiscence</p>
<ul>
<li>4 GB</li>
</ul>
<p>Storage Drive</p>
<ul>
<li>SATA 250GB Onerous Drive 7,200 rpm</li>
</ul>
<p>Optical Drive</p>
<ul>
<li>BD-ROM/DVD /-RW</li>
</ul>
<p>Show Dimension</p>
<ul>
<li>15.6 inches</li>
</ul>
<p>Native Decision</p>
<ul>
<li>1920 x 1080</li>
</ul>
<p>Dimension</p>
<ul>
<li>Top: 1.92 inches x Width: 14.88 inches x 12.15 inches</li>
</ul>
<p>Graphics Card</p>
<ul>
<li>Nvidia GeForce GTX 260M with 1 GB VRAM</li>
</ul>
<p>Weight</p>
<ul>
<li>9.0 kilos</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Professionals</strong></p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x with Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 only a notch much less highly effective than the one with the Intel&reg; Core(TM) i7.</p>
<p>The Dell Alienware M15x with Intel&reg; CoreTM i5 is actually admirable with its superior graphics, full HD show and a Blu-Ray prepared drive.</p>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<p>This Alienware comes with an Inside Excessive-Definition 5.1 Encompass Sound Audio system that delivers sound adequately. With a weight of 9 kilos, some individuals may discover the Dell Alienware M15x too heavy. This does not have an HDMI port, solely a firewire port.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
