<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>telephones &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/telephones/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Methods to Unfreeze Your Android and iOS Telephones</title>
		<link>/methods-to-unfreeze-your-android-and-ios-telephones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[methods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unfreeze]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[your]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/how-to-unfreeze-your-android-and-ios-phones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Your Smartphone just isn&#8217;t precisely your pc even after you utilize it for varied functions. Nonetheless nonetheless there are some widespread troubles that you simply [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your Smartphone just isn&#8217;t precisely your pc even after you utilize it for varied functions. Nonetheless nonetheless there are some widespread troubles that you simply may undergo like frozen telephone. Even if you&#8217;re utilizing an iOS gadget or an Android primarily based telephone the issue is widespread. This can be very annoying if you undergo such hassle and infrequently you have no idea what to do. Listed here are just a few ideas for unfreezing your iPhone and your Android telephone.</p>
<p><b>Methods to unfreeze your iPhone</b></p>
<p>• Usually freezes occur attributable to app hassle that leaves your telephone frozen. Right now you must force-close. If you&#8217;re utilizing iOS 7 then double faucet on Residence button to disclose app switcher inside the multitask bar, then scroll left to find the app that&#8217;s frozen, swipe as much as fling it off the display. For these utilizing iOS 6 Residence button-&gt; App Switcher-&gt;maintain down on the App icon and when it wriggles faucet the &#8211; button to close it down.</p>
<p>• In case your iPhone goes bonkers and wouldn&#8217;t allow you to entry app switcher then the most suitable choice that you&#8217;ve is to restart your telephone. Press and maintain the Sleep Button positioned on the high of your telephone until you see Slide to Energy Off slider seem. Slide to proper to energy down the telephone. To energy again your telephone you then must press down the Sleep Button once more until the Apple emblem seems.</p>
<p>• If you&#8217;re dealing with a state of affairs the place your iPhone is non-responsive to your faucets then you must force-restart it. Press and maintain down the Sleep button + Residence Button until you possibly can see the Apple emblem on the display. After a couple of minutes your iPhone can be up and operating as earlier than.</p>
<p>• One other method of getting previous your freezing iPhone is to go for manufacturing facility reset or the default settings. Nonetheless, take warning as you may lose all of your knowledge in your telephone so it&#8217;s advisable to take an information backup previous to making an attempt manufacturing facility reset. Settings-&gt;Common-&gt;Reset-&gt;Reset All Settings. Now as quickly as you&#8217;re by way of with all this your telephone will return to the manufacturing facility settings and every thing together with your apps and extra software program can be wiped off.</p>
<p>• You may also go for iTunes restore by plugging your telephone by way of USB into your system. A listing of gadgets will seem from which you must choose your telephone. Abstract tab-&gt;Restore iPhone possibility, a backup of all of the settings will start. As quickly because it finishes obtain and set up contemporary iOS after which apply the default setting. To revive your knowledge go to Backups -&gt; Restore Backup.</p>
<p><b>Methods to unfreeze your Android telephone?</b></p>
<p><b>Pressure-close an app:</b></p>
<p>• Initially you must drive shut the app that&#8217;s inflicting hassle, Swipe to disclose the tab-&gt;Choose the app you need to kill by tapping the cease button. If you&#8217;re not in a position to view the app within the given listing then go to the higher proper nook and search for Present Cached Processes.</p>
<p>• You possibly can even try a drive shutdown maintain and press down energy button + quantity up button until the display turns off. Energy on by urgent the ability button. If you&#8217;re having hassle utilizing the quantity up button then use the quantity down button.</p>
<p>• In case your Android has a detachable battery then you possibly can take away the again cowl of your telephone and pull out the battery. After just a few seconds substitute the battery and shut the battery cowl, now flip again your telephone. Nonetheless, bear in mind to make use of this methodology when anything just isn&#8217;t working in unfreezing your Android Cellphone.</p>
<p>• One other method of unfreezing your telephone is to check out the strategy of manufacturing facility reset. Restoring your telephone again to the manufacturing facility default may provide help to eliminate the telephone freeze hassle. Nonetheless, earlier than you start the method of manufacturing facility reset you must take a backup of your telephone by connecting it to your system by way of USB.</p>
<p>• For manufacturing facility reset go to Settings-&gt;Backup-&gt;Reset and find Manufacturing facility knowledge reset, faucet it. A affirmation is required for continuing additional. After you might have confirmed the method of manufacturing facility reset will start.</p>
<p>Enterprise the above-mentioned steps will make sure that you rid your telephone of the telephone freeze hassle. Nonetheless, if it once more occurs then you must get in contact with a tech professional.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Newest Android Telephones Providing Hello-Fi and Good Music</title>
		<link>/the-newest-android-telephones-providing-hello-fi-and-good-music/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hello-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hi-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[newest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[providing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-latest-android-phones-offering-hi-fi-and-smart-music/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their fundamental theme. Their motto for the Indian viewers is to Play Hello-fi and Stay Good. The providing was one-of-its-kind within the nation and proved to be a boon for music lovers. Addressing the mid-range market, the manufacturing firms launched music-based android telephones within the worth vary of INR 15,000 to twenty,000.</p>
<p><strong>Comfortable Listening on Funtouch OS</strong></p>
<p>The collection was designed solely for Indian clients to expertise Hello-fi music within the thinnest doable metallic physique with a customized Funtouch OS. These fastidiously crafted, smooth and light-weight handsets are full of specs to enrich the enthusiastic, energetic and passionate Indian youth of at the moment.</p>
<p><strong>Limitless Downloads with Expandable Reminiscence</strong></p>
<p>To supply sooner pace that matches the superior sound high quality of those gadgets, they&#8217;re geared up with a Funtouch 2.1 (based mostly on Android Lollipop 5.0) Working System. They&#8217;re powered by a 64-bit Octa-Core Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a space for storing of 16GB ROM and 2GB RAM expandable as much as 128GB. The expansive storage capability helps you to obtain limitless music, video games and films, and permits you to surf and share with ease.</p>
<p><strong>Go on with the Lengthy-Lasting Battery</strong></p>
<p>The musical expertise is healthier when you might have a long-lasting 2300mAh battery with stamina mode, permitting your android telephone to go on and on for fairly lengthy. Including to the delight is an ultra-slim and curvy physique that blends completely with its eagle eye engineering precision.</p>
<p><strong>Double Twin Audio Audio system</strong></p>
<p>The handsets have double twin sound programs together with two skilled degree 5 magnetic circuit audio system to choose up the slightest of sounds and supply minimal distortion. For the reason that producers are devoted to making sure one of the best sound high quality, they&#8217;ve a novel audio speaker at each ends of the telephone. Simply 0.4mm in diameter, the 140 dots speaker creates an final sound expertise.</p>
<p><strong>Get rid of Disturbing Noises with Professional-Stage Audio Chip</strong></p>
<p>One other characteristic that makes these telephones good is the skilled degree Hello-fi chip. It might play tunes over 105dB and beneath -95dB with the least doable sound distortion. It might produce high-fidelity high quality with a twin chip audio decoding programme to reinforce your general sound expertise. To make the expertise even higher, android telephone manufacturing firms are finishing up analysis and growth in areas associated to enhancement of audio high quality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Android Telephones Right now</title>
		<link>/android-telephones-right-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[now]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[right]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[today]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-phones-today/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Android is a cell phone working system developed by the search supplier Google. Used on all kinds of sensible telephones, Android is at the moment [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Android is a cell phone working system developed by the search supplier Google. Used on all kinds of sensible telephones, Android is at the moment one of the best promoting cellular working system on this planet. Android is an open supply OS, letting anybody develop their very own software program (similar to functions or video games) to be run on Android platforms. The Android OS can be utilized in pill computer systems, with the most recent model being Android 3.0. Whereas the Android OS has been in use since 2008, common updates and assist for Google retains Android the modern system it&#8217;s right this moment.</p>
<p>Cell phones working the Android working system all have the same set of options supplied by the OS. The Android OS is made to be run on sensible telephones, telephones which might run a wide range of Java based mostly functions that give the telephone added performance. Along with fundamental telephone and textual content/media messaging service, Android telephones have a wide range of net based mostly providers and functions. Android telephones are related with the proprietor&#8217;s Google account, permitting entry to Gmail and Google Calendar in addition to a wide range of different functions. Along with wi-fi web and Bluetooth connectivity, Android telephones permit for wi-fi tethering &#8211; utilizing the telephone as a modem to attach a laptop computer laptop to the web. All android telephones permit for streaming video, with the most recent fashions ready to hook up with the 4G community and video conferencing utilizing Google Discuss. Probably the most well-known facet of the Android platform is entry to the Android Market. Just like the Apple App Retailer, the Android Market permits customers to obtain functions and video games for his or her telephone, a lot of that are free.</p>
<p>The primary Android telephone to be launched was the G1, developed by HTC and launched in 2008. Working Android 1.0, this telephone had lots of the options at the moment present in Android telephones, together with synchronization with the person&#8217;s Google account and the Android Marketplace for downloading telephone apps. Since then, there have been many updates to the Android working system &#8211; main updates are given the identify of a dessert. The most recent model of Android for cell phones is Android 2.3.4, Gingerbread. Designed to be used on 4G telephones with elevated efficiency and pace, Gingerbread gives higher video playback and assist for entrance going through cameras for video conferencing.</p>
<p>The Android working system permits telephones to be produced by many producers. With the present technology of 4G telephones, the main producers are Motorola and Samsung. Motorola is the creator of the Droid line of telephones &#8211; a collection that have been made fashionable by their availability with Verizon service in the US. The Droid X2, the most recent mannequin within the Droid collection, features a multi-touch interface, 8 GB of reminiscence together with an 8 GB micro SD card for storage, and an 8 megapixel digital camera with inbuilt video recorder. Samsung is the opposite main producer of Android telephones and have collaborated with Google on the Nexus S. The Nexus was the primary telephone to make use of the brand new Gingerbread working system and included a strong processor and 512 MB of RAM. The Nexus S has 16 GB of inside storage and may entry the 4G community utilizing a Dash service plan. Different firms similar to HTC produce Android telephones as effectively, giving the buyer all kinds of selections when attempting to decide on one of the best Android telephone for his or her wants.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cellular Telephones: A Vogue Assertion</title>
		<link>/cellular-telephones-a-vogue-assertion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assertion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion,]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[statement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vogue]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/mobile-phones-a-fashion-statement/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Earlier cell phones was once cumbersome handsets with costly service plans and excessive name prices. Folks used to point out off their cell phones to [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Earlier <b>cell phones</b> was once cumbersome handsets with costly service plans and excessive name prices. Folks used to point out off their cell phones to the world to realize consideration or to only present that they don&#8217;t seem to be left behind. Right this moment, cell phones have grow to be extra of a necessity and an extension of your private fashion. Cellphones at the moment are thought of as an announcement of who you might be your individuality, persona and even a standing image.</p>
<p>The look and the design of a cell phone are the very first thing that attraction to you whereas shopping for a cell phone. The fashion definition began with Nokia 6600 handset which other than having nice appears to be like, can be filled with options like bluetooth/infrared, actual one participant, exterior reminiscence slot, VGA digicam and host of different options.</p>
<p>Development acutely aware folks stress extra on the design than options. The design issue actually shapes up the client&#8217;s determination making course of whereas shopping for a cell phone. However clients today additionally demand the newest options of their handsets. The color of your cellphone can be measured whereas taking fashion into consideration. The color black makes a trend assertion that&#8217;s classically stylish and complex. You possibly can even personalize your cellphone with completely different coloration schemes. At on-line cellular outlets, you possibly can assessment completely different service supplier choices, discover low-cost cell phone offers having the newest <a target="_new" rel="nofollow noopener" href="http://www.mobilerainbow.co.uk/"><b>mobile phones</b></a> and a spread of cellular enhancements associated to your new cellphone. A number of the newest cell phones place focus extra on performance and ship a super mixture of mobility, multimedia functions, and enterprise options.</p>
<p>So now that <b>cell phones</b> have grow to be a will need to have trend accent with an ever blossoming multitude of features, what are you ready for? The most recent telephones with enticing offers are ready so that you can be explored.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nokia 5610 XpressMusic Cell Evaluation &#8211; Nokia Goals For The Walkman Telephones</title>
		<link>/nokia-5610-xpressmusic-cell-evaluation-nokia-goals-for-the-walkman-telephones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5610]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aims]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[walkman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xpressmusic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/nokia-5610-xpressmusic-mobile-review-nokia-aims-for-the-walkman-phones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Music gamers in telephones have, because the introduction of the Motorola ROKR, grow to be a normal characteristic throughout the board. What was once one [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Music gamers in telephones have, because the introduction of the Motorola ROKR, grow to be a normal characteristic throughout the board. What was once one thing that differentiated one cellphone and producer from one other is now a characteristic that each cellphone put available on the market (apart from these which might be &#8220;free telephones should you join a contract&#8221;) appears to have.</p>
<p>Trying to distinguish in your music participant has, for the longest time, been akin to making an attempt to distinguish your vehicle primarily based on the stylishness of your cup holders. With their 5610 slider-form issue cell phone, Nokia manages to distinguish on the mixing of the music participant with the remainder of the cellphone.</p>
<p>The important thing to it is a set of capabilities referred to as the Navislide, which is used to manage the musical capabilities of the cellphone with a single thumb-flick on the controls &#8211; the Nokia 5610&#8217;s total keypad is relatively properly designed, with the keys giving numerous good tactile suggestions and a fast response curve. With the general development of the machine, all the package deal is properly constructed &#8211; suits within the hand, can be utilized one handed simply, and it is properly strong.</p>
<p>However again to the Navislide &#8211; should you&#8217;ve ever used an iPod thumb-wheel, the Navislide is like falling off a log. It is simple, and adjustable, and remarkably simple to make use of. Rock it left to make use of the music participant, rock it proper to make use of the in-built FM radio, rock it up for the subsequent observe or station, or down for the earlier one. It is a remarkably simple machine to get used to.</p>
<p>That slider bar can also be fairly useful when utilizing the menus for the opposite capabilities on the cellphone. First a be aware on the display: It is a easy truism of how a lot these gadgets have matured because the market has grown; this display would have been thought of beautiful and excessive finish two years in the past; it is crisp, vivid and simple to learn; the display is QVA decision, and fairly ok for watching video. (Certainly, the cellular has a small VGA digital camera for doing video phone calls.)</p>
<p>The menu system is properly laid out, with 4 configuration choices obtainable, and it is clear that Nokia is leveraging their improvement efforts into the System 40 working methods properly. The D-pad is totally person configurable, and offers you loads of choices for utilizing the cellphone fluidly and simply.</p>
<p>As a cellphone, it is a full GSM/HSDPA 3G community cellphone, and may have its firmware up to date wirelessly, no have to hook it as much as a desktop laptop. Its inboard contact system can retailer 2000 contacts, and there is full lower and paste between all functions on the cellphone. (In earnest, as soon as you&#8217;ve got used lower and paste on a cellphone, the subsequent query is &#8220;Why did this take so lengthy to get carried out&#8230;&#8221;)</p>
<p>Lastly, the 5610 has a wonderful 3.2 megapixel digital camera with an built-in LED flash and respectable autof ocus. Whereas it isn&#8217;t going to make you surrender your devoted digital digital camera as a pictures software, it is greater than sufficient (and borderline overkill) for one thing to take fast snapshots. Once more, Nokia&#8217;s consideration to the person interface makes the digital camera a dream to make use of.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
