<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>2015 &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/2015/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Finest Android Video games Of 2015</title>
		<link>/the-finest-android-video-games-of-2015/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-best-android-games-of-2015/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Typically, you get solely what you pay for within the sense that you simply get some good video games for cash. You could find a [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Typically, you get solely what you pay for within the sense that you simply get some good video games for cash. You could find a number of incredible video games on Android, however you need to spend a bit cash and you&#8217;ll take pleasure in a number of video games in your cell phone. You may merely obtain a few of the greatest Android video games and begin enjoying them. Listed below are a few of the greatest Android video games of 2015.</p>
<p>Threes!</p>
<p>A merely ingenious recreation that&#8217;s simple to play, however that&#8217;s tough to grasp, Threes has a 4 by 4 grid and a variety of sliding tiles for the instruments that you&#8217;d be utilizing to play the sport. Every of those numbered tiles might be mixed solely with one other kind of tile. At this level, it turns into a single tile and their values add as much as its constituents. The first concept behind the sport is to maintain enjoying it. The sound results, music, and so forth. are merely the icing on the cake.</p>
<p>Monument Valley</p>
<p>There are lots of debates on whether or not Android video games might be creative and Monument Valley checks the &#8220;artwork&#8221; field. It&#8217;s a delicate and a lovely arcade journey recreation that options the makes an attempt of a lovely princess to discover monuments. Monument Valley has been crafted rigorously, thoughtfully, and the expertise all through is reflective. The structure strikes as you drag and spin the elements.</p>
<p>Drop7</p>
<p>Every so often, a puzzle recreation seems that might not merely allow you to go of it. You&#8217;ll work with puzzles on this recreation, though you would want to drop discs and will the variety of any disc not match with the disc depend in its column or row, it might explode. If you&#8217;d like the face quantity revealed, then it&#8217;s best to make the grey blocks have two adjoining explosions. It is without doubt one of the greatest Android puzzles round.</p>
<p>Indignant birds &#8211; Star Wars II</p>
<p>Right here is one thing for ardent players of Indignant Birds. The sequel to Indignant Birds &#8211; Star Wars I improves on the design concepts of the sport. The sequel to the sport comes with character packs and degree branching that permit you to swap and check out totally different methods. This recreation is an ideal match for the followers of Darth Maul. If you happen to thought that the titular birds had been method too indignant, then you will have the chance to get revenge on them proper now with this Android recreation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
