<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>probook &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/probook/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>HP ProBook 4520s Assessment</title>
		<link>/hp-probook-4520s-assessment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4520s]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[probook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-probook-4520s-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The HP ProBook 4520s is aimed toward small and medium companies. This 15.6 inch laptop computer is the successor to the ProBook 4510s. Whereas its [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The HP ProBook 4520s is aimed toward small and medium companies. This 15.6 inch laptop computer is the successor to the ProBook 4510s. Whereas its predecessor had Intel Core 2 Duo processors, the brand new mannequin is accessible along with your selection of a Core i3, i5 and i7 processors.</p>
<p><b>Our HP ProBook 4520s Specs:</b></p>
<p>Processor: Intel Core i5 430M Processor (2.26GHz, 3MB cache)<br />OS: Microsoft Home windows 7 Skilled (32-bit)<br />Show: 15.6-inch LED-backlit anti-glare HD show (1366 x 768)<br />Graphics: Intel GMA HD Built-in Graphics<br />Reminiscence: 4GB DDR2 800MHz RAM<br />Laborious drive: 320GB 7200RPM HDD<br />Battery: 6-cell 47Whr battery</p>
<p>Worth as configured: $749</p>
<p><b>Construct and Design</b><br />The brand new HP ProBook 4520s incorporates a semi-rugged case design with brushed steel lid which seems extra sturdy than the plastic lid on the 4510s. The underside of the pocket book has no entry panels for user-replaceable components. So upgrading this machine down the road could also be a little bit of a problem. Construct high quality is great. The pocket book seems and feels stable in your arms.</p>
<p><b>Show</b><br />The ProBook 4520s has a 15.6 inch anti-glare show with a decision of 1366 x 768 pixels. The show options good coloration and distinction and the matte end makes it simpler to learn outdoor. Horizontal viewing angles are glorious, however vertical viewing angles are common.</p>
<p><b>Keyboard and Touchpad</b><br />The HP ProBook 4520s has a full-size chiclet model keyboard. There&#8217;s good spacing between the keys. One other main plus is the devoted quantity pad which can turn out to be useful in case you use your laptop for information entry. The keyboard exhibits barely any flex in any respect and the keys present good tactile suggestions.</p>
<p>The Synaptics touchpad has a button-less design. It exhibits good sensitivity and is straightforward to make use of. However the button-less format has its share of drawbacks. This association can also require some getting used to.</p>
<p><b>Ports and Options</b><br />Port choice is passable. There are 3 USB 2.0 ports, one eSATA/USB combo port, VGA, HDMI-output, LAN and audio jacks. There&#8217;s additionally an ExpressCard/34 slot and SDHC-card reader for growth.</p>
<p><b>Efficiency and Benchmarks</b><br />The ProBook 4520s options Intel Core sequence processors which provide good efficiency. HP gives pre-configured fashions with the Intel Core i3 350M processor and the Intel Core i5 430M. Customized configurations with as much as the two.66GHz Core i7 620M and ATI Radeon 4350 devoted graphics are additionally attainable.</p>
<p>The 4520s gives considerably higher efficiency than the 4510s in lots of respects. The brand new Core i5 processor is far sooner than the Core 2 Duo seen within the earlier mannequin. Graphics efficiency has additionally improved. The machine can simply deal with HD video content material. The 4520s has a sooner 7200rpm arduous drive as in opposition to the slower 5400rpm arduous drive seen on the 4510s. Agreed, it is not as quick as the newest SSDs, however it does handle to cut back utility load occasions.</p>
<p><b>Warmth and Noise</b><br />Warmth and noise ranges are properly inside regular limits. The laptop computer is sort of lap-friendly.</p>
<p><b>Battery Life</b><br />The ProBook 4520s comes commonplace with a 47Wh 6-cell battery. It will get a bit over 4 hours of battery life. It&#8217;s price mentioning that the 4510s with its 63Wh 8-cell battery will get over 5 hours.</p>
<p><b>Conclusion</b><br />The HP ProBook 4520s is certainly price contemplating in case you are available in the market for a transportable enterprise laptop computer. It&#8217;s reasonably priced and is considerably higher than its predecessor in each seems and efficiency. The button-free touchpad, nevertheless, badly wants some refinement. You may additionally need to spend money on a bigger battery in case you journey quite a bit.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HP ProBook 650 G3 Evaluation &#8211; A Should-Have Enterprise Pocket book With Safety and Collaboration Options</title>
		<link>/hp-probook-650-g3-evaluation-a-should-have-enterprise-pocket-book-with-safety-and-collaboration-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[–]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[650]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[book]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[collaboration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[must-have]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[notebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pocket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[probook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[should-have]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[with]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/hp-probook-650-g3-review-a-must-have-business-notebook-with-security-and-collaboration-features/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is a sensible choice of a enterprise pocket book with its clean system efficiency, simple deployment, and security measures. You possibly can rely on [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is a sensible choice of a enterprise pocket book with its clean system efficiency, simple deployment, and security measures. You possibly can rely on getting essentially the most out of your funding with the HP ProBook 650 G3, as its configurations help all of as we speak&#8217;s technological necessities. It may be described as a 15.6-inch mid-range enterprise laptop computer.</p>
<p>The 15.6-inch show has anti-glare and LED-backlit know-how. The bottom / least expensive configuration choice has a show decision of 1366 x 768, however you&#8217;ll be able to go for a greater one for those who select a distinct configuration. It additionally comes with a 720p HD digital camera for video-chatting. The stereo audio system and microphone are built-in.</p>
<p>Even at peak efficiency, the pocket book doesn&#8217;t overheat. All the parts keep comparatively low, it doesn&#8217;t matter what sorts of duties you&#8217;ve operating. The premium keyboard is designed to be spill-resistant and straightforward to look after. The touchpad has an on / off button and helps two-way scrolling, two-finger zooming, tapping, and a wide range of different gestures.</p>
<p>The general design of the HP ProBook 650 G3 is good, and it has a beginning weight of 5.1-lbs, making it an average-sized enterprise pocket book. With particular security measures comparable to HP BIOSphere, you&#8217;ve every thing it&#8217;s worthwhile to forestall downtime and information breaches. Theft prevention is supplied with TPM 2.0 know-how, HP Fingerprint Sensor, Password Supervisor, and the lock slot, though the lock itself is bought individually.</p>
<p><u><strong>HP ProBook 650 G3 Specs</strong></u></p>
<p>The bottom mannequin comes with the next:</p>
<p>&bull; Twin-core Intel Core i5 processor (seventh era) 2.5 Ghz / as much as 3.1 Ghz with turbo enhance</p>
<p>&bull; 2 SODIMM reminiscence slots / one occupied with 4GB DDR4 2133 SDRAM</p>
<p>&bull; 128 GB SSD drive M.2 SATA TLC</p>
<p>&bull; Intel HD built-in graphics (620)</p>
<p>&bull; DVD-writer optical drive</p>
<p>&bull; Home windows 10 Professional OS 64</p>
<p>There are alternatives to go along with a extra highly effective processor and develop the reminiscence for those who require extra.</p>
<p>It comes with every thing you want for collaboration, regardless of the place you&#8217;re taking the laptop computer to: HP Audio Increase, Noise Cancellation Software program, Skype, 720p webcam, and so on. The three-cell, 48-WH Li-Ion prismatic battery has a protracted life and might run for a number of hours. The ability provide is supplied through a 65-W Good AC adapter.</p>
<p>You get the latest dual-band wi-fi AC (2×2) know-how mixed with Bluetooth 4.2 for networking. The laptop computer gives help for SD, SDXC, and SDHC card studying. Connectivity is straightforward because of the two USB 3.0 (one for charging) ports, 1 Sort-C USB port, DIsplayPort, VGA port, and extra.</p>
<p>Total, the HP ProBook 650 G3 is a superb selection for any skilled or enterprise person who needs an reasonably priced pocket book.</p>
<p>HP gives notebooks and tablets to swimsuit the necessity of any enterprise person. The ProBook collection positively options a number of the greatest notebooks &#8211; and they&#8217;re all reasonably priced because of HP low cost gives. Get your self a <a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" href="https://www.dealectronic.com/hp/">HP ProBook 650 G3</a> coupon and get began along with your order.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
