<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>smart &#8211; Gaurav Mobile</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/smart/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Gaurav Mobile Blog , Mobile Review, Mobile tech releted site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Newest Android Telephones Providing Hello-Fi and Good Music</title>
		<link>/the-newest-android-telephones-providing-hello-fi-and-good-music/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[and]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hello-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hi-fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[newest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[providing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telephones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/the-latest-android-phones-offering-hi-fi-and-smart-music/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We knew {that a} revolution was happening when world smartphone manufacturers launched in India a collection of handsets incorporating Hello-fi and good music as their fundamental theme. Their motto for the Indian viewers is to Play Hello-fi and Stay Good. The providing was one-of-its-kind within the nation and proved to be a boon for music lovers. Addressing the mid-range market, the manufacturing firms launched music-based android telephones within the worth vary of INR 15,000 to twenty,000.</p>
<p><strong>Comfortable Listening on Funtouch OS</strong></p>
<p>The collection was designed solely for Indian clients to expertise Hello-fi music within the thinnest doable metallic physique with a customized Funtouch OS. These fastidiously crafted, smooth and light-weight handsets are full of specs to enrich the enthusiastic, energetic and passionate Indian youth of at the moment.</p>
<p><strong>Limitless Downloads with Expandable Reminiscence</strong></p>
<p>To supply sooner pace that matches the superior sound high quality of those gadgets, they&#8217;re geared up with a Funtouch 2.1 (based mostly on Android Lollipop 5.0) Working System. They&#8217;re powered by a 64-bit Octa-Core Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a space for storing of 16GB ROM and 2GB RAM expandable as much as 128GB. The expansive storage capability helps you to obtain limitless music, video games and films, and permits you to surf and share with ease.</p>
<p><strong>Go on with the Lengthy-Lasting Battery</strong></p>
<p>The musical expertise is healthier when you might have a long-lasting 2300mAh battery with stamina mode, permitting your android telephone to go on and on for fairly lengthy. Including to the delight is an ultra-slim and curvy physique that blends completely with its eagle eye engineering precision.</p>
<p><strong>Double Twin Audio Audio system</strong></p>
<p>The handsets have double twin sound programs together with two skilled degree 5 magnetic circuit audio system to choose up the slightest of sounds and supply minimal distortion. For the reason that producers are devoted to making sure one of the best sound high quality, they&#8217;ve a novel audio speaker at each ends of the telephone. Simply 0.4mm in diameter, the 140 dots speaker creates an final sound expertise.</p>
<p><strong>Get rid of Disturbing Noises with Professional-Stage Audio Chip</strong></p>
<p>One other characteristic that makes these telephones good is the skilled degree Hello-fi chip. It might play tunes over 105dB and beneath -95dB with the least doable sound distortion. It might produce high-fidelity high quality with a twin chip audio decoding programme to reinforce your general sound expertise. To make the expertise even higher, android telephone manufacturing firms are finishing up analysis and growth in areas associated to enhancement of audio high quality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Android Sensible Cellphone Evaluate</title>
		<link>/android-sensible-cellphone-evaluate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 01:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cellphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evaluate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sensible]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2021/05/15/android-smart-phone-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been some time now because the first cellphone to make use of Google&#8217;s revolutionary Android Working System, the T Cellular G1, was launched [...]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been some time now because the first cellphone to make use of Google&#8217;s revolutionary Android Working System, the T Cellular G1, was launched and the idea appears to have gathered tempo considerably, with a number of recent Android cellphones and good telephones now obtainable. Here is transient evaluation of every of the previous and present Android telephones launched to this point.</p>
<p><strong>T Cellular G1</strong><br />
<br />The unique &#8216;Google Cellphone&#8217; launched after a lot hype in October 2008, the G1 was touted as the large risk to the established iPhone. It needs to be stated that the G1, manufactured by the Taiwanese cell specialists HTC, was one thing of a disappointment. The cellphone itself was cumbersome and the slide-out keyboard drew complaints for being unwieldy and unattainable to make use of with only one hand.</p>
<p>The G1 did, nevertheless, embody some improvements, most notably, the seamless integration of lots of Google&#8217;s well-known purposes similar to search, maps and avenue view. And most of the people who reviewed the cellphone have been impressed with the velocity and reliability of the connection made to the web whereas they have been out and about &#8211; this was, in spite of everything, a venture which aimed to make the web actually cell?</p>
<p><strong>HTC Magic</strong><br />
<br />The world did not have to attend lengthy for some enhancements to happen with the discharge of the HTC Magic in April 2009. The slide-out keyboard was ditched in favor of an intuitive contact display screen perform, the a lot criticised digicam was upgraded to three.2 mega pixels and the handset itself was smaller, lighter and rather more enticing.<br />
<br />The critics began to wonder if, in actual fact, Google have been on to one thing right here?</p>
<p><strong>HTC Hero</strong><br />
<br />Just some brief weeks later and the HTC Hero, also called the G2 Contact, got here onto the market and now folks actually have been taking discover. The HTC Hero is a smooth, trendy wanting handset with all the standard options and a few notable enhancements.</p>
<p>The three.2&#8243; show with touch-screen performance is shiny and responsive with an iPhone like &#8216;pinch-to-zoom&#8217; characteristic and likewise shows helpful climate updates in addition to updates on all of your favourite twitter and Fb feeds.<br />
<br />The Hero is also the primary cellphone to make use of HTC&#8217;s progressive &#8216;Sense&#8217; that includes seven particular person, personalized dwelling screens which will be modified with the sweep of a finger.</p>
<p><strong>HTC Tattoo</strong><br />
<br />The newest providing from HTC is aimed, primarily, on the finances and pre-pay market. A barely smaller and extra compact handset with a 2.8&#8243; display screen and a few trimming down within the characteristic division, the thought is clearly aimed toward bringing Android to the plenty and who would guess towards it?</p>
<p><strong>Motorola Dext</strong><br />
<br />It has been some time since Motorola have been linked with something that might be described as progressive however the Dext could nicely change a couple of perceptions of one of many authentic and oldest cell handset producers?</p>
<p>Along with the Android working system, Motorola have included their very own utility, generally known as &#8216;MotoBlur&#8217; which checks Twitter, MySpace and Fb for standing updates and shows these on one in all it is 5 dwelling screens. Clearly aimed on the social community era the Dext additionally re-introduces the slide-out QWERTY keyboard which is much more simple to make use of than the unique idea trialled within the G1. The Motorola additionally features a nifty safety utility which permits customers to remotely wipe all private knowledge from the cellphone ought to or not it&#8217;s misplaced or stolen.</p>
<p><strong>Samsung Galaxy i7500</strong><br />
<br />The primary Android cellphone on the O2 community, in addition to Samsung&#8217;s first foray on this sector, the Galaxy i7500 contains a 3.2&#8243; display screen, 8MB in-built reminiscence and a 5 mega pixel digicam with built-in flash and auto-focus. A few of the Android options have been lower down however, general, a top quality good cellphone that can undoubtedly be successful?</p>
<p>The velocity and tempo of growth of the Android venture over the past twelve months has been phenomenal and there will be no doubting Google&#8217;s dedication to be a serious power in cell expertise growth sooner or later. Whether or not the Google cellphone idea will ever topple Apple&#8217;s iPhone because the handset of alternative stays to be seen, however given the progress to this point it will likely be attention-grabbing to see how the idea develops over the following few years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
